(window["webpackJsonpogden-german"]=window["webpackJsonpogden-german"]||[]).push([[0],{32:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"id":0,"question":"come","answers":[{"word":"ankommen"},{"word":"treten","l":1},{"word":"herauskommen","l":1},{"word":"geschehen","l":1},{"word":"hierherkommen","l":1},{"word":"mitkommen","l":1},{"word":"rauskommen","l":1},{"word":"beikommen","l":1},{"word":"erh\xe4ltlich sein","l":1},{"word":"abspritzen","l":1},{"word":"gekommen"},{"word":"herausgekommen","l":1},{"word":"hierhergekommen","l":1},{"word":"eingekehrt","l":1},{"word":"machen"},{"word":"betragen","l":1}]},{"id":1,"question":"get","answers":[{"word":"werden"},{"word":"erhalten"},{"word":"bekommen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) verstehen"},{"word":"gelangen"},{"word":"jdm. etw. besorgen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) kapieren"},{"word":"schaffen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erreichen","l":1},{"word":"bringen","l":1},{"word":"nehmen","l":1},{"word":"kriegen","l":1},{"word":"sichDat etw.akk aneignen","l":1},{"word":"sichDat etw.Akk verschaffen","l":1},{"word":"gewinnen","l":1},{"word":"treten","l":1},{"word":"sichDat etw.Akk besorgen","l":1},{"word":"erzielen","l":1},{"word":"erlangen","l":1},{"word":"beziehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erwerben","l":1},{"word":"erwischen","l":1},{"word":"abbekommen","l":1},{"word":"sichDat etw.Akk zulegen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk checken","l":1},{"word":"mitbekommen","l":1},{"word":"sichDat etw.Akk anschaffen","l":1},{"word":"abkriegen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erringen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk schnallen","l":1}]},{"id":2,"question":"give","answers":[{"word":"(etw.Akk) bieten"},{"word":"verleihen"},{"word":"jdm. etw.Akk schenken"},{"word":"ergeben"},{"word":"spenden"},{"word":"etw.Akk abhalten"},{"word":"zuweisen"},{"word":"vermitteln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erteilen","l":1},{"word":"aufgeben","l":1},{"word":"zur\xfcckgeben","l":1},{"word":"erkl\xe4ren","l":1},{"word":"jdm. etw. mitgeben","l":1},{"word":"nachgeben","l":1},{"word":"verabreichen","l":1},{"word":"durchgeben","l":1},{"word":"bestellen","l":1},{"word":"federn","l":1},{"word":"hinreichen","l":1},{"word":"darreichen","l":1},{"word":"pfeifen","l":1},{"word":"applizieren","l":1},{"word":"verabfolgen","l":1},{"word":"Nachgiebigkeit","gender":"f"}]},{"id":3,"question":"go","answers":[{"word":"werden"},{"word":"fahren"},{"word":"laufen"},{"word":"passen"},{"word":"hingehen"},{"word":"verlaufen"},{"word":"kommen","l":1},{"word":"machen","l":1},{"word":"wandern","l":1},{"word":"treten","l":1},{"word":"ziehen","l":1},{"word":"weggehen","l":1},{"word":"fortfahren","l":1},{"word":"funktionieren","l":1},{"word":"Versuch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Anlauf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Go","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Elan","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":4,"question":"keep","answers":[{"word":"bleiben"},{"word":"aufbewahren"},{"word":"wahren"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) behalten"},{"word":"aufheben"},{"word":"einhalten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erhalten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zur\xfcckhalten","l":1},{"word":"bewahren","l":1},{"word":"beibehalten","l":1},{"word":"unterhalten","l":1},{"word":"einl\xf6sen","l":1},{"word":"reservieren","l":1},{"word":"versorgen","l":1},{"word":"aufhalten","l":1},{"word":"freihalten","l":1},{"word":"fortfahren","l":1},{"word":"bestehen lassen","l":1},{"word":"weitermachen","l":1},{"word":"aushalten","l":1},{"word":"beh\xfcten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk nicht weggeben","l":1},{"word":"Unterhalt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bergfried","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterhaltskosten","l":1}]},{"id":5,"question":"let","answers":[{"word":"lassen"},{"word":"etw.Akk vermieten"},{"word":"vermietet"},{"word":"Vermietung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Netzball","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":6,"question":"make","answers":[{"word":"(etw.Akk) machen"},{"word":"treffen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) bilden"},{"word":"etw.Akk erstellen"},{"word":"vornehmen"},{"word":"herstellen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) schaffen"},{"word":"erzeugen"},{"word":"verdienen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) anfertigen"},{"word":"basteln"},{"word":"ablegen"},{"word":"gestalten","l":1},{"word":"f\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"arbeiten","l":1},{"word":"bauen","l":1},{"word":"f\xe4llen","l":1},{"word":"zimmern","l":1},{"word":"abgeben","l":1},{"word":"zubereiten","l":1},{"word":"anbringen","l":1},{"word":"erheben","l":1},{"word":"eingehen","l":1},{"word":"anlegen","l":1},{"word":"kochen","l":1},{"word":"begehen","l":1},{"word":"anmachen","l":1},{"word":"schreinern","l":1},{"word":"Marke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Herstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fabrikat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Automarke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Machart","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":7,"question":"put","answers":[{"word":"legen"},{"word":"stecken"},{"word":"tun"},{"word":"ausdr\xfccken"},{"word":"hinsetzen"},{"word":"verwenden","l":1},{"word":"anlegen","l":1},{"word":"anbringen","l":1},{"word":"ausgeben","l":1},{"word":"hinstellen","l":1},{"word":"vorlegen","l":1},{"word":"gesetzt","l":1},{"word":"gesteckt","l":1},{"word":"getan","l":1}]},{"id":8,"question":"seem","answers":[{"word":"scheinen"},{"word":"erscheinen"},{"word":"wirken"},{"word":"vorkommen","l":1},{"word":"anmuten","l":1},{"word":"d\xfcnken","l":1}]},{"id":9,"question":"take","answers":[{"word":"\xfcbernehmen"},{"word":"dauern"},{"word":"ergreifen"},{"word":"mitnehmen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) aufnehmen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) einnehmen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) annehmen"},{"word":"brauchen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) beanspruchen"},{"word":"eingehen"},{"word":"erfordern"},{"word":"befolgen"},{"word":"besuchen","l":1},{"word":"halten","l":1},{"word":"holen","l":1},{"word":"vornehmen","l":1},{"word":"ablegen","l":1},{"word":"erobern","l":1},{"word":"wegnehmen","l":1},{"word":"schlagen","l":1},{"word":"sch\xf6pfen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk fassen","l":1},{"word":"ausf\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"besetzen","l":1},{"word":"vertragen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk stechen","l":1},{"word":"wegstecken","l":1},{"word":"aushalten","l":1},{"word":"unterbringen","l":1},{"word":"Einstellung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Einnahmen","l":1},{"word":"Beute","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Filmaufnahme","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":10,"question":"be","answers":[{"word":"stehen"},{"word":"liegen"},{"word":"bestehen"},{"word":"stattfinden"},{"word":"betragen"},{"word":"existieren"},{"word":"bilden","l":1},{"word":"sitzen","l":1}]},{"id":11,"question":"do","answers":[{"word":"(etw.Akk) tun"},{"word":"machen"},{"word":"unternehmen"},{"word":"erledigen"},{"word":"leisten"},{"word":"anfangen"},{"word":"absolvieren"},{"word":"anfertigen"},{"word":"treiben"},{"word":"geben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ausf\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"richten","l":1},{"word":"verrichten","l":1},{"word":"erweisen","l":1},{"word":"nachmachen","l":1},{"word":"Sitte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Feier","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":12,"question":"have","answers":[{"word":"etw.Akk haben"},{"word":"etw.Akk bieten"},{"word":"aufweisen"},{"word":"etw.Akk besitzen"},{"word":"aus\xfcben","l":1},{"word":"einnehmen","l":1},{"word":"einlegen","l":1}]},{"id":13,"question":"say","answers":[{"word":"(etw.Akk) sagen"},{"word":"sprechen"},{"word":"reden"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) besagen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) anmerken"},{"word":"feststellen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk \xe4u\xdfern","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) aussagen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) bemerken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk aussprechen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk artikulieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erw\xe4hnen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk anzeigen","l":1},{"word":"zum Beispiel"},{"word":"Mitspracherecht","gender":"n"},{"word":"Mitsprache","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesagte","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gesagtes","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"quasi"}]},{"id":14,"question":"see","answers":[{"word":"(etw.Akk) erkennen"},{"word":"verstehen"},{"word":"etw.Akk ansehen"},{"word":"aufsuchen"},{"word":"nachsehen"},{"word":"einsehen","l":1},{"word":"begreifen","l":1},{"word":"ersehen","l":1},{"word":"erblicken","l":1},{"word":"zusehen","l":1},{"word":"miterleben","l":1},{"word":"siehe"},{"word":"Bistum","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bischofssitz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Landeskirche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Di\xf6zese","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":15,"question":"send","answers":[{"word":"senden"},{"word":"schicken"},{"word":"verschicken"},{"word":"\xfcbersenden"},{"word":"(jdm.) (etw.Akk) zukommen lassen"},{"word":"etw.Akk abschicken"},{"word":"etw.Akk zuschicken"},{"word":"etw.Akk \xfcbermitteln","l":1},{"word":"versenden","l":1},{"word":"entsenden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bef\xf6rdern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk expedieren","l":1}]},{"id":16,"question":"may","answers":[{"word":"Mai","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bl\xfctezeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lenz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"d\xfcrfen"}]},{"id":17,"question":"will","answers":[{"word":"Willen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Wille","gender":"m"},{"word":"Testament","gender":"n"},{"word":"Bereitschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"letzter Wille","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":18,"question":"about","answers":[{"word":"\xfcber"},{"word":"um"},{"word":"etwa"},{"word":"ungef\xe4hr"},{"word":"circa"},{"word":"rund","l":1},{"word":"so","l":1},{"word":"zirka","l":1},{"word":"vielleicht","l":1},{"word":"herum","l":1},{"word":"umher","l":1}]},{"id":19,"question":"across","answers":[{"word":"\xfcber"},{"word":"durch"},{"word":"quer durch"},{"word":"jenseits"},{"word":"gegen\xfcber","l":1},{"word":"dar\xfcber","l":1},{"word":"quer","l":1},{"word":"kreuzweise","l":1},{"word":"waagerecht","l":1},{"word":"her\xfcber","l":1},{"word":"hin\xfcber","l":1},{"word":"r\xfcber","l":1},{"word":"quer dar\xfcber","l":1}]},{"id":20,"question":"after","answers":[{"word":"nach"},{"word":"gem\xe4\xdf"},{"word":"hinter","l":1},{"word":"nachdem"},{"word":"danach"},{"word":"sp\xe4ter","l":1},{"word":"nachher","l":1},{"word":"hinterher","l":1}]},{"id":21,"question":"against","answers":[{"word":"gegen"},{"word":"entgegen","l":1},{"word":"wider","l":1},{"word":"zuwider","l":1}]},{"id":22,"question":"among","answers":[{"word":"unter"},{"word":"zwischen"},{"word":"bei"},{"word":"inmitten"}]},{"id":23,"question":"at","answers":[{"word":"in"},{"word":"zu"},{"word":"im"},{"word":"auf"},{"word":"an"},{"word":"bei"},{"word":"\xfcber"},{"word":"um"},{"word":"um 5 Uhr","l":1}]},{"id":24,"question":"before","answers":[{"word":"vor"},{"word":"bis"},{"word":"zuvor"},{"word":"vorher"},{"word":"fr\xfcher","l":1},{"word":"voran","l":1}]},{"id":25,"question":"between","answers":[{"word":"zwischen"},{"word":"darunter","l":1},{"word":"mittendrin","l":1}]},{"id":26,"question":"by","answers":[{"word":"von"},{"word":"durch"},{"word":"mit"},{"word":"an"},{"word":"bei"},{"word":"nach"},{"word":"bis"},{"word":"per"},{"word":"seitens"},{"word":"neben"},{"word":"\xfcber","l":1},{"word":"mittels","l":1},{"word":"laut","l":1},{"word":"bis sp\xe4testens","l":1},{"word":"vorbei an","l":1},{"word":"von Seiten","l":1},{"word":"indem"},{"word":"vor\xfcber"}]},{"id":27,"question":"down","answers":[{"word":"ausgefallen"},{"word":"au\xdfer Betrieb"},{"word":"zusammengebrochen","l":1},{"word":"senkrecht","l":1},{"word":"unten"},{"word":"hinunter"},{"word":"herunter"},{"word":"runter"},{"word":"nach unten"},{"word":"hinab","l":1},{"word":"nieder","l":1},{"word":"herab","l":1},{"word":"abw\xe4rts","l":1},{"word":"unterhalb","l":1},{"word":"hernieder","l":1},{"word":"r\xfcckw\xe4rts","l":1},{"word":"Daunen"},{"word":"Daune","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Flaum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"H\xfcgelland","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"H\xf6henzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"niederschlagen"},{"word":"abschie\xdfen"},{"word":"herunterholen","l":1},{"word":"bezwingen","l":1},{"word":"zu Fall bringen","l":1}]},{"id":28,"question":"from","answers":[{"word":"von"},{"word":"aus"},{"word":"vom"},{"word":"vor"},{"word":"ab","l":1}]},{"id":29,"question":"in","answers":[{"word":"in"},{"word":"auf"},{"word":"im"},{"word":"an"},{"word":"herein","l":1},{"word":"hinein","l":1}]},{"id":30,"question":"off","answers":[{"word":"ausgeschaltet"},{"word":"abgeschaltet"},{"word":"verdorben"},{"word":"abseits"},{"word":"weg"},{"word":"los"},{"word":"abseits","l":1},{"word":"abseits von","l":1},{"word":"weg von","l":1},{"word":"herunter von","l":1},{"word":"herab von","l":1},{"word":"ab von","l":1}]},{"id":31,"question":"on","answers":[{"word":"in"},{"word":"auf"},{"word":"zu"},{"word":"bei"},{"word":"an"},{"word":"\xfcber"},{"word":"eingeschaltet"},{"word":"darauf","l":1},{"word":"dabei","l":1},{"word":"dran","l":1},{"word":"weiter","l":1}]},{"id":32,"question":"over","answers":[{"word":"\xfcber"},{"word":"gegen\xfcber"},{"word":"wegen","l":1},{"word":"oberhalb von","l":1},{"word":"oberhalb","l":1},{"word":"vorbei"},{"word":"zu Ende"},{"word":"her\xfcber"},{"word":"vor\xfcber"},{"word":"r\xfcber","l":1},{"word":"hin\xfcber","l":1},{"word":"quer dar\xfcber","l":1}]},{"id":33,"question":"through","answers":[{"word":"durch"},{"word":"\xfcber"},{"word":"bis","l":1},{"word":"w\xe4hrend","l":1},{"word":"via","l":1},{"word":"im Verlauf von","l":1},{"word":"Durchgangs-","l":1},{"word":"fertig","l":1},{"word":"durch"},{"word":"hindurch"},{"word":"zu Ende","l":1},{"word":"ganz durch","l":1},{"word":"bis zum Ende","l":1}]},{"id":34,"question":"to","answers":[{"word":"zu"},{"word":"auf"},{"word":"nach"},{"word":"an"},{"word":"bis"},{"word":"gegen"},{"word":"um zu"}]},{"id":35,"question":"under","answers":[{"word":"unter"},{"word":"hinter","l":1},{"word":"darunter","l":1},{"word":"unten","l":1},{"word":"hinunter","l":1}]},{"id":36,"question":"up","answers":[{"word":"auf"},{"word":"oben"},{"word":"hoch"},{"word":"nach oben"},{"word":"hinauf","l":1},{"word":"aufw\xe4rts","l":1},{"word":"herauf","l":1},{"word":"rauf","l":1},{"word":"empor","l":1},{"word":"hinan","l":1},{"word":"droben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erh\xf6hen"},{"word":"aufstehen","l":1},{"word":"entlang","l":1},{"word":"l\xe4ngs","l":1},{"word":"lang","l":1}]},{"id":37,"question":"with","answers":[{"word":"mit"},{"word":"zu"},{"word":"bei"},{"word":"vor"},{"word":"zusammen mit","l":1},{"word":"anhand","l":1}]},{"id":38,"question":"as","answers":[{"word":"als"},{"word":"wie"},{"word":"w\xe4hrend"},{"word":"da"},{"word":"weil"},{"word":"denn","l":1},{"word":"wie zum Beispiel","l":1},{"word":"gleichwie","l":1},{"word":"als"},{"word":"so"},{"word":"ebenso","l":1},{"word":"so dass"}]},{"id":39,"question":"for","answers":[{"word":"f\xfcr"},{"word":"auf"},{"word":"bei"},{"word":"aus"},{"word":"\xfcber"},{"word":"seit"},{"word":"wegen"},{"word":"pro","l":1},{"word":"denn","l":1},{"word":"weil","l":1}]},{"id":40,"question":"of","answers":[{"word":"von"},{"word":"an"},{"word":"aus"}]},{"id":41,"question":"till","answers":[{"word":"bis"},{"word":"bis in","l":1},{"word":"bestellen"},{"word":"bearbeiten"},{"word":"ackern"},{"word":"bebauen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bewirtschaften","l":1},{"word":"kultivieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk beackern","l":1},{"word":"Kasse","gender":"f"},{"word":"Geldkassette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geschiebelehm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geldkasse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geldschublade","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ladenkasse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geldkasten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geschiebemergel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tillit","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":42,"question":"than","answers":[{"word":"als"}]},{"id":43,"question":"the","answers":[{"word":"den"},{"word":"die","l":1}]},{"id":44,"question":"all","answers":[{"word":"alle"},{"word":"alles"},{"word":"jeder","l":1},{"word":"s\xe4mtlich","l":1},{"word":"s\xe4mtliche","l":1},{"word":"jede","l":1},{"word":"ganz","l":1},{"word":"vollst\xe4ndig","l":1},{"word":"v\xf6llig","l":1}]},{"id":45,"question":"any","answers":[{"word":"jede"},{"word":"irgendwelche"},{"word":"irgendeiner","l":1},{"word":"etwas","l":1},{"word":"irgendeine","l":1},{"word":"irgendetwas","l":1},{"word":"irgendein beliebiger","l":1}]},{"id":46,"question":"every","answers":[{"word":"jede"},{"word":"alle"},{"word":"jedwede"}]},{"id":47,"question":"little","answers":[{"word":"wenig"},{"word":"klein"},{"word":"gering"},{"word":"ein bisschen"},{"word":"bisserl","l":1},{"word":"bissel","l":1},{"word":"kaum"},{"word":"so wenig"}]},{"id":48,"question":"much","answers":[{"word":"sehr"},{"word":"weit"},{"word":"viel"},{"word":"weitaus","l":1},{"word":"bei weitem","l":1},{"word":"viel"},{"word":"so viel"},{"word":"so sehr"}]},{"id":49,"question":"no","answers":[{"word":"nicht"},{"word":"keine"},{"word":"kein"},{"word":"Nein","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Neinstimme","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":50,"question":"other","answers":[{"word":"andere"},{"word":"Sonstiges","l":1},{"word":"Verschiedenes","l":1},{"word":"sonstig"},{"word":"anderweitig","l":1},{"word":"zus\xe4tzlich","l":1}]},{"id":51,"question":"some","answers":[{"word":"einige"},{"word":"manche"},{"word":"ein paar"},{"word":"ein bisschen"},{"word":"manch"},{"word":"irgendeine","l":1},{"word":"irgendein","l":1},{"word":"welches","l":1},{"word":"irgendeines","l":1},{"word":"irgendetwas","l":1},{"word":"etwa"}]},{"id":52,"question":"such","answers":[{"word":"solche"},{"word":"solcher"},{"word":"solch"},{"word":"solches","l":1},{"word":"solcherlei","l":1},{"word":"so"},{"word":"derartig"}]},{"id":53,"question":"that","answers":[{"word":"dieser"},{"word":"welches"},{"word":"jener"},{"word":"den","l":1},{"word":"welche","l":1},{"word":"denen","l":1},{"word":"dies","l":1},{"word":"das da","l":1},{"word":"welcher","l":1},{"word":"jene","l":1},{"word":"jenes","l":1},{"word":"derjenige","l":1},{"word":"diejenige","l":1},{"word":"dasjenige","l":1},{"word":"so"},{"word":"damit"},{"word":"so dass","l":1},{"word":"sodass","l":1},{"word":"auf dass","l":1},{"word":"so dass"}]},{"id":54,"question":"this","answers":[{"word":"den"},{"word":"dieser"},{"word":"dieses"},{"word":"dem","l":1}]},{"id":55,"question":"he","answers":[{"word":"er"}]},{"id":56,"question":"you","answers":[{"word":"Sie"},{"word":"Ihnen"},{"word":"man"},{"word":"du"},{"word":"euch"},{"word":"dir"},{"word":"dich"}]},{"id":57,"question":"who","answers":[{"word":"den","l":1},{"word":"das","l":1},{"word":"welche","l":1},{"word":"welcher","l":1},{"word":"wen","l":1},{"word":"welches","l":1},{"word":"wem","l":1}]},{"id":58,"question":"and","answers":[{"word":"und"},{"word":"sowie"}]},{"id":59,"question":"because","answers":[{"word":"weil"},{"word":"da"},{"word":"denn"},{"word":"zumal","l":1},{"word":"alldieweil","l":1},{"word":"dieweil","l":1},{"word":"sintemal","l":1}]},{"id":60,"question":"but","answers":[{"word":"aber"},{"word":"sondern"},{"word":"doch"},{"word":"au\xdfer","l":1},{"word":"allein","l":1},{"word":"ohne dass","l":1},{"word":"au\xdfer dass","l":1},{"word":"blo\xdf","l":1},{"word":"nur"},{"word":"allerdings","l":1},{"word":"daf\xfcr","l":1},{"word":"obendrein","l":1},{"word":"mit Ausnahme von"}]},{"id":61,"question":"or","answers":[{"word":"bzw.","l":1},{"word":"oder auch","l":1},{"word":"oder so"}]},{"id":62,"question":"if","answers":[{"word":"wenn"},{"word":"falls"},{"word":"sofern"},{"word":"ob"},{"word":"wenn ja"}]},{"id":63,"question":"though","answers":[{"word":"obwohl"},{"word":"jedoch"},{"word":"wenngleich"},{"word":"aber","l":1},{"word":"obgleich","l":1},{"word":"obschon","l":1},{"word":"immerhin","l":1},{"word":"wiewohl","l":1},{"word":"obzwar","l":1},{"word":"gleichwohl","l":1},{"word":"allerdings"},{"word":"immerhin","l":1}]},{"id":64,"question":"while","answers":[{"word":"w\xe4hrend"},{"word":"obwohl"},{"word":"indem","l":1},{"word":"solange","l":1},{"word":"wohingegen","l":1},{"word":"derweil","l":1},{"word":"indes","l":1},{"word":"dieweil","l":1},{"word":"indessen","l":1},{"word":"wogegen","l":1},{"word":"Weile","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeitspanne","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"eine Weile"}]},{"id":65,"question":"how","answers":[{"word":"wie"},{"word":"inwiefern"},{"word":"wodurch"}]},{"id":66,"question":"when","answers":[{"word":"wenn"},{"word":"als"},{"word":"sobald"},{"word":"w\xe4hrend"},{"word":"da","l":1},{"word":"wann"}]},{"id":67,"question":"where","answers":[{"word":"wo"},{"word":"wohin"}]},{"id":68,"question":"why","answers":[{"word":"warum"},{"word":"weshalb"},{"word":"wieso","l":1},{"word":"weswegen","l":1},{"word":"wozu","l":1}]},{"id":69,"question":"again","answers":[{"word":"erneut"},{"word":"noch einmal"},{"word":"nochmals","l":1},{"word":"wiederum","l":1},{"word":"nochmal","l":1},{"word":"abermals","l":1},{"word":"noch mal","l":1},{"word":"schon wieder","l":1},{"word":"mal wieder","l":1},{"word":"von neuem","l":1},{"word":"neuerlich","l":1},{"word":"ferner","l":1},{"word":"neuerdings","l":1}]},{"id":70,"question":"ever","answers":[{"word":"immer"},{"word":"jemals"},{"word":"je"},{"word":"schon mal"},{"word":"st\xe4ndig","l":1}]},{"id":71,"question":"far","answers":[{"word":"weit"},{"word":"fern"},{"word":"weit"},{"word":"weitaus"},{"word":"viel","l":1},{"word":"fern","l":1},{"word":"bislang"},{"word":"bisher"},{"word":"bis jetzt"},{"word":"bisherig","l":1},{"word":"bis hierher","l":1}]},{"id":72,"question":"forward","answers":[{"word":"vordere"},{"word":"vorderer","l":1},{"word":"vorderes","l":1},{"word":"vorlaut","l":1},{"word":"dreist","l":1},{"word":"weiter"},{"word":"vorw\xe4rts"},{"word":"nach vorne"},{"word":"bugw\xe4rts","l":1},{"word":"weiterleiten"},{"word":"etw.Akk weiterleiten"},{"word":"senden"},{"word":"bef\xf6rdern"},{"word":"f\xf6rdern"},{"word":"\xfcbersenden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk \xfcbermitteln","l":1},{"word":"voranbringen","l":1},{"word":"schicken","l":1},{"word":"versenden","l":1},{"word":"absenden","l":1},{"word":"vorantreiben","l":1},{"word":"nachschicken","l":1},{"word":"verschicken","l":1},{"word":"weiterschicken","l":1},{"word":"beg\xfcnstigen","l":1},{"word":"expedieren","l":1},{"word":"nachsenden","l":1},{"word":"St\xfcrmer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Angreifer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Angreiferin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xfcrmerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Angriffsspieler","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":73,"question":"here","answers":[{"word":"hier"},{"word":"da"},{"word":"hierher"},{"word":"dabei","l":1},{"word":"hierbei","l":1},{"word":"hierhin","l":1},{"word":"hieran","l":1},{"word":"hierauf","l":1}]},{"id":74,"question":"near","answers":[{"word":"nahe"},{"word":"in der N\xe4he"},{"word":"unweit","l":1},{"word":"fast","l":1},{"word":"nahezu","l":1},{"word":"beinahe","l":1},{"word":"nahe an","l":1},{"word":"heran","l":1},{"word":"schier","l":1},{"word":"bei"},{"word":"in der N\xe4he von"},{"word":"nah","l":1}]},{"id":75,"question":"now","answers":[{"word":"jetzt"},{"word":"nun"},{"word":"gerade"},{"word":"nunmehr","l":1},{"word":"eben","l":1},{"word":"gleich","l":1}]},{"id":76,"question":"out","answers":[{"word":"aus"},{"word":"heraus"},{"word":"hinaus"},{"word":"drau\xdfen"},{"word":"hervor"},{"word":"au\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"raus","l":1},{"word":"ausw\xe4rts","l":1},{"word":"zu Ende","l":1},{"word":"au\xdfer Haus","l":1},{"word":"vor\xfcber","l":1},{"word":"jdn. outen"}]},{"id":77,"question":"still","answers":[{"word":"still"},{"word":"ruhig"},{"word":"schweigend"},{"word":"bewegungslos","l":1},{"word":"ohne Kohlens\xe4ure","l":1},{"word":"windstill","l":1},{"word":"reglos","l":1},{"word":"unbewegt","l":1},{"word":"feststehend","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk nicht bewegend","l":1},{"word":"immer noch"},{"word":"noch immer"},{"word":"dennoch"},{"word":"doch"},{"word":"trotzdem","l":1},{"word":"weiter","l":1},{"word":"nach wie vor","l":1},{"word":"immerhin","l":1},{"word":"Standbild","gender":"n"},{"word":"Stille","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Standfoto","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Brennerei","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Destillierapparat","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fotografie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Destillationsapparat","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"beruhigen"},{"word":"beschwichtigen","l":1},{"word":"bes\xe4nftigen","l":1},{"word":"gl\xe4tten","l":1},{"word":"abklingen lassen","l":1}]},{"id":78,"question":"then","answers":[{"word":"dann"},{"word":"anschlie\xdfend"},{"word":"danach"},{"word":"damals"},{"word":"nun","l":1},{"word":"darauf","l":1},{"word":"sodann","l":1},{"word":"folglich","l":1},{"word":"alsdann","l":1}]},{"id":79,"question":"there","answers":[{"word":"dort"},{"word":"da"},{"word":"dahin"},{"word":"dabei","l":1},{"word":"dorthin","l":1}]},{"id":80,"question":"together","answers":[{"word":"ausgeglichen"},{"word":"gemeinsam"},{"word":"zusammen"},{"word":"miteinander"},{"word":"aneinander","l":1},{"word":"zueinander","l":1},{"word":"beieinander","l":1},{"word":"beisammen","l":1},{"word":"zugleich","l":1}]},{"id":81,"question":"well","answers":[{"word":"so"},{"word":"also"},{"word":"gesund"},{"word":"gut"},{"word":"sehr","l":1},{"word":"wohl","l":1},{"word":"hervorragend","l":1},{"word":"sch\xf6n","l":1},{"word":"wohlauf","l":1},{"word":"g\xe4nzlich","l":1},{"word":"nun","l":1},{"word":"ja","l":1},{"word":"na ja","l":1},{"word":"hm","l":1},{"word":"Brunnen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Quelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bohrloch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ursprung","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Brunnenschacht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schacht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Senke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wanne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tiefbett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kuhle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"quellen"},{"word":"sprudeln"},{"word":"gut"},{"word":"sch\xf6n"},{"word":"brav"},{"word":"lieb"},{"word":"g\xfcltig"},{"word":"g\xfcnstig","l":1},{"word":"geh\xf6rig","l":1},{"word":"zutr\xe4glich","l":1},{"word":"artig","l":1},{"word":"triftig","l":1}]},{"id":82,"question":"almost","answers":[{"word":"fast"},{"word":"nahezu"},{"word":"beinahe"},{"word":"bald"},{"word":"geradezu","l":1},{"word":"ann\xe4hernd","l":1},{"word":"schier","l":1},{"word":"quasi","l":1},{"word":"beinah","l":1},{"word":"so gut wie","l":1}]},{"id":83,"question":"enough","answers":[{"word":"ausreichend"},{"word":"hinreichend","l":1},{"word":"gen\xfcgend"}]},{"id":84,"question":"even","answers":[{"word":"gerade"},{"word":"gleich"},{"word":"eben"},{"word":"gleichm\xe4\xdfig"},{"word":"glatt"},{"word":"quitt"},{"word":"ausgeglichen","l":1},{"word":"geradzahlig","l":1},{"word":"b\xfcndig","l":1},{"word":"flach","l":1},{"word":"unentschieden","l":1},{"word":"gleich gro\xdf","l":1},{"word":"punktgleich","l":1},{"word":"platt","l":1},{"word":"in gleicher H\xf6he","l":1},{"word":"auch"},{"word":"noch"},{"word":"selbst"},{"word":"sogar"},{"word":"gar","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberhaupt","l":1},{"word":"selbst dann"},{"word":"trotzdem","l":1},{"word":"ebnen"}]},{"id":85,"question":"not","answers":[{"word":"nicht"},{"word":"kein"}]},{"id":86,"question":"only","answers":[{"word":"alleinig"},{"word":"nur"},{"word":"erst"},{"word":"lediglich"},{"word":"noch","l":1},{"word":"einzig","l":1},{"word":"ausschlie\xdflich","l":1},{"word":"blo\xdf","l":1}]},{"id":87,"question":"quite","answers":[{"word":"ganz"},{"word":"ziemlich"},{"word":"recht"},{"word":"durchaus","l":1},{"word":"v\xf6llig","l":1},{"word":"wirklich","l":1},{"word":"vollst\xe4ndig","l":1}]},{"id":89,"question":"very","answers":[{"word":"sehr"},{"word":"hoch"},{"word":"ganz"},{"word":"recht"},{"word":"\xe4u\xdferst"},{"word":"wirklich","l":1},{"word":"extrem","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberaus","l":1},{"word":"enorm","l":1}]},{"id":90,"question":"tomorrow","answers":[{"word":"morgen"}]},{"id":91,"question":"yesterday","answers":[{"word":"Gestern","gender":"n"},{"word":"gestrig"},{"word":"gestern"},{"word":"am gestrigen Tage","l":1}]},{"id":92,"question":"north","answers":[{"word":"Nord","gender":"m"},{"word":"Norden","gender":"m"},{"word":"n\xf6rdlich"},{"word":"nach Norden"},{"word":"nordw\xe4rts"}]},{"id":93,"question":"south","answers":[{"word":"S\xfcd","gender":"m"},{"word":"S\xfcden","gender":"m"},{"word":"s\xfcdlich"},{"word":"nach S\xfcden","l":1},{"word":"s\xfcdw\xe4rts","l":1}]},{"id":94,"question":"east","answers":[{"word":"Osten","gender":"m"},{"word":"Orient","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Morgenland","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Osten","gender":"m"},{"word":"\xf6stlich"},{"word":"nach Osten","l":1},{"word":"ostw\xe4rts","l":1}]},{"id":95,"question":"west","answers":[{"word":"Westen","gender":"m"},{"word":"westlich"}]},{"id":96,"question":"please","answers":[{"word":"bitte"},{"word":"bitte sehr","l":1},{"word":"bitte"},{"word":"(jdm.) gefallen"},{"word":"erfreuen"},{"word":"Freude machen"},{"word":"behagen","l":1},{"word":"gef\xe4llig sein","l":1},{"word":"begl\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"angenehm sein","l":1},{"word":"verw\xf6hnen","l":1}]},{"id":97,"question":"yes","answers":[{"word":"ja"},{"word":"aber ja","l":1},{"word":"jawohl","l":1},{"word":"Ja","gender":"n"}]},{"id":98,"question":"account","answers":[{"word":"Konto","gender":"n"},{"word":"Account","gender":"m"},{"word":"Rechnung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Rechenschaft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kunde","gender":"m"},{"word":"Berechnung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Darstellung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bericht","gender":"m"},{"word":"Beschreibung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abrechnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Forderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wiedergabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erkl\xe4rung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erz\xe4hlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auflistung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bedeutung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schilderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ursache","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rechenschaftsbericht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rechenschaft ablegen"}]},{"id":99,"question":"act","answers":[{"word":"Gesetz","gender":"n"},{"word":"Akt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Tat","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schau","gender":"f"},{"word":"Handlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Haltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Darbietung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pose","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"handeln"},{"word":"wirken"},{"word":"auftreten"},{"word":"agieren","l":1},{"word":"arbeiten","l":1},{"word":"reagieren","l":1},{"word":"geben","l":1},{"word":"verfahren","l":1},{"word":"funktionieren","l":1},{"word":"darstellen","l":1},{"word":"Ma\xdfnahmen ergreifen","l":1},{"word":"vorgehen","l":1},{"word":"auff\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"mimen","l":1},{"word":"ansetzen","l":1},{"word":"schauspielern","l":1},{"word":"Theater spielen","l":1},{"word":"vorspielen","l":1}]},{"id":100,"question":"addition","answers":[{"word":"Hinzuf\xfcgen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Erg\xe4nzung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hinzuf\xfcgung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Addition","gender":"f"},{"word":"Nachtrag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Anbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zuwachs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zusatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zugabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zuschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Beigabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Addieren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Beimischung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zutat","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einf\xfcgung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beif\xfcgung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beimengung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zusammenrechnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dazugeben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anlagerung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vermehrung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":101,"question":"adjustment","answers":[{"word":"Anpassung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Umstellung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Korrektur","gender":"f"},{"word":"Einstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wertberichtigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ver\xe4nderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xc4nderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einstellen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Abstimmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Justierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Berichtigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausgleich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Regelung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abgleich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Regulierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Justieren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Justage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Neuausrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Angleichung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Nachstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bereinigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einstellvorgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einregulierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Adaptierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gew\xf6hnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schadensregelung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Richtigstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) anpassen"},{"word":"regeln"},{"word":"etw.Akk einstellen"},{"word":"abstimmen"},{"word":"verstellen"},{"word":"ausrichten"},{"word":"etw.Akk \xe4ndern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk justieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk korrigieren","l":1},{"word":"richten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ver\xe4ndern","l":1},{"word":"regulieren","l":1},{"word":"abgleichen","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk umstellen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk berichtigen","l":1},{"word":"ausgleichen","l":1},{"word":"nachstellen","l":1},{"word":"angleichen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk einregeln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk in Ordnung bringen","l":1},{"word":"ordnen","l":1},{"word":"anordnen","l":1},{"word":"adjustieren","l":1},{"word":"bereinigen","l":1},{"word":"einpassen","l":1},{"word":"zurechtr\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"zurichten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ausregeln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk richtigstellen","l":1}]},{"id":102,"question":"advertisement","answers":[{"word":"Werbung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anzeige","gender":"f"},{"word":"Reklame","gender":"f"},{"word":"Werbeanzeige","gender":"f"},{"word":"Inserat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Annonce","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ank\xfcndigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausschreibung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeitungsanzeige","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Werbespot","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bekanntmachung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeitungsinserat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bewerbung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Suchanzeige","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Werbeplakat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"werben"},{"word":"bewerben"},{"word":"etw.Akk inserieren"},{"word":"ank\xfcndigen"},{"word":"Werbung machen"},{"word":"etw.Akk anzeigen","l":1},{"word":"ausschreiben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk annoncieren","l":1},{"word":"Reklame machen","l":1},{"word":"anpreisen","l":1}]},{"id":103,"question":"agreement","answers":[{"word":"Vereinbarung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zustimmung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vertrag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abkommen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Einigung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Einvernehmen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Absprache","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einverst\xe4ndnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Einwilligung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Agreement","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Abmachung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verabredung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verst\xe4ndigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abrede","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pakt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kongruenz","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":104,"question":"air","answers":[{"word":"Luft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Auftreten","gender":"n"},{"word":"Atemluft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wetter","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aussehen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"\xc4ther","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Haltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Melodie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Miene","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pose","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lied","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gestus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) l\xfcften"},{"word":"senden"},{"word":"entl\xfcften","l":1},{"word":"bel\xfcften","l":1},{"word":"Luft auff\xfcllen","l":1},{"word":"durchl\xfcften","l":1}]},{"id":105,"question":"amount","answers":[{"word":"Betrag","gender":"m"},{"word":"H\xf6he","gender":"f"},{"word":"Summe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Menge","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anzahl","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geldbetrag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Umfang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ma\xdf","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anteil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Quantum","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"betragen"},{"word":"ausmachen","l":1},{"word":"ausmachen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk auf etw.Akk beziffern","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Dat) gleichkommen","l":1}]},{"id":106,"question":"amusement","answers":[{"word":"Unterhaltung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Belustigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vergn\xfcgen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Erheiterung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Heiterkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vergn\xfcgung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zerstreuung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Am\xfcsement","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kurzweil","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gaudium","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"(jdn.) unterhalten"},{"word":"am\xfcsieren"},{"word":"erheitern","l":1},{"word":"jdm. Spa\xdf machen","l":1},{"word":"erg\xf6tzen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. ablenken","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk unterhalten","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk am\xfcsieren","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk zerstreuen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk belustigen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk verlustieren","l":1}]},{"id":107,"question":"animal","answers":[{"word":"Tier","gender":"n"},{"word":"tierisch","l":1},{"word":"animalisch","l":1}]},{"id":108,"question":"answer","answers":[{"word":"jdm. antworten"},{"word":"etw.Akk beantworten"},{"word":"sichAkk verantworten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erwidern","l":1},{"word":"l\xf6sen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk entgegnen","l":1},{"word":"abheben","l":1},{"word":"abnehmen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk entgegenhalten","l":1},{"word":"Antwort","gender":"f"},{"word":"L\xf6sung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Beantwortung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ergebnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Reaktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erwiderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bescheid","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xfcckantwort","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Klageerwiderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entgegnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Antwortschreiben","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":109,"question":"apparatus","answers":[{"word":"Apparat","gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorrichtung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ger\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Apparatur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausr\xfcstung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":110,"question":"approval","answers":[{"word":"Zustimmung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Genehmigung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abnahme","gender":"f"},{"word":"Einverst\xe4ndnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Best\xe4tigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Annahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zulassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Billigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einwilligung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Freigabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anerkennung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bewilligung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Akzeptanz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verabschiedung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zuschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Beifall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bef\xfcrwortung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lob","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Plazet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Guthei\xdfung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":111,"question":"argument","answers":[{"word":"Argument","gender":"n"},{"word":"Streit","gender":"m"},{"word":"Auseinandersetzung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Argumentation","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"These","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beweis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Debatte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beweisf\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Diskussion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Parameter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Er\xf6rterung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wortwechsel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Widerrede","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beweisgrund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Knies","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":112,"question":"art","answers":[{"word":"Kunst","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kunstfertigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kunsterziehung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeichenunterricht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kunstgriff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geschick","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":113,"question":"attack","answers":[{"word":"Angriff","gender":"m"},{"word":"Attacke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Befall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sturm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Offensive","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sturmreihe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sturmlauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"(jdn./etw.Akk) angreifen"},{"word":"befallen","l":1},{"word":"(jdn./etw.Akk) attackieren","l":1},{"word":"(jdn.) anfallen","l":1},{"word":"(jdn.) \xfcberfallen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) in Angriff nehmen","l":1},{"word":"(jdn.) angehen","l":1},{"word":"anst\xfcrmen","l":1},{"word":"st\xfcrmen","l":1},{"word":"vorsto\xdfen","l":1}]},{"id":114,"question":"attempt","answers":[{"word":"Versuch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bem\xfchen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ansatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anlauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bestreben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Unternehmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorsto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bestrebung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) versuchen"},{"word":"den Versuch unternehmen","l":1},{"word":"wagen","l":1},{"word":"erproben","l":1}]},{"id":115,"question":"attention","answers":[{"word":"Aufmerksamkeit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Augenmerk","gender":"n"},{"word":"Achtung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Beachtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Acht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sorgfalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ber\xfccksichtigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorsicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zuwendung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wartung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Umsicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Obacht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abruf","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":116,"question":"attraction","answers":[{"word":"Attraktion","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anziehungskraft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anziehung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Reiz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Attraktivit\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anziehungspunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anreiz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sehensw\xfcrdigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verlockung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zugkraft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Affinit\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zauber","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zugnummer","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":117,"question":"authority","answers":[{"word":"Beh\xf6rde","gender":"f"},{"word":"Autorit\xe4t","gender":"f"},{"word":"Befugnis","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kompetenz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Instanz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Macht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vollmacht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Obrigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Berechtigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erm\xe4chtigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufsicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gewalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Souver\xe4nit\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kenner","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Weisungsbefugnis","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Amtsgewalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kapazit\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Befehlsgewalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Experte","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Legitimation","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ansehen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Machtvollkommenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Quelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"zuverl\xe4ssige Quelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Amtsbefugnis","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Expertin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Herrschaftsgewalt","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":118,"question":"back","answers":[{"word":"r\xfcckw\xe4rtig"},{"word":"zur\xfcck"},{"word":"retour"},{"word":"r\xfcckw\xe4rts","l":1},{"word":"R\xfccken","gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xfcckseite","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fond","gender":"m"},{"word":"Lehne","gender":"f"},{"word":"R\xfcckwand","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"R\xfcckenlehne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hintergrund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hinterseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Heck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kehrseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"hinterer Teil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wagenfond","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Buckel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xfcckfront","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"decken"},{"word":"(jdn.) unterst\xfctzen"},{"word":"setzen","l":1},{"word":"zur\xfcckschieben","l":1},{"word":"zur\xfcckfahren","l":1},{"word":"st\xfctzen","l":1},{"word":"auf etw.Akk setzen","l":1},{"word":"zur\xfccksto\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"bef\xfcrworten","l":1}]},{"id":119,"question":"balance","answers":[{"word":"Bilanz","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gleichgewicht","gender":"n"},{"word":"Saldo","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausgleich","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kontostand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Balance","gender":"f"},{"word":"Rest","gender":"m"},{"word":"Guthaben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Unterschiedsbetrag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausgewogenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausgeglichenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Restbetrag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Waage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unruh","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gegengewicht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Abgleich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Symmetrie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Differenz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Restsumme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xdcberschuss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Differenzbetrag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rechnungssaldo","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hauptgewicht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) ausgleichen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) balancieren"},{"word":"begleichen"},{"word":"bilanzieren","l":1},{"word":"saldieren","l":1},{"word":"ausbalancieren","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk ausbalancieren","l":1},{"word":"abw\xe4gen","l":1},{"word":"abstimmen","l":1},{"word":"die Balance halten","l":1},{"word":"auswuchten","l":1},{"word":"das Gleichgewicht halten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abgleichen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk im Gleichgewicht halten","l":1},{"word":"ins Gleichgewicht bringen","l":1}]},{"id":120,"question":"base","answers":[{"word":"Basis","gender":"f"},{"word":"Base","gender":"f"},{"word":"Grundlage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sockel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Boden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Grundplatte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xfctzpunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Grund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fu\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fundament","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Grundfl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ansatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterteil","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tr\xe4germaterial","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Grundstoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bezugswert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Grundstock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Grundlinie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zahlenbasis","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Standquartier","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bezugsgr\xf6\xdfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lauge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fliegerhorst","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Grundwert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Substrat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Postament","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Etappe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"gemein"},{"word":"niedertr\xe4chtig"},{"word":"nieder","l":1},{"word":"nichtsw\xfcrdig","l":1},{"word":"niedrig","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk basieren"},{"word":"etw.Akk gr\xfcnden","l":1},{"word":"begr\xfcnden","l":1}]},{"id":121,"question":"behavior","answers":[{"word":"Verhalten","gender":"n"},{"word":"Benehmen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Verhaltensweise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Handlungsweise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gebaren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Umgangsform","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Betragen","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":122,"question":"belief","answers":[{"word":"Glauben","gender":"m"},{"word":"Glaube","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ansicht","gender":"f"},{"word":"\xdcberzeugung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auffassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vertrauen","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":123,"question":"birth","answers":[{"word":"Geburt","gender":"f"},{"word":"Geburtsstunde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ursprung","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Herkunft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Niederkunft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abstammung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"geb\xe4ren"}]},{"id":124,"question":"bit","answers":[{"word":"Bit","gender":"n"},{"word":"St\xfcck","gender":"n"},{"word":"Trense","gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xfcckchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gebiss","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Deut","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schl\xfcsselbart","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bissen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"H\xe4ppchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kandare","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bart","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bin\xe4rzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"ein bisschen"},{"word":"bisserl","l":1},{"word":"ein Weilchen","l":1},{"word":"bissel","l":1},{"word":"(jdn.) bei\xdfen"},{"word":"stechen"},{"word":"zubei\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"zerstechen","l":1}]},{"id":125,"question":"bite","answers":[{"word":"Biss","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stich","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bei\xdfen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bissen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kleinigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bisswunde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Greifen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Happen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fassen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kaliberdruck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sch\xe4rfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(jdn.) bei\xdfen"},{"word":"stechen"},{"word":"zubei\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"zerstechen","l":1}]},{"id":126,"question":"blood","answers":[{"word":"Blut","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gebl\xfct","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schwei\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":127,"question":"blow","answers":[{"word":"Blasen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schlag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Blas","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schicksalsschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xfcckschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Streich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"blasen"},{"word":"wehen"},{"word":"durchbrennen"},{"word":"pusten"},{"word":"etw.Akk vermasseln"},{"word":"etw.Akk sprengen","l":1},{"word":"ausblasen","l":1},{"word":"anblasen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk platzen lassen","l":1},{"word":"schnaufen","l":1},{"word":"bl\xfchen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zerst\xf6ren","l":1}]},{"id":128,"question":"body","answers":[{"word":"K\xf6rper","gender":"m"},{"word":"Body","gender":"m"},{"word":"Geh\xe4use","gender":"n"},{"word":"Organ","gender":"n"},{"word":"Leiche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gremium","gender":"n"},{"word":"Einrichtung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Karosserie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Korpus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leib","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"K\xf6rperschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rumpf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leichnam","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hauptteil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klangk\xf6rper","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Masse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesellschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Menge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wagenkasten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Torso","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Institut","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vereinigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tote","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Komitee","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":129,"question":"brass","answers":[{"word":"Messing","gender":"n"},{"word":"Blech","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Messingschild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Messingplatte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Messingtafel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Messinggegenstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Moneten","l":1},{"word":"Kies","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Moos","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zaster","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Knete","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Frechheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Prostituierte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bulle","gender":"m"},{"word":"aus Messing"}]},{"id":130,"question":"bread","answers":[{"word":"Brot","gender":"n"},{"word":"Hostie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zaster","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Knete","gender":"f"},{"word":"Moos","gender":"n"},{"word":"panieren"}]},{"id":131,"question":"breath","answers":[{"word":"Atem","gender":"m"},{"word":"Atemzug","gender":"m"},{"word":"Hauch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Luft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Puste","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Atemluft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Odem","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schnaufer","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":132,"question":"brother","answers":[{"word":"Bruder","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kollege","gender":"m"}]},{"id":133,"question":"building","answers":[{"word":"Geb\xe4ude","gender":"n"},{"word":"Aufbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Haus","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bauwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Erstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Errichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufbauen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bauk\xf6rper","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Immobilie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Baut\xe4tigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bauausf\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bauingenieurwesen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Erbauung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) aufbauen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) errichten"},{"word":"bilden"},{"word":"etw.Akk schaffen","l":1},{"word":"erstellen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) herstellen","l":1},{"word":"gr\xfcnden","l":1},{"word":"basteln","l":1},{"word":"konstruieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erschaffen","l":1},{"word":"erbauen","l":1},{"word":"mauern","l":1}]},{"id":134,"question":"burn","answers":[{"word":"Brennen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Verbrennung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Brandfleck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Z\xfcndung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Brandwunde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ver\xe4tzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Brandstelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Brandmal","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"brennen"},{"word":"verbrennen"},{"word":"niederbrennen"},{"word":"anbrennen"},{"word":"verheizen"},{"word":"abbrennen","l":1},{"word":"verfeuern","l":1},{"word":"feuern","l":1},{"word":"leuchten","l":1},{"word":"ver\xe4tzen","l":1},{"word":"verkohlen","l":1},{"word":"gl\xfchen","l":1},{"word":"verschmoren","l":1}]},{"id":135,"question":"burst","answers":[{"word":"Ausbruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Explosion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Platzer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"H\xe4ufung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Farbsynchronsignal","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"platzen"},{"word":"bersten"},{"word":"zerspringen"},{"word":"zerplatzen"},{"word":"etw.Akk sprengen","l":1},{"word":"brechen","l":1},{"word":"aufplatzen","l":1},{"word":"ausbrechen","l":1},{"word":"zerbersten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zum Platzen bringen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk aufsprengen","l":1},{"word":"explodieren","l":1},{"word":"zersprengen","l":1},{"word":"durchbrechen","l":1},{"word":"krepieren","l":1},{"word":"geplatzt","l":1},{"word":"zersprungen","l":1},{"word":"aufgeplatzt","l":1},{"word":"gebrochen","l":1},{"word":"geborsten","l":1},{"word":"zum Platzen gebracht","l":1},{"word":"zerborsten","l":1},{"word":"gesprengt","l":1}]},{"id":136,"question":"business","answers":[{"word":"Business","gender":"n"},{"word":"Unternehmen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ft","gender":"n"},{"word":"Betrieb","gender":"m"},{"word":"Angelegenheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Firma","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsverkehr","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsleben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aufgabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Branche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gewerbe","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsbetrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Handel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sache","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beruf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gewerbebetrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Problem","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Laden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pflicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Chose","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"gesch\xe4ftlich"},{"word":"betriebswirtschaftlich"},{"word":"gewerblich"},{"word":"kaufm\xe4nnisch"},{"word":"dienstlich"},{"word":"unternehmerisch","l":1}]},{"id":137,"question":"butter","answers":[{"word":"Butter","gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk mit Butter bestreichen","l":1},{"word":"buttern","l":1}]},{"id":138,"question":"canvas","answers":[{"word":"Leinwand","gender":"f"},{"word":"Segeltuch","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gem\xe4lde","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tuch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kanevas","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Segeltuchbezug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zelttuch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Segelleinwand","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Drillich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wagenplane","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":139,"question":"care","answers":[{"word":"Sorgfalt","gender":"f"},{"word":"Pflege","gender":"f"},{"word":"Betreuung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorsicht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zuwendung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Versorgung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sorge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Behandlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xfcrsorge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Achtsamkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufsicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Obacht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sorgfaltspflicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Obhut","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Umsicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schonung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufbewahrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anteilnahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wartung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sorgf\xe4ltigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verwahrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kummer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"sorgen"},{"word":"beh\xfcten"}]},{"id":140,"question":"cause","answers":[{"word":"Ursache","gender":"f"},{"word":"Grund","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sache","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anlass","gender":"m"},{"word":"Anliegen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ausl\xf6ser","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verursacher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Erreger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Veranlassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beweggrund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"veranlassen"},{"word":"etw.Akk verursachen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) hervorrufen"},{"word":"ausl\xf6sen"},{"word":"erzeugen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) anrichten"},{"word":"stiften"},{"word":"erregen"},{"word":"herbeif\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"zuf\xfcgen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bewirken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bedingen","l":1},{"word":"weil"}]},{"id":141,"question":"chalk","answers":[{"word":"Kreide","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kalk","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kalkstein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kreidestift","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":142,"question":"chance","answers":[{"word":"Chance","gender":"f"},{"word":"M\xf6glichkeit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gelegenheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Risiko","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gl\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zufall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wahrscheinlichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aussicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xfcgung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wagnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"zuf\xe4llig"},{"word":"riskieren"},{"word":"wagen","l":1},{"word":"ein Risiko eingehen","l":1},{"word":"ein Wagnis eingehen","l":1},{"word":"zuf\xe4llig geschehen","l":1}]},{"id":143,"question":"change","answers":[{"word":"Ver\xe4nderung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wechsel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Wandel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abwechslung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wechselgeld","gender":"n"},{"word":"Umstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Austausch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wandlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Umstieg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wende","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Umtausch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Umwandlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ab\xe4nderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kleingeld","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Umkehr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Umschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wendung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Um\xe4nderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auswechslung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auswechselung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"M\xfcnzgeld","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"\xe4ndern"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) ver\xe4ndern"},{"word":"wechseln"},{"word":"umsteigen"},{"word":"tauschen"},{"word":"wandeln","l":1},{"word":"verwandeln","l":1},{"word":"austauschen","l":1},{"word":"umschalten","l":1},{"word":"ab\xe4ndern","l":1},{"word":"umtauschen","l":1},{"word":"schalten","l":1},{"word":"umbuchen","l":1},{"word":"verschieben","l":1},{"word":"umwandeln","l":1},{"word":"umstimmen","l":1},{"word":"umschlagen","l":1},{"word":"um\xe4ndern","l":1},{"word":"umlegen","l":1},{"word":"umschreiben","l":1},{"word":"umkrempeln","l":1},{"word":"einwechseln","l":1},{"word":"umwechseln","l":1},{"word":"trockenlegen","l":1},{"word":"ummodeln","l":1}]},{"id":144,"question":"cloth","answers":[{"word":"Tuch","gender":"n"},{"word":"Stoff","gender":"m"},{"word":"Lappen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Leinen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gewebe","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Putzlappen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Putztuch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tischtuch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wischlappen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wischtuch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zeug","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kaliko","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lumpen","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":145,"question":"coal","answers":[{"word":"Kohle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Steinkohle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kohle einnehmen","l":1},{"word":"bekohlen","l":1}]},{"id":146,"question":"color","answers":[{"word":"Farbe","gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk f\xe4rben"},{"word":"err\xf6ten"},{"word":"sichAkk f\xe4rben","l":1},{"word":"kolorieren","l":1},{"word":"ausmalen","l":1},{"word":"rot werden","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) farbig machen","l":1},{"word":"anmalen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk besch\xf6nigen","l":1}]},{"id":147,"question":"comfort","answers":[{"word":"Komfort","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gem\xfctlichkeit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Geborgenheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Trost","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Behaglichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bequemlichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Annehmlichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zufriedenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hilfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zuspruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abrollkomfort","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tr\xf6stung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lichtblick","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xfcckversicherung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausgeglichenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xfctze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"beruhigen"},{"word":"(jdn.) tr\xf6sten"},{"word":"ermutigen","l":1},{"word":"bes\xe4nftigen","l":1}]},{"id":148,"question":"committee","answers":[{"word":"Komitee","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ausschuss","gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorstand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kommission","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gremium","gender":"n"},{"word":"Pr\xe4sidium","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Arbeitsgemeinschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Organ","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":149,"question":"company","answers":[{"word":"Gesellschaft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Unternehmen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Firma","gender":"f"},{"word":"Begleitung","gender":"f"},{"word":"G\xe4ste"},{"word":"Betrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unternehmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kompanie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Handelsgesellschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Umgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Runde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Truppe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ensemble","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schauspieltruppe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftshaus","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"firmeneigen"},{"word":"werkseigen","l":1}]},{"id":150,"question":"comparison","answers":[{"word":"Vergleich","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abgleich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gegen\xfcberstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Komparation","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":151,"question":"competition","answers":[{"word":"Wettbewerb","gender":"m"},{"word":"Konkurrenz","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gewinnspiel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Wettkampf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wettstreit","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gegner","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auswahlverfahren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Konkurrenzkampf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Preisausschreiben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bewerb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wetteifer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Preisausschreibung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":152,"question":"condition","answers":[{"word":"Bedingung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zustand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Voraussetzung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Lage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Erkrankung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Auflage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Klausel","gender":"f"},{"word":"Beschaffenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorbedingung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kondition","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verfassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Situation","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gegebenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Befinden","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Leiden","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"k\xf6rperliche Verfassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"konditionieren"},{"word":"etw.Akk anpassen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zur Bedingung machen","l":1},{"word":"aufbereiten","l":1}]},{"id":153,"question":"connection","answers":[{"word":"Zusammenhang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verbindung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anbindung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anschluss","gender":"m"},{"word":"Beziehung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bezug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verbundenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verkn\xfcpfung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ankn\xfcpfung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bindeglied","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Querverbindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ankopplung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vereinigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anschlussflug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anschlussstutzen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Konnektion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verkehrsverbindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Konnex","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verkopplung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schaltverbindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anschlusszug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zwischenst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":154,"question":"control","answers":[{"word":"Kontrolle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Steuerung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bek\xe4mpfung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xdcberwachung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gewalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pr\xfcfung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Regulierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schalter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Regelung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ansteuerung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bedienung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beherrschung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Regler","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Controlling","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lenkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Herrschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kontrollelement","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bewirtschaftung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufsicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bedienungselement","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Einstellknopf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fuchtel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xfcberwachen"},{"word":"etw.Akk steuern"},{"word":"regeln"},{"word":"im Griff haben"},{"word":"z\xe4hmen"},{"word":"kontrollieren","l":1},{"word":"ansteuern","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberpr\xfcfen","l":1},{"word":"pr\xfcfen","l":1},{"word":"regulieren","l":1},{"word":"bek\xe4mpfen","l":1},{"word":"bet\xe4tigen","l":1},{"word":"lenken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk beaufsichtigen","l":1},{"word":"unter Kontrolle halten","l":1},{"word":"b\xe4ndigen","l":1},{"word":"bezwingen","l":1},{"word":"bez\xe4hmen","l":1}]},{"id":155,"question":"cook","answers":[{"word":"kochen"},{"word":"garen"},{"word":"zubereiten"},{"word":"sieden"},{"word":"Essen zubereiten"},{"word":"braten","l":1},{"word":"Koch","gender":"m"},{"word":"K\xf6chin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"K\xfcchenfee","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Nebenl\xf6sung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Klumpen bilden","l":1},{"word":"sintern","l":1},{"word":"zusammenbacken","l":1}]},{"id":156,"question":"copper","answers":[{"word":"Kupfer","gender":"n"},{"word":"Kessel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kupferm\xfcnze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Waschkessel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bulle","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"kupfern","l":1},{"word":"kupferrot","l":1}]},{"id":157,"question":"copy","answers":[{"word":"Kopie","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abschrift","gender":"f"},{"word":"Exemplar","gender":"n"},{"word":"Nachbildung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abzug","gender":"m"},{"word":"Imitation","gender":"f"},{"word":"Text","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausfertigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reproduktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fotokopie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vervielf\xe4ltigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Nachahmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Druckvorlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Durchschrift","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abdruck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Durchschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Photokopie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Manuskript","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Abbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Replik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abklatsch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ablichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Replikat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zweitschrift","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zweitausfertigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"kopieren"},{"word":"etw.Akk abschreiben"},{"word":"abmalen"},{"word":"imitieren"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) vervielf\xe4ltigen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk reproduzieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk duplizieren","l":1},{"word":"(jdn./etw.Akk) nachmachen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) nachbilden","l":1},{"word":"abgucken","l":1},{"word":"(jdn.) nachahmen","l":1},{"word":"abpausen","l":1},{"word":"(jdn.) nach\xe4ffen","l":1},{"word":"pausen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) ablichten","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) abzeichnen","l":1},{"word":"nachformen","l":1}]},{"id":158,"question":"cork","answers":[{"word":"Kork","gender":"m"},{"word":"Korken","gender":"m"},{"word":"Pfropfen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk verkorken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zukorken","l":1},{"word":"zupfropfen","l":1},{"word":"pfropfen","l":1}]},{"id":159,"question":"cotton","answers":[{"word":"Baumwolle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Watte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Garn","gender":"n"},{"word":"Baumwollgewebe","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Baumwollgarn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Baumwollstoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"N\xe4hgarn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"N\xe4hfaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kattun","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":160,"question":"cough","answers":[{"word":"husten"},{"word":"Husten","gender":"m"}]},{"id":161,"question":"country","answers":[{"word":"Land","gender":"n"},{"word":"Staat","gender":"m"},{"word":"Heimat","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gegend","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gel\xe4nde","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"l\xe4ndlich"}]},{"id":162,"question":"cover","answers":[{"word":"Abdeckung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Cover","gender":"n"},{"word":"Decke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Deckung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bezug","gender":"m"},{"word":"H\xfclle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Titelseite","gender":"f"},{"word":"Deckel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Versicherungsschutz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Umschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schutz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Plane","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Titelbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Haube","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Versicherung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einband","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Titel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Versicherungsdeckung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Klappe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ummantelung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Coverversion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mantel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Umh\xfcllung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schutzhaube","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Deckschicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Blende","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kappe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bedeckung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schutzumschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tarnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gedeck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verschlussdeckel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bespannung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeitungsmantel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Glocke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zudecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Eingussformh\xe4lfte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kuvert","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) decken"},{"word":"umfassen"},{"word":"erfassen"},{"word":"abdecken"},{"word":"versichern"},{"word":"bedecken"},{"word":"zur\xfccklegen"},{"word":"behandeln"},{"word":"verdecken"},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk abdecken","l":1},{"word":"zudecken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk beziehen","l":1},{"word":"belegen","l":1},{"word":"auslegen","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberziehen","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberdecken","l":1},{"word":"verkleiden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bespannen","l":1},{"word":"umh\xfcllen","l":1},{"word":"verh\xfcllen","l":1},{"word":"ummanteln","l":1},{"word":"einh\xfcllen","l":1},{"word":"einschlagen","l":1},{"word":"verh\xe4ngen","l":1},{"word":"einwickeln","l":1}]},{"id":163,"question":"crack","answers":[{"word":"Riss","gender":"m"},{"word":"Crack","gender":"n"},{"word":"Spalt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sprung","gender":"m"},{"word":"Witz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Spalte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Versuch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ritze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ritz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Knall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anriss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einriss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schrunde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fissur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schnalzer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Knack","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Knacks","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufbruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) knacken"},{"word":"zersplittern"},{"word":"brechen"},{"word":"zerbrechen"},{"word":"zusammenbrechen"},{"word":"spalten","l":1},{"word":"aufspringen","l":1},{"word":"krachen","l":1},{"word":"platzen","l":1},{"word":"einbrechen","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberkippen","l":1},{"word":"cracken","l":1},{"word":"aufknacken","l":1},{"word":"springen","l":1},{"word":"knallen","l":1},{"word":"zerspringen","l":1},{"word":"knack"},{"word":"erstklassig"}]},{"id":164,"question":"credit","answers":[{"word":"Kredit","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gutschrift","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ehre","gender":"f"},{"word":"Pump","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kreditw\xfcrdigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Guthaben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Darlehen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verdienst","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Glaube","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ansehen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Quellenangabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vertrauen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Glaubw\xfcrdigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entlastung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auszeichnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gutpunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Danksagung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Namensnennung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"gutschreiben"},{"word":"kreditieren","l":1},{"word":"anrechnen","l":1},{"word":"entlasten","l":1},{"word":"jdm. Glauben schenken","l":1}]},{"id":165,"question":"crime","answers":[{"word":"Kriminalit\xe4t","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verbrechen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Straftat","gender":"f"},{"word":"Delikt","gender":"n"},{"word":"Tat","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Frevel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"S\xfcnde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Untat","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schande","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":166,"question":"crush","answers":[{"word":"zerkleinern"},{"word":"vernichten"},{"word":"zerquetschen"},{"word":"zerstampfen"},{"word":"zerdr\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"zerschlagen","l":1},{"word":"quetschen","l":1},{"word":"brechen","l":1},{"word":"ausdr\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zerst\xf6ren","l":1},{"word":"zusammendr\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zermahlen","l":1},{"word":"zertreten","l":1},{"word":"zermalmen","l":1},{"word":"erdr\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"knicken","l":1},{"word":"zerknautschen","l":1},{"word":"zerschmettern","l":1},{"word":"zerknittern","l":1},{"word":"niederschlagen","l":1},{"word":"zerreiben","l":1},{"word":"schroten","l":1},{"word":"zerkn\xfcllen","l":1},{"word":"niederwerfen","l":1},{"word":"Gedr\xe4nge","gender":"n"},{"word":"Andrang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Massenandrang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gew\xfchl","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":167,"question":"cry","answers":[{"word":"schreien"},{"word":"rufen"},{"word":"heulen","l":1},{"word":"flennen","l":1},{"word":"Schrei","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ruf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausruf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufschrei","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":168,"question":"current","answers":[{"word":"aktuell"},{"word":"gegenw\xe4rtig"},{"word":"momentan"},{"word":"derzeitig"},{"word":"jetzig"},{"word":"laufend","l":1},{"word":"augenblicklich","l":1},{"word":"geltend","l":1},{"word":"g\xe4ngig","l":1},{"word":"bestehend","l":1},{"word":"gebr\xe4uchlich","l":1},{"word":"gel\xe4ufig","l":1},{"word":"herrschend","l":1},{"word":"Strom","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stromst\xe4rke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Str\xf6mung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"elektrischer Strom","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lauf","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":169,"question":"curve","answers":[{"word":"Kurve","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kr\xfcmmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bogen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Biegung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rundung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Linie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kurvenlineal","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Biege","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"biegen"},{"word":"schweifen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk w\xf6lben","l":1}]},{"id":170,"question":"damage","answers":[{"word":"Schaden","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sch\xe4den"},{"word":"Verlust","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verluste"},{"word":"Besch\xe4digung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verletzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schadensbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sch\xe4digung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beeintr\xe4chtigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beeintr\xe4chtigungen","l":1},{"word":"Havarie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"schaden"},{"word":"beeintr\xe4chtigen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) besch\xe4digen"},{"word":"sch\xe4digen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) l\xe4dieren","l":1},{"word":"versehren","l":1}]},{"id":171,"question":"danger","answers":[{"word":"Gefahr","gender":"f"},{"word":"Risiko","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gef\xe4hrdung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gef\xe4hrlichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bedrohung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":172,"question":"daughter","answers":[{"word":"Tochter","gender":"f"}]},{"id":173,"question":"day","answers":[{"word":"Tag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spieltag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tagesablauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"t\xe4glich"}]},{"id":174,"question":"death","answers":[{"word":"Todesfall","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ableben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ende","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sterben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lebensende","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sterbefall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Trauerfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Exitus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hingang","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":175,"question":"debt","answers":[{"word":"Schulden"},{"word":"Schuld","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verschuldung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Forderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verpflichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geldschuld","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verbindlichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":176,"question":"decision","answers":[{"word":"Entscheidung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Entschluss","gender":"m"},{"word":"Beschluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Urteil","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Entscheid","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wahl","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entschlossenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":177,"question":"degree","answers":[{"word":"Grad","gender":"n"},{"word":"Grad","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ma\xdf","gender":"n"},{"word":"Abschluss","gender":"m"},{"word":"Diplom","gender":"n"},{"word":"Hochschulabschluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausma\xdf","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Umfang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stufe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Universit\xe4tsabschluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Studienabschluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"akademischer Grad","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bogengrad","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":178,"question":"design","answers":[{"word":"Design","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gestaltung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Entwicklung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Konstruktion","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anordnung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Muster","gender":"n"},{"word":"Dessin","gender":"n"},{"word":"Konzeption","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Form","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Modell","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Entwurf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auslegung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Plan","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Planung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausf\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bauweise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Formgebung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeichnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bauart","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausgestaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Formgestaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Konstruktionslehre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Machart","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Skizze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"gestalten"},{"word":"etw.Akk entwickeln"},{"word":"etw.Akk konzipieren"},{"word":"auslegen"},{"word":"entwerfen"},{"word":"planen"},{"word":"etw.Akk konstruieren"},{"word":"designen"},{"word":"vorsehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk beabsichtigen","l":1},{"word":"zeichnen","l":1},{"word":"skizzieren","l":1},{"word":"ausbilden","l":1}]},{"id":179,"question":"desire","answers":[{"word":"Wunsch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Lust","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verlangen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Sehnsucht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Begierde","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wollen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Begehren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bestreben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bed\xfcrfnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Drang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leidenschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Begehrlichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Trieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Begehr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gel\xfcst","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Begier","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gel\xfcste","l":1},{"word":"w\xfcnschen"},{"word":"begehren"},{"word":"sichDat etw.Akk w\xfcnschen","l":1},{"word":"verlangen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk m\xf6chten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk haben wollen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk nach etw.Dat sehnen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ersehnen","l":1}]},{"id":180,"question":"destruction","answers":[{"word":"Zerst\xf6rung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vernichtung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Untergang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verw\xfcstung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Destruktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zerschlagung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abwrackung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beseitigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zertr\xfcmmerung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vertilgung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":181,"question":"detail","answers":[{"word":"Detail","gender":"n"},{"word":"Einzelheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausschnitt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Teil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Angabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausf\xfchrlichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bildausschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kleinigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Trupp","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"zuweisen"},{"word":"genau beschreiben"},{"word":"zuteilen","l":1},{"word":"abkommandieren","l":1},{"word":"genau berichten","l":1}]},{"id":182,"question":"development","answers":[{"word":"Entwicklung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Werden","gender":"n"},{"word":"Erarbeitung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufbau","gender":"m"},{"word":"Erschlie\xdfung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bebauung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Entwickeln","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Entwicklungsprozess","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Durchf\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bildung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verlauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Entstehung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausarbeitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entfaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Werdegang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fortentwicklung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Projektierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Planung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Herausbildung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entwicklungsgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufschluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ereignis","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":183,"question":"digestion","answers":[{"word":"Verdauung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verarbeitung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Digestion","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verdauungsprozess","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufschluss","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":184,"question":"direction","answers":[{"word":"Leitung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausrichtung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Regie","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anweisung","gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahrtrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verf\xfcgung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weisung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorschrift","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Laufrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Orientierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anleitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Himmelsrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lenkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tendenz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Str\xf6mung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stabf\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":185,"question":"discovery","answers":[{"word":"Entdeckung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fund","gender":"m"},{"word":"Erkenntnis","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Feststellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Befund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auffindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausforschungsbeweis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Offenlegung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"entdecken"},{"word":"feststellen"},{"word":"erfahren"},{"word":"etw.Akk erkunden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk kennenlernen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk herausfinden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk vorfinden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk aufsp\xfcren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk rausfinden","l":1}]},{"id":186,"question":"discussion","answers":[{"word":"Diskussion","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gespr\xe4ch","gender":"n"},{"word":"Auseinandersetzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Besprechung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Er\xf6rterung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Debatte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beratung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterhaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterredung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aussprache","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Konferenz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Durchsprache","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":187,"question":"disease","answers":[{"word":"Krankheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Erkrankung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Leiden","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Morbus","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":188,"question":"disgust","answers":[{"word":"Ekel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abscheu","gender":"f"},{"word":"Emp\xf6rung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verachtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Widerwille","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Entr\xfcstung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Absto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"emp\xf6ren","l":1},{"word":"jdm. zuwider sein","l":1},{"word":"absto\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"ver\xe4rgern","l":1},{"word":"anwidern","l":1},{"word":"entr\xfcsten","l":1}]},{"id":189,"question":"distance","answers":[{"word":"Abstand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Entfernung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ferne","gender":"f"},{"word":"Weg","gender":"m"},{"word":"Distanz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Strecke","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":190,"question":"distribution","answers":[{"word":"Verteilung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vertrieb","gender":"m"},{"word":"Distribution","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verbreitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auslieferung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Versand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Absatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Austeilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausgabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Streuung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aussch\xfcttung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausbreitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zuweisung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk verteilen"},{"word":"vertreiben"},{"word":"etw.Akk aussch\xfctten"},{"word":"absetzen"},{"word":"etw.Akk zuteilen","l":1},{"word":"ausgeben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk vermarkten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk austeilen","l":1},{"word":"verleihen","l":1}]},{"id":191,"question":"division","answers":[{"word":"Aufteilung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bereich","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abteilung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Division","gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterteilung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsbereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Teilen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Teil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sparte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unternehmensbereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsfeld","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Einteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gliederung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Trennung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Liga","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zweiteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kategorie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Skalenteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Trennlinie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sektor","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Untergliederung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufgliederung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spielklasse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufspaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kammer","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Trennungsstrich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hammelsprung","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk teilen"},{"word":"etw.Akk unterteilen"},{"word":"etw.Akk aufteilen"},{"word":"etw.Akk dividieren"},{"word":"verteilen","l":1},{"word":"trennen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk trennen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk spalten","l":1},{"word":"zerteilen","l":1},{"word":"entzweien","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk gliedern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abteilen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk aufgliedern","l":1}]},{"id":192,"question":"doubt","answers":[{"word":"Zweifel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bedenken"},{"word":"zweifeln"},{"word":"bezweifeln","l":1},{"word":"Zweifel hegen","l":1},{"word":"anzweifeln","l":1}]},{"id":193,"question":"drink","answers":[{"word":"trinken"},{"word":"Getr\xe4nk","gender":"n"},{"word":"Drink","gender":"m"},{"word":"Alkohol","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Trank","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Umtrunk","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Trunk","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gl\xe4schen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"auf jdn./etw.Akk ansto\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"(jdm.) zutrinken","l":1}]},{"id":194,"question":"driving","answers":[{"word":"fahrend"},{"word":"antreibend","l":1},{"word":"treibend","l":1},{"word":"heftig","l":1},{"word":"ansteuernd","l":1},{"word":"chauffierend","l":1},{"word":"lenkend","l":1},{"word":"st\xfcrmisch","l":1},{"word":"fahren"},{"word":"antreiben"},{"word":"Auto fahren"},{"word":"etw.Akk vorantreiben"},{"word":"treiben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk steuern","l":1},{"word":"lenken","l":1},{"word":"ansteuern","l":1},{"word":"chauffieren","l":1},{"word":"jagen","l":1},{"word":"karren","l":1},{"word":"vortreiben","l":1},{"word":"kutschieren","l":1}]},{"id":195,"question":"dust","answers":[{"word":"Staub","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abrieb","gender":"m"},{"word":"abstauben"},{"word":"best\xe4uben"},{"word":"Staub wischen"},{"word":"entstauben","l":1},{"word":"einst\xe4uben","l":1}]},{"id":196,"question":"earth","answers":[{"word":"Erde","gender":"f"},{"word":"Welt","gender":"f"},{"word":"Boden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Masse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erdung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erdreich","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Erdboden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bau","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":197,"question":"edge","answers":[{"word":"Rand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kante","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schneide","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorteil","gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorsprung","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Flanke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grenze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sch\xe4rfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Umrandung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Saum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ufer","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dachkante","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schliff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rahmen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einfassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grat","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"scharfe Kante","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Traufe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zacke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ansatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"vorstehender Grat","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"umranden"},{"word":"dr\xe4ngen"},{"word":"etw.Akk r\xe4ndern","l":1},{"word":"sch\xe4rfen","l":1},{"word":"antreiben","l":1},{"word":"einfassen","l":1},{"word":"s\xe4umen","l":1},{"word":"besetzen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk schieben","l":1},{"word":"schleifen","l":1},{"word":"ums\xe4umen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk begrenzen","l":1},{"word":"scharf machen","l":1}]},{"id":198,"question":"education","answers":[{"word":"Ausbildung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bildung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Erziehung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bildungswesen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schulbildung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterricht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schulung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"P\xe4dagogik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bildungsweg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterrichtswesen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Erziehungswesen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Erziehungswissenschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":199,"question":"effect","answers":[{"word":"Wirkung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Effekt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Auswirkung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kraft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Einfluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Folge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ergebnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"G\xfcltigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Eindruck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einwirkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausbeute","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) bewirken"},{"word":"etw.Akk verursachen"},{"word":"durchf\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"t\xe4tigen","l":1},{"word":"ausf\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erwirken","l":1},{"word":"bewerkstelligen","l":1},{"word":"herbeif\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"zu Stande bringen","l":1}]},{"id":200,"question":"end","answers":[{"word":"Ende","gender":"n"},{"word":"Aus","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schluss","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausgang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zweck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ziel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Abschluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Endpunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausklang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Beendung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Endst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zigarettenkippe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zipfel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kippe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zigarettenstummel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"enden"},{"word":"etw.Akk beenden"},{"word":"aufh\xf6ren"},{"word":"etw.Akk abschlie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"auslaufen","l":1},{"word":"beschlie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"endigen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk beendigen","l":1}]},{"id":201,"question":"error","answers":[{"word":"Fehler","gender":"m"},{"word":"Irrtum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Versehen","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":202,"question":"event","answers":[{"word":"Fall","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ereignis","gender":"n"},{"word":"Veranstaltung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Event","gender":"n"},{"word":"Anlass","gender":"m"},{"word":"Begebenheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorkommnis","gender":"n"},{"word":"Termin","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wettkampf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Disziplin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geschehnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wertungslauf","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":203,"question":"example","answers":[{"word":"Beispiel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Vorbild","gender":"n"},{"word":"Exemplar","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Fall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Muster","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Exempel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Beispielsatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Probe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leitbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Betrachtungsbeispiel","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":204,"question":"exchange","answers":[{"word":"Austausch","gender":"m"},{"word":"B\xf6rse","gender":"f"},{"word":"Umtausch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tausch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wechsel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geldwechsel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vermittlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fernsprechamt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zentrale","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abtausch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Telefonvermittlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auswechslung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schlagabtausch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einwechseln","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vermittlungsamt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vertauschung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wortwechsel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"austauschen"},{"word":"tauschen"},{"word":"umtauschen"},{"word":"etw.Akk wechseln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk auswechseln","l":1},{"word":"eintauschen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk einwechseln","l":1}]},{"id":205,"question":"existence","answers":[{"word":"Bestehen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Existenz","gender":"f"},{"word":"Leben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vorliegen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vorhandensein","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bestand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dasein","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vorkommen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"vorhanden"},{"word":"existent","l":1},{"word":"bestehend","l":1},{"word":"gegenw\xe4rtig","l":1},{"word":"pr\xe4sent","l":1}]},{"id":206,"question":"expansion","answers":[{"word":"Ausbau","gender":"m"},{"word":"Expansion","gender":"f"},{"word":"Entwicklung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Erweiterung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausweitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wachstum","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ausdehnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vergr\xf6\xdferung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erg\xe4nzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verbreiterung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausdehnen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Erweitern","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ausbreitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dehnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entfaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wachsen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"etw.Akk erweitern"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) ausbauen"},{"word":"etw.Akk expandieren"},{"word":"etw.Akk ausdehnen"},{"word":"etw.Akk aufbl\xe4hen"},{"word":"etw.Akk erh\xf6hen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ausweiten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk vergr\xf6\xdfern","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk ausdehnen","l":1},{"word":"dehnen","l":1},{"word":"aufsch\xe4umen","l":1},{"word":"nachr\xfcsten","l":1}]},{"id":207,"question":"experience","answers":[{"word":"Erfahrung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Erlebnis","gender":"n"},{"word":"Erleben","gender":"n"},{"word":"Erfahren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Praxis","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erfahrungswerte","l":1},{"word":"Routine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sachkenntnis","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Widerfahrnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"erfahren"},{"word":"erleben"},{"word":"sp\xfcren","l":1},{"word":"feststellen","l":1},{"word":"f\xfchlen","l":1},{"word":"Erfahrung machen","l":1},{"word":"eine Erfahrung machen","l":1},{"word":"empfinden","l":1},{"word":"durchmachen","l":1},{"word":"bemerken","l":1},{"word":"durchleben","l":1},{"word":"mitmachen","l":1}]},{"id":208,"question":"expert","answers":[{"word":"Experte","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sachverst\xe4ndiger","gender":"m"},{"word":"Fachmann","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sachverst\xe4ndige","gender":"f"},{"word":"Spezialist","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gutachter","gender":"m"},{"word":"Fachkundiger","gender":"m"},{"word":"Profi","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fachkraft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kenner","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sachkundige","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fachfrau","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Referent","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Koryph\xe4e","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sachkenner","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kapazit\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"erfahren"},{"word":"sachverst\xe4ndig"},{"word":"fachm\xe4nnisch","l":1},{"word":"fachkundig","l":1},{"word":"sachkundig","l":1},{"word":"geschickt","l":1},{"word":"kunstgerecht","l":1},{"word":"kunstfertig","l":1},{"word":"kennerhaft","l":1}]},{"id":209,"question":"fact","answers":[{"word":"Tatsache","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fakt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Faktum","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gegebenheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Umstand","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":210,"question":"fall","answers":[{"word":"Fallen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Fall","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sturz","gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xfcckgang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Untergang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Absturz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zerfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gef\xe4lle","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Niedergang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verringerung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abnahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einbruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Baisse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rutsch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Herbst","gender":"m"},{"word":"fallen"},{"word":"sinken"},{"word":"st\xfcrzen"},{"word":"scheitern"},{"word":"zur\xfcckgehen"},{"word":"abst\xfcrzen"},{"word":"verfallen","l":1},{"word":"abfallen","l":1},{"word":"umfallen","l":1},{"word":"absinken","l":1},{"word":"hinfallen","l":1},{"word":"umst\xfcrzen","l":1},{"word":"abnehmen","l":1},{"word":"nachgeben","l":1},{"word":"hereinbrechen","l":1},{"word":"fliegen","l":1},{"word":"purzeln","l":1},{"word":"plumpsen","l":1},{"word":"abgleiten","l":1},{"word":"hinst\xfcrzen","l":1},{"word":"anbrechen","l":1},{"word":"niedergehen","l":1},{"word":"zufallen"}]},{"id":211,"question":"family","answers":[{"word":"Familie","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sippe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geschlecht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anhang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"famili\xe4r"}]},{"id":212,"question":"father","answers":[{"word":"Vater","gender":"m"},{"word":"Pater","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pfarrer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk ins Leben rufen","l":1},{"word":"Urheber von etw. sein","l":1},{"word":"v\xe4terlich"}]},{"id":213,"question":"fear","answers":[{"word":"Angst","gender":"f"},{"word":"Furcht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schreck","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bef\xfcrchtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sorge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bangnis","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk bef\xfcrchten"},{"word":"etw.Akk f\xfcrchten"},{"word":"Angst haben"}]},{"id":214,"question":"feeling","answers":[{"word":"Gef\xfchl","gender":"n"},{"word":"Eindruck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Feeling","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Empfinden","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Emotion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Empfindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gem\xfct","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Meinung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Regung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ahnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"gef\xfchlvoll","l":1},{"word":"f\xfchlend","l":1},{"word":"empfindend","l":1},{"word":"sp\xfcrend","l":1},{"word":"mitf\xfchlend","l":1},{"word":"versp\xfcrend","l":1},{"word":"abtastend","l":1},{"word":"nachempfindend","l":1},{"word":"nachf\xfchlend","l":1},{"word":"betastend","l":1},{"word":"etw. f\xfchlen"},{"word":"etw. sp\xfcren"},{"word":"etw. glauben"},{"word":"etw.Akk empfinden"},{"word":"etw.Akk versp\xfcren"},{"word":"etw. anfassen"},{"word":"sichAkk befinden","l":1},{"word":"etw. nachempfinden","l":1},{"word":"etw. bef\xfchlen","l":1},{"word":"tasten","l":1},{"word":"etw. nachf\xfchlen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abtasten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk betasten","l":1},{"word":"jdn. verstehen"}]},{"id":215,"question":"fiction","answers":[{"word":"Fiktion","gender":"f"},{"word":"Belletristik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erdichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erfindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erz\xe4hlliteratur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Annahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Prosaliteratur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Romanliteratur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"sch\xf6ngeistige Literatur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"erfundene Geschichte","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":216,"question":"field","answers":[{"word":"Bereich","gender":"m"},{"word":"Feld","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gebiet","gender":"n"},{"word":"Branche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fachgebiet","gender":"n"},{"word":"Fachbereich","gender":"m"},{"word":"Weide","gender":"f"},{"word":"Spielfeld","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Fach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sektor","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fachrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sparte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Acker","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Platz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einsatzgebiet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"K\xf6rper","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Datenfeld","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Einsatzfeld","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sachgebiet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Rasenplatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"fangen"},{"word":"aufstellen"}]},{"id":217,"question":"fight","answers":[{"word":"Kampf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Fight","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schlacht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Streit","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auseinandersetzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Boxkampf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schl\xe4gerei","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gefecht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Rauferei","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Raufhandel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pr\xfcgelei","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"k\xe4mpfen"},{"word":"bek\xe4mpfen"},{"word":"ank\xe4mpfen"},{"word":"sichAkk streiten","l":1},{"word":"fighten","l":1},{"word":"boxen","l":1},{"word":"angehen","l":1},{"word":"gegen etw.Akk angehen","l":1},{"word":"Krach haben","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk keilen","l":1},{"word":"gegen jdn. boxen","l":1}]},{"id":218,"question":"fire","answers":[{"word":"Feuer","gender":"n"},{"word":"Brand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Beschuss","gender":"m"},{"word":"Flamme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schie\xdfen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Glut","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Brandstelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"entlassen"},{"word":"schie\xdfen"},{"word":"abdr\xfccken"},{"word":"abfeuern","l":1},{"word":"feuern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk anz\xfcnden","l":1},{"word":"brennen","l":1},{"word":"z\xfcnden","l":1},{"word":"abgeben","l":1},{"word":"befeuern","l":1},{"word":"verschie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"hinauswerfen","l":1},{"word":"abziehen","l":1},{"word":"anfeuern","l":1},{"word":"b\xf6llern","l":1},{"word":"jdn. feuern"},{"word":"jdn. hinauswerfen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. rauswerfen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. rausschmei\xdfen","l":1}]},{"id":219,"question":"flame","answers":[{"word":"Flamme","gender":"f"},{"word":"Feuer","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lohe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anpflaumerei","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Freundin","gender":"f"},{"word":"flammen"},{"word":"flambieren","l":1},{"word":"leuchten","l":1},{"word":"lodern","l":1}]},{"id":220,"question":"flight","answers":[{"word":"Flug","gender":"m"},{"word":"Flucht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Flugreise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fliehen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"H\xf6henflug","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":221,"question":"flower","answers":[{"word":"Bl\xfcte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Blume","gender":"f"},{"word":"bl\xfchen"}]},{"id":222,"question":"fold","answers":[{"word":"(etw.Akk) falten"},{"word":"zusammenklappen"},{"word":"etw.Akk verschr\xe4nken"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) knicken"},{"word":"etw.Akk falzen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk klappen","l":1},{"word":"zusammenlegen","l":1},{"word":"aussteigen","l":1},{"word":"zusammenfalten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk umknicken","l":1},{"word":"umbiegen","l":1},{"word":"abkanten","l":1},{"word":"brechen","l":1},{"word":"einwickeln","l":1},{"word":"eingehen","l":1},{"word":"Falz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Falte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Herde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abkantung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Talmulde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pferch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kniff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"H\xfcrde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk f\xe4llen"},{"word":"abholzen"},{"word":"umlegen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abhauen","l":1},{"word":"einschlagen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk umhauen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk schlagen","l":1},{"word":"bestialisch","l":1},{"word":"t\xf6dlich","l":1},{"word":"f\xfcrchterlich","l":1},{"word":"grausam","l":1}]},{"id":223,"question":"food","answers":[{"word":"Lebensmittel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Essen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Nahrung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Nahrungsmittel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Speise","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ern\xe4hrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verpflegung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Futter","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kost","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fressen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verk\xf6stigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Esswaren","l":1}]},{"id":224,"question":"force","answers":[{"word":"Kraft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gewalt","gender":"f"},{"word":"Macht","gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xe4rke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Truppe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zwang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wucht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einfluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wirkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Druck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Durchschlagskraft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"H\xe4rte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Willk\xfcr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"zwingen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) erzwingen"},{"word":"n\xf6tigen"},{"word":"forcieren","l":1},{"word":"jdn. dr\xe4ngen","l":1},{"word":"treiben","l":1},{"word":"zw\xe4ngen","l":1},{"word":"aufzwingen","l":1},{"word":"aufbrechen","l":1}]},{"id":225,"question":"form","answers":[{"word":"(etw.Akk) bilden"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) formen"},{"word":"gr\xfcnden"},{"word":"entstehen"},{"word":"gestalten"},{"word":"formieren"},{"word":"aufbauen"},{"word":"eingehen"},{"word":"sichAkk bilden","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk formen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk ausbilden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ausgestalten","l":1},{"word":"ausformen","l":1},{"word":"Form","gender":"f"},{"word":"Formular","gender":"n"},{"word":"Art","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gestalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gestaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Formblatt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vordruck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fragebogen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klasse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausformung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausgestaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schalung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Jahrgangsstufe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gebilde","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schulklasse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schulbank","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Drucksorte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verschalung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":226,"question":"friend","answers":[{"word":"Freund","gender":"m"},{"word":"Freundin","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bekannte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bekannter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kumpel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kamerad","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gevatterin","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":227,"question":"front","answers":[{"word":"Front","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorderseite","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fassade","gender":"f"},{"word":"Frontseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vordergrund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Brust","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorderfront","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stirnseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stirn","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anfang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"vordere"},{"word":"jdm. die Stirn bieten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Dat gegen\xfcberliegen","l":1}]},{"id":228,"question":"fruit","answers":[{"word":"Frucht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Obst","gender":"n"},{"word":"Resultat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ergebnis","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":229,"question":"glass","answers":[{"word":"Glas","gender":"n"},{"word":"Scheibe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gl\xe4schen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Becher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Trinkglas","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Spiegel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Becherglas","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"aus Glas"},{"word":"verglasen"}]},{"id":230,"question":"gold","answers":[{"word":"Gold","gender":"n"},{"word":"golden"}]},{"id":231,"question":"government","answers":[{"word":"Regierung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Landesregierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gouvernement","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"staatlich"}]},{"id":232,"question":"grain","answers":[{"word":"Getreide","gender":"n"},{"word":"Maserung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Korn","gender":"n"},{"word":"Struktur","gender":"f"},{"word":"Qu\xe4ntchen","gender":"n"},{"word":"K\xf6rnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Narben","l":1},{"word":"Fadenlauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Narbung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Faser","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Strich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"K\xf6rnigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Getreidekorn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Faserabweichung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"K\xf6rnchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Samenkorn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Saatkorn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Holzfaser","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Narbe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Faserung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kern","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gran","gender":"n"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) narben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk k\xf6rnen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk levantieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk krispeln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk marmorieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk chagrinieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk masern","l":1},{"word":"adern","l":1}]},{"id":233,"question":"grass","answers":[{"word":"Rasen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Spitzel","gender":"m"},{"word":"begr\xfcnen"}]},{"id":234,"question":"grip","answers":[{"word":"Griffigkeit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Halt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Haftung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Handgriff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Haltegriff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klammer","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reisetasche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Heft","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"packen"},{"word":"ergreifen"},{"word":"fassen"},{"word":"zugreifen","l":1},{"word":"zupacken","l":1}]},{"id":235,"question":"group","answers":[{"word":"Gruppe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Konzern","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verbund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gruppierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vereinigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schule","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verband","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Clique","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pulk","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kollegium","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Geschwader","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Herde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) gruppieren"},{"word":"in Gruppen einteilen","l":1}]},{"id":236,"question":"growth","answers":[{"word":"Wachstum","gender":"n"},{"word":"Entwicklung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Geschwulst","gender":"f"},{"word":"Tumor","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zuwachs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Steigerung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anstieg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wuchs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zunahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Expansion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Heranwachsen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bewuchs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gew\xe4chs","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wucherung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auswuchs","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":237,"question":"guide","answers":[{"word":"lotsen"},{"word":"anleiten"},{"word":"jdn. begleiten","l":1},{"word":"lenken","l":1},{"word":"beraten","l":1},{"word":"F\xfchrer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Anleitung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Handbuch","gender":"n"},{"word":"Leitfaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Reisef\xfchrer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"F\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reiseleiter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fremdenf\xfchrer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wegweiser","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Orientierungshilfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Orientierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reisef\xfchrerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fremdenf\xfchrerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reiseleiterin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Richtschnur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lenker","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anhaltspunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lotse","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Brevier","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"F\xfchrerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lenkerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Cicerone","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":238,"question":"harbor","answers":[{"word":"Hafen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterschlupf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zufluchtsort","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"beherbergen"},{"word":"bergen","l":1},{"word":"hegen","l":1},{"word":"jdm. Unterschlupf gew\xe4hren","l":1}]},{"id":239,"question":"harmony","answers":[{"word":"Harmonie","gender":"f"},{"word":"Einklang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zusammenklang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Harmonielehre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gleichgewicht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Harmonik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Eintracht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einvernehmen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wohlklang","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":240,"question":"hate","answers":[{"word":"Hass","gender":"m"},{"word":"hassen"},{"word":"nicht m\xf6gen","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk verabscheuen","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk nicht ausstehen k\xf6nnen","l":1}]},{"id":241,"question":"hearing","answers":[{"word":"Hearing","gender":"n"},{"word":"Anh\xf6rung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Geh\xf6r","gender":"n"},{"word":"Verhandlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"H\xf6ren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anh\xf6rungsverfahren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"H\xf6rverm\xf6gen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vernehmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gerichtsverhandlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geh\xf6rsinn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Audienz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anh\xf6ren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verh\xf6r","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"h\xf6rend","l":1},{"word":"anh\xf6rend","l":1},{"word":"vernehmend","l":1},{"word":"h\xf6ren"},{"word":"etw.Akk erfahren"},{"word":"erh\xf6ren"},{"word":"anh\xf6ren","l":1},{"word":"Bescheid bekommen","l":1}]},{"id":242,"question":"heat","answers":[{"word":"W\xe4rme","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hitze","gender":"f"},{"word":"Durchgang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Brunst","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rennen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Glut","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"L\xe4ufigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorlauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Brunstzeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausscheidungsrennen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Brunftzeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Paarungszeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausscheidungskampf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"heizen"},{"word":"erw\xe4rmen"},{"word":"aufheizen"},{"word":"erhitzen","l":1},{"word":"w\xe4rmen","l":1},{"word":"aufw\xe4rmen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) beheizen","l":1},{"word":"anw\xe4rmen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk befeuern","l":1},{"word":"warm werden","l":1}]},{"id":243,"question":"help","answers":[{"word":"helfen"},{"word":"jdn. unterst\xfctzen"},{"word":"f\xf6rdern","l":1},{"word":"verhelfen","l":1},{"word":"dienen","l":1},{"word":"jdm. weiterhelfen","l":1},{"word":"mitwirken","l":1},{"word":"mithelfen","l":1},{"word":"nachhelfen","l":1},{"word":"Hilfe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterst\xfctzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mithilfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hilfefunktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hilfeleistung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zutun","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aushilfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beistand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Handreichung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hilfskraft","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":244,"question":"history","answers":[{"word":"Geschichte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Historie","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorgeschichte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Werdegang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geschichtswissenschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":245,"question":"hole","answers":[{"word":"Loch","gender":"n"},{"word":"Bohrung","gender":"f"},{"word":"\xd6ffnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"L\xfccke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grube","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schlupfloch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"H\xf6hle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hohlraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Defektelektron","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kuhle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Markierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dreckloch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Nest","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Drecknest","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Knast","gender":"m"},{"word":"L\xf6cher in etw.Akk machen","l":1},{"word":"ein Loch in etw.Akk machen","l":1}]},{"id":246,"question":"hope","answers":[{"word":"Hoffnung","gender":"f"},{"word":"hoffen"}]},{"id":247,"question":"hour","answers":[{"word":"Stunde","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wegstunde","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":248,"question":"humor","answers":[{"word":"Humor","gender":"m"},{"word":"Komik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stimmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Witzigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":249,"question":"ice","answers":[{"word":"Eis","gender":"n"},{"word":"Eisw\xfcrfel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Klunker","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Diamant","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"vereisen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) glasieren","l":1}]},{"id":250,"question":"idea","answers":[{"word":"Idee","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorstellung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gedanke","gender":"m"},{"word":"Konzept","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ahnung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Plan","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Meinung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Begriff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Konzeption","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anregung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anschauung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":251,"question":"impulse","answers":[{"word":"Impuls","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ansto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anregung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reiz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Antrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Drang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Trieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stromsto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Regung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anwandlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anreiz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"pl\xf6tzliche Regung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Impetus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Triebkraft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kraftsto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kaprize","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":252,"question":"increase","answers":[{"word":"Erh\xf6hung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Steigerung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zunahme","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anstieg","gender":"m"},{"word":"Wachstum","gender":"n"},{"word":"Zuwachs","gender":"m"},{"word":"Erweiterung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vergr\xf6\xdferung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verst\xe4rkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausweitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vermehrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anhebung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufstockung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Versch\xe4rfung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Intensivierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Steigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hebung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Belebung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mehrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verschlimmerung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufbesserung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk erh\xf6hen"},{"word":"zunehmen"},{"word":"steigern"},{"word":"wachsen"},{"word":"ansteigen"},{"word":"vergr\xf6\xdfern"},{"word":"steigen"},{"word":"etw.Akk st\xe4rken"},{"word":"anwachsen"},{"word":"sichAkk vergr\xf6\xdfern","l":1},{"word":"erh\xf6ht werden","l":1},{"word":"erweitern","l":1},{"word":"vermehren","l":1},{"word":"heben","l":1},{"word":"mehren","l":1},{"word":"aufstocken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk heraufsetzen","l":1},{"word":"aufbessern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk potenzieren","l":1},{"word":"\xe4ufnen","l":1}]},{"id":253,"question":"industry","answers":[{"word":"Industrie","gender":"f"},{"word":"Branche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sektor","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gewerbe","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wirtschaftszweig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Industriezweig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"gewerbliche Wirtschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Flei\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Emsigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":254,"question":"ink","answers":[{"word":"Tinte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Farbe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Tusche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Druckfarbe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Druckerschw\xe4rze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"unterzeichnen"},{"word":"jdn. t\xe4towieren","l":1}]},{"id":255,"question":"insect","answers":[{"word":"Insekt","gender":"n"},{"word":"Kerf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kerbtier","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":256,"question":"instrument","answers":[{"word":"Instrument","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ger\xe4t","gender":"n"},{"word":"Werkzeug","gender":"n"},{"word":"Mittel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Messger\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Instrumentarium","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Apparat","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Urkunde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wertpapier","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Papier","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Handelspapier","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Armatur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"instrumentieren"}]},{"id":257,"question":"insurance","answers":[{"word":"Versicherung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Versicherungswesen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Assekuranz","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":258,"question":"interest","answers":[{"word":"Interesse","gender":"n"},{"word":"Zinsen"},{"word":"Aufmerksamkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bedeutung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zins","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verzinsung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorteil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Belang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wichtigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"interessieren"}]},{"id":259,"question":"invention","answers":[{"word":"Erfindung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Invention","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":260,"question":"iron","answers":[{"word":"Eisen","gender":"n"},{"word":"B\xfcgeleisen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schie\xdfeisen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Pl\xe4tteisen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"eisern"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) b\xfcgeln"},{"word":"aufb\xfcgeln","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) pl\xe4tten","l":1}]},{"id":261,"question":"jelly","answers":[{"word":"Gelee","gender":"n"},{"word":"G\xf6tterspeise","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wackelpudding","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gallerte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gallert","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wackelpeter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"S\xfclze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"gelieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk in Aspik einlegen","l":1}]},{"id":262,"question":"join","answers":[{"word":"etw.Dat beitreten"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) verbinden"},{"word":"sichAkk anschlie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk verbinden","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk treffen","l":1},{"word":"teilnehmen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. begleiten","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk vereinigen","l":1},{"word":"sich vereinigen","l":1},{"word":"besuchen","l":1},{"word":"in etw.Dat eintreten","l":1},{"word":"kombinieren","l":1},{"word":"zusammenf\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk zu jdm. setzen","l":1},{"word":"jdm./etw.Dat Gesellschaft leisten","l":1},{"word":"zusammenkommen","l":1},{"word":"dazusto\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"aneinander grenzen","l":1},{"word":"zusammengehen","l":1},{"word":"zusammensto\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk anf\xfcgen","l":1},{"word":"aneinanderf\xfcgen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk angliedern","l":1},{"word":"mit jdm. mitgehen","l":1},{"word":"zusammenwachsen","l":1},{"word":"in etw.Akk einm\xfcnden","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk begegnen","l":1},{"word":"in etw.Akk m\xfcnden","l":1},{"word":"zusammenflie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"Verbindung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verkn\xfcpfung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fuge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verbindungsstelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Naht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vereinigungsmenge","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":263,"question":"journey","answers":[{"word":"Reise","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahrt","gender":"f"},{"word":"Weg","gender":"m"},{"word":"Anfahrt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anfahrtsweg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"reisen"}]},{"id":264,"question":"judge","answers":[{"word":"Richter","gender":"m"},{"word":"Richterin","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schiedsrichter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kampfrichter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kampfrichterin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Preisrichterin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Punktrichterin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Punktrichter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sachverst\xe4ndige","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sachverst\xe4ndiger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"beurteilen"},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk einsch\xe4tzen"},{"word":"richten","l":1},{"word":"urteilen","l":1},{"word":"ermessen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verurteilen","l":1}]},{"id":265,"question":"jump","answers":[{"word":"Sprung","gender":"m"},{"word":"Absprung","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anstieg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"sprunghafter Anstieg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Flugschanze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Satz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"pl\xf6tzlicher Anstieg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"abspringen","l":1},{"word":"zusammenzucken","l":1},{"word":"emporschnellen","l":1},{"word":"einen Sprung machen","l":1}]},{"id":266,"question":"kick","answers":[{"word":"Kick","gender":"m"},{"word":"Spa\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Nervenkitzel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kitzel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Absto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schuss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fu\xdftritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hufschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xfccksto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fimmel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"kicken"},{"word":"sto\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"ausschlagen","l":1},{"word":"strampeln","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk einen Tritt geben","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk einen Tritt verpassen","l":1},{"word":"einen Fu\xdftritt geben","l":1},{"word":"auf jdn. eintreten","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk einen Fu\xdftritt verpassen","l":1},{"word":"hintreten","l":1}]},{"id":267,"question":"kiss","answers":[{"word":"(jdn.) k\xfcssen"},{"word":"jdn. b\xfctzen","l":1},{"word":"busseln","l":1},{"word":"Kuss","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bussi","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schmatzer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Karambolage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schmatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Busserl","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bussel","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":268,"question":"knowledge","answers":[{"word":"Wissen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Kenntnis","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kenntnisse"},{"word":"Erkenntnisse"},{"word":"Erkenntnis","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":269,"question":"land","answers":[{"word":"landen"},{"word":"anlegen"},{"word":"l\xf6schen","l":1},{"word":"anlanden","l":1},{"word":"aufsetzen","l":1},{"word":"aufkommen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk an Land ziehen","l":1},{"word":"ausschiffen","l":1},{"word":"ausladen","l":1},{"word":"Land","gender":"n"},{"word":"Festland","gender":"n"},{"word":"Grundst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Boden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Grund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bundesland","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Terrain","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Feld","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anwesen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Grund und Boden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Steg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"L\xf6tauge","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":270,"question":"language","answers":[{"word":"Sprache","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausdrucksweise","gender":"f"},{"word":"Programmiersprache","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Landessprache","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":271,"question":"laugh","answers":[{"word":"Lachen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Lache","gender":"f"},{"word":"Spa\xdf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Witz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lacher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"lachen"}]},{"id":272,"question":"law","answers":[{"word":"Recht","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gesetz","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gesetzgebung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rechtswissenschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rechtswesen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Regel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Juristerei","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Prinzip","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gebot","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lehrsatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"gesetzliche Vorschrift","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":273,"question":"lead","answers":[{"word":"anf\xfchren"},{"word":"vorangehen"},{"word":"lenken","l":1},{"word":"herbeif\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"f\xfchrend sein","l":1},{"word":"bleien","l":1},{"word":"vorausgehen","l":1},{"word":"ausspielen","l":1},{"word":"Blei","gender":"n"},{"word":"Leitung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorsprung","gender":"m"},{"word":"Hauptrolle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hinweis","gender":"m"},{"word":"Federf\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spitze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorreiterrolle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kabel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anschlussdraht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zuleitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anspiel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lot","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aufmacher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anhaltspunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bleistiftmine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leitartikel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wurfgewicht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anf\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gewindesteigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ader","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hundeleine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tipp","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":274,"question":"learning","answers":[{"word":"Lernen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Bildung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erlernen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wissen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lernprozess","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gelehrsamkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"erlernend","l":1},{"word":"erfahrend","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk lernen"},{"word":"etw.Akk erfahren"},{"word":"etw.Akk erlernen"},{"word":"h\xf6ren"},{"word":"etw.Akk in Erfahrung bringen","l":1},{"word":"dazulernen","l":1}]},{"id":275,"question":"leather","answers":[{"word":"Leder","gender":"n"},{"word":"ledern","l":1},{"word":"rindsledern","l":1}]},{"id":276,"question":"letter","answers":[{"word":"Schreiben","gender":"n"},{"word":"Buchstabe","gender":"m"},{"word":"Brief","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anschreiben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zuschrift","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schriftzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sendung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einsendung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Drucktype","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"beschriften"}]},{"id":277,"question":"level","answers":[{"word":"Ebene","gender":"f"},{"word":"Niveau","gender":"n"},{"word":"Level","gender":"n"},{"word":"Stufe","gender":"f"},{"word":"H\xf6he","gender":"f"},{"word":"Grad","gender":"m"},{"word":"Etage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Libelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pegel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"F\xfcllstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wasserwaage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spiegel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stockwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schwellwert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wasserpegel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sohle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Nivellierger\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Nivellierinstrument","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Deck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"eben"},{"word":"waagerecht"},{"word":"flach"},{"word":"plan"},{"word":"b\xfcndig","l":1},{"word":"gleichm\xe4\xdfig","l":1},{"word":"punktgleich","l":1},{"word":"h\xf6hengleich","l":1},{"word":"horizontal","l":1},{"word":"waagrecht","l":1},{"word":"auf gleicher Ebene","l":1},{"word":"s\xf6hlig","l":1},{"word":"platt","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) ebnen"},{"word":"angleichen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) planieren"},{"word":"nivellieren","l":1},{"word":"anpassen","l":1},{"word":"beseitigen","l":1},{"word":"abflachen","l":1},{"word":"ausgleichen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) einebnen","l":1},{"word":"gleichmachen","l":1}]},{"id":278,"question":"lift","answers":[{"word":"Lift","gender":"m"},{"word":"Hub","gender":"m"},{"word":"Mitfahrgelegenheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Erfolgserlebnis","gender":"n"},{"word":"Heben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Personenaufzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hubh\xf6he","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auftriebskraft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hebeb\xfchne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auftrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hochheben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Hochziehen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Hebevorrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufschwung","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hebung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahrstuhl","gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Winde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"anheben"},{"word":"aufheben"},{"word":"heben"},{"word":"abheben"},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk hochheben"},{"word":"sichAkk heben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk f\xf6rdern","l":1},{"word":"jdn. erheben","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk lichten","l":1},{"word":"lichten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk stemmen","l":1},{"word":"lupfen","l":1},{"word":"emporheben","l":1},{"word":"beseitigen","l":1},{"word":"in die H\xf6he halten","l":1},{"word":"aufpulvern","l":1},{"word":"Auftrieb geben","l":1},{"word":"hochhalten","l":1},{"word":"roden","l":1}]},{"id":279,"question":"light","answers":[{"word":"Licht","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ampel","gender":"f"},{"word":"Beleuchtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lichtquelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leuchte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lampe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Helligkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Beleuchtungsk\xf6rper","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Feuer","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Licht\xf6ffnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leuchtfeuer","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lichtschein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"leicht"},{"word":"hell"},{"word":"bek\xf6mmlich","l":1},{"word":"locker","l":1},{"word":"schwach","l":1},{"word":"luftig","l":1},{"word":"gelind","l":1},{"word":"gelinde","l":1},{"word":"glimpflich","l":1},{"word":"blond","l":1},{"word":"beleuchten"},{"word":"etw.Akk anz\xfcnden"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) erleuchten"},{"word":"etw.Akk anmachen"},{"word":"leuchten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erhellen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk entz\xfcnden","l":1},{"word":"z\xfcnden","l":1},{"word":"befeuern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk anbrennen","l":1},{"word":"anstecken","l":1},{"word":"anfeuern","l":1}]},{"id":280,"question":"limit","answers":[{"word":"Frist","gender":"f"},{"word":"Limit","gender":"n"},{"word":"Beschr\xe4nkung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Limes","gender":"m"},{"word":"Begrenzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"H\xf6chstgrenze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grenze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Obergrenze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grenzwert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Limitierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grenzbereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Belastungsgrenze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xc4u\xdferste","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schranke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) beschr\xe4nken"},{"word":"begrenzen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) einschr\xe4nken"},{"word":"etw.Akk limitieren"},{"word":"befristen"},{"word":"limitieren","l":1},{"word":"eingrenzen","l":1},{"word":"bremsen","l":1}]},{"id":281,"question":"linen","answers":[{"word":"W\xe4sche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bettw\xe4sche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bettzeug","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Laken","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wei\xdfwaren","l":1},{"word":"Linnen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Leinenzeug","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Leinzeug","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"leinen","l":1},{"word":"linnen","l":1},{"word":"s\xe4umen"},{"word":"auskleiden"},{"word":"auslegen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) f\xfcttern"},{"word":"ausschlagen","l":1},{"word":"ums\xe4umen","l":1},{"word":"ausf\xfcttern","l":1},{"word":"abf\xfcttern","l":1},{"word":"kaschieren","l":1}]},{"id":282,"question":"liquid","answers":[{"word":"fl\xfcssig"},{"word":"verf\xfcgbar","l":1},{"word":"zahlungsf\xe4hig","l":1},{"word":"Fl\xfcssigkeit","gender":"f"}]},{"id":283,"question":"list","answers":[{"word":"Liste","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verzeichnis","gender":"n"},{"word":"Aufstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auflistung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufz\xe4hlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schlagseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Register","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Leistchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kr\xe4ngung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"listen"},{"word":"auff\xfchren"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) auflisten"},{"word":"verzeichnen","l":1},{"word":"Schlagseite haben","l":1},{"word":"aufz\xe4hlen","l":1},{"word":"in eine Liste schreiben","l":1},{"word":"erfassen","l":1},{"word":"aufschreiben","l":1},{"word":"in einer Liste erfassen","l":1},{"word":"an der B\xf6rse zulassen","l":1},{"word":"in einer Liste aufstellen","l":1},{"word":"in einer Liste notieren","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberliegen","l":1},{"word":"in einer Liste auff\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"kr\xe4ngen","l":1}]},{"id":284,"question":"look","answers":[{"word":"suchen"},{"word":"schauen"},{"word":"blicken"},{"word":"nachschlagen","l":1},{"word":"gucken","l":1},{"word":"hinsehen","l":1},{"word":"nachschauen","l":1},{"word":"ausschauen","l":1},{"word":"hinschauen","l":1},{"word":"anblicken","l":1},{"word":"hinblicken","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk ausnehmen","l":1},{"word":"kieken","l":1},{"word":"\xe4ugen","l":1},{"word":"nachsuchen","l":1},{"word":"Look","gender":"m"},{"word":"Optik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Betrachtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erscheinungsbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ausstrahlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Design","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anblick","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Miene","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Augenaufschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":285,"question":"loss","answers":[{"word":"Verlust","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abhandenkommen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Niederlage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Minus","gender":"n"},{"word":"D\xe4mpfung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Untergang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wegfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xfcckgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Minderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einbu\xdfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kursverlust","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schwund","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":286,"question":"love","answers":[{"word":"Liebe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schatz","gender":"m"},{"word":"herzliche Gr\xfc\xdfe"},{"word":"Minne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Liebling","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"lieben"}]},{"id":287,"question":"machine","answers":[{"word":"Maschine","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ger\xe4t","gender":"n"},{"word":"Anlage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Automat","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Apparat","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Arbeitsmaschine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kraftmaschine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"maschinell"},{"word":"bearbeiten"},{"word":"zerspanen","l":1},{"word":"maschinell herstellen","l":1},{"word":"spanen","l":1},{"word":"maschinell bearbeiten","l":1},{"word":"mit Maschinen bearbeiten","l":1},{"word":"abspanen","l":1}]},{"id":288,"question":"man","answers":[{"word":"Mann","gender":"m"}]},{"id":289,"question":"manager","answers":[{"word":"Manager","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsf\xfchrer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Leiter","gender":"m"},{"word":"Managerin","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abteilungsleiter","gender":"m"},{"word":"Chef","gender":"m"},{"word":"Direktor","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"F\xfchrungskraft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsf\xfchrerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verwalter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leiterin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Betriebsleiter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsleiter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Chefin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unternehmensleiter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Direktorin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Trainer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"leitender Angestellter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorsteher","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":290,"question":"mark","answers":[{"word":"Marke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeichen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Note","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ziel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Markierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kennzeichnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kennzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Spur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Merkmal","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Benoten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Fleck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Punkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abdruck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Benotung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kratzer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Narbe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zensur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schulnote","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Merkzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zielscheibe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schramme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"markieren"},{"word":"kennzeichnen"},{"word":"kenntlich machen"},{"word":"benoten"},{"word":"beschriften"},{"word":"zeichnen","l":1},{"word":"anzeichnen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) auszeichnen","l":1},{"word":"beachten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk benoten","l":1},{"word":"bezeichnen","l":1},{"word":"abstecken","l":1},{"word":"bewerten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk anrei\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"einzeichnen","l":1},{"word":"hervorheben","l":1},{"word":"anstreichen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) zensieren","l":1},{"word":"zinken","l":1},{"word":"korrigieren","l":1},{"word":"m\xe4rken","l":1},{"word":"herausheben","l":1},{"word":"schmutzig machen","l":1},{"word":"beschildern","l":1},{"word":"zerkratzen","l":1},{"word":"charakterisieren","l":1},{"word":"besch\xe4digen","l":1},{"word":"eichen","l":1}]},{"id":291,"question":"market","answers":[{"word":"Markt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Vertrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"B\xf6rse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Absatzmarkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bedarf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Absatzgebiet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wirtschaftsraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Interessentenkreis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk vermarkten"},{"word":"verkaufen","l":1},{"word":"vertreiben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk in Verkehr bringen","l":1}]},{"id":292,"question":"mass","answers":[{"word":"Masse","gender":"f"},{"word":"Messe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Menge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xfclle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Haufen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unmenge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"sichAkk konzentrieren","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk zusammenballen","l":1},{"word":"zusammenziehen","l":1}]},{"id":293,"question":"meal","answers":[{"word":"Mahlzeit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Essen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gericht","gender":"n"},{"word":"Mehl","gender":"n"},{"word":"Mahl","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Speise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schrotmehl","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":294,"question":"measure","answers":[{"word":"Ma\xdf","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ma\xdfnahme","gender":"f"},{"word":"Takt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ma\xdfstab","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Messger\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Mittel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ausma\xdf","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Rhythmus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ma\xdfeinheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Metrum","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ma\xdfregel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorkehrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Versma\xdf","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Satzbreite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mensur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"messen"},{"word":"vermessen","l":1},{"word":"ausmessen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erfassen","l":1},{"word":"bemessen","l":1},{"word":"abmessen","l":1},{"word":"nachmessen","l":1},{"word":"gewichten","l":1}]},{"id":295,"question":"meat","answers":[{"word":"Fleisch","gender":"n"},{"word":"Substanz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fleischeinlage","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":296,"question":"meeting","answers":[{"word":"Treffen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Meeting","gender":"n"},{"word":"Sitzung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Versammlung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Veranstaltung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Besprechung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zusammentreffen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Zusammenkunft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Konferenz","gender":"f"},{"word":"Begegnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tagung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Treff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zusammentritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wiedersehen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zusammenfluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"begegnend","l":1},{"word":"begleichend","l":1},{"word":"erf\xfcllen"},{"word":"decken"},{"word":"treffen"},{"word":"etw.Dat entsprechen"},{"word":"(etw.Dat) begegnen"},{"word":"einhalten"},{"word":"tagen"},{"word":"zusammenkommen"},{"word":"etw.Akk befriedigen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk begegnen","l":1},{"word":"gen\xfcgen","l":1},{"word":"entgegenkommen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. empfangen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bew\xe4ltigen","l":1},{"word":"abholen","l":1},{"word":"zusammentreffen","l":1},{"word":"aufeinandertreffen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk versammeln","l":1},{"word":"antreffen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk vereinigen","l":1},{"word":"zusammentreten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk begleichen","l":1}]},{"id":297,"question":"memory","answers":[{"word":"Erinnerung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Speicher","gender":"m"},{"word":"Andenken","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ged\xe4chtnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Speicherplatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Arbeitsspeicher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gedenken","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Datenspeicher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Erinnerungsverm\xf6gen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kopf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Reminiszenz","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":298,"question":"metal","answers":[{"word":"Metall","gender":"n"},{"word":"Blech","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schotter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"metallisch"},{"word":"blechern"},{"word":"metallen","l":1}]},{"id":299,"question":"middle","answers":[{"word":"Mitte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Mittelpunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"mittlerer Teil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Taille","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"mittlere"},{"word":"mittlerer","l":1},{"word":"mittleres","l":1}]},{"id":300,"question":"milk","answers":[{"word":"Milch","gender":"f"},{"word":"melken"},{"word":"Milch geben","l":1}]},{"id":301,"question":"mind","answers":[{"word":"Geist","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verstand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kopf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sinn","gender":"m"},{"word":"Meinung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Psyche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gedanken","l":1},{"word":"Ged\xe4chtnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gem\xfct","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ansicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gedanke","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Absicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Denkweise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Phantasie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wille","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fantasie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Neigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"beachten"},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk h\xfcten"},{"word":"aufpassen"},{"word":"bedenken","l":1},{"word":"achten","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk k\xfcmmern","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk kehren","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk h\xfcten","l":1},{"word":"beaufsichtigen","l":1}]},{"id":302,"question":"mine","answers":[{"word":"meiner"},{"word":"mein","l":1},{"word":"Mine","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bergwerk","gender":"n"},{"word":"Grube","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grubenbetrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Steinbruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abbaubetrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bergwerksanlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grubenanlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abbauanlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"sch\xfcrfen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) abbauen"},{"word":"f\xf6rdern"},{"word":"Minen verlegen","l":1},{"word":"graben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bergm\xe4nnisch gewinnen","l":1},{"word":"Minen legen","l":1}]},{"id":303,"question":"minute","answers":[{"word":"Minute","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sitzungsprotokoll","gender":"n"},{"word":"Niederschrift","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Augenblick","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spielminute","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Konzept","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"kurzer Entwurf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Memorandum","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"winzig"},{"word":"minuzi\xf6s","l":1},{"word":"sehr klein","l":1},{"word":"minuti\xf6s","l":1},{"word":"peinlich genau","l":1},{"word":"protokollieren"},{"word":"notieren","l":1}]},{"id":304,"question":"mist","answers":[{"word":"Nebel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Dunst","gender":"m"},{"word":"Dunstschleier","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Beschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schleier","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spr\xfchregen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"feuchter Dunst","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"beschlagen"}]},{"id":305,"question":"money","answers":[{"word":"Geld","gender":"n"}]},{"id":306,"question":"month","answers":[{"word":"Monat","gender":"m"},{"word":"Mond","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"monatlich"}]},{"id":307,"question":"morning","answers":[{"word":"Morgen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Vormittag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Fr\xfche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"morgendlich"},{"word":"vormitt\xe4glich","l":1}]},{"id":308,"question":"mother","answers":[{"word":"Mutter","gender":"f"},{"word":"Muttertier","gender":"n"}]},{"id":309,"question":"motion","answers":[{"word":"Bewegung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Motion","gender":"f"},{"word":"Antrag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Lauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Thema","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Stuhlgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"ein Zeichen geben"},{"word":"jdm. winken","l":1}]},{"id":310,"question":"mountain","answers":[{"word":"Berg","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gebirge","gender":"n"}]},{"id":311,"question":"move","answers":[{"word":"bewegen"},{"word":"verschieben"},{"word":"ziehen"},{"word":"etw.Akk versetzen"},{"word":"r\xfccken"},{"word":"\xfcbertragen"},{"word":"transportieren","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk entfernen","l":1},{"word":"\xfcbersiedeln","l":1},{"word":"ausziehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk absetzen","l":1},{"word":"verstellen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk r\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk regen","l":1},{"word":"antreiben","l":1},{"word":"umlegen","l":1},{"word":"abwandern","l":1},{"word":"verziehen","l":1},{"word":"erweichen","l":1},{"word":"aufw\xfchlen","l":1},{"word":"an einen anderen Ort bringen","l":1},{"word":"milde stimmen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk umr\xe4umen","l":1},{"word":"erregen","l":1},{"word":"Umzug","gender":"m"},{"word":"Spielzug","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bewegung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schachzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verlegung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xdcbersiedlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auszug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xdcbergang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xdcbersiedelung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zuzug","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":312,"question":"music","answers":[{"word":"Musik","gender":"f"},{"word":"Musikalien","l":1},{"word":"Mucke","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":313,"question":"name","answers":[{"word":"Name","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bezeichnung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Benennung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Titulierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"nennen"},{"word":"etw.Akk bezeichnen"},{"word":"etw.Akk mit einem Namen versehen","l":1}]},{"id":314,"question":"nation","answers":[{"word":"Nation","gender":"f"},{"word":"Staat","gender":"m"},{"word":"Land","gender":"n"},{"word":"Volk","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":315,"question":"need","answers":[{"word":"Bedarf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Notwendigkeit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bed\xfcrfnis","gender":"n"},{"word":"Not","gender":"f"},{"word":"Nachfrage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erfordernis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bed\xfcrftigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Notlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Armut","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"m\xfcssen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) ben\xf6tigen"},{"word":"brauchen"},{"word":"bed\xfcrfen"},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk n\xf6tig haben","l":1}]},{"id":316,"question":"news","answers":[{"word":"Nachricht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Nachrichten"},{"word":"Neuigkeiten"},{"word":"Neuigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Meldungen","l":1},{"word":"Tagesschau","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":317,"question":"night","answers":[{"word":"Nacht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abend","gender":"m"}]},{"id":318,"question":"noise","answers":[{"word":"L\xe4rm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Rauschen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ger\xe4usch","gender":"n"},{"word":"Krach","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Laut","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"St\xf6rger\xe4usch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Radau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Get\xf6se","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"St\xf6rung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Nebenger\xe4usch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tamtam","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":319,"question":"note","answers":[{"word":"Hinweis","gender":"m"},{"word":"Anmerkung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Note","gender":"f"},{"word":"Notiz","gender":"f"},{"word":"Mitteilung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zettel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Geldschein","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ton","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vermerk","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bemerkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"kurze Mitteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Nachricht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erl\xe4uterung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Brief","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schuldschein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kommentar","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Textziffer","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Billett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufzeichnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aktennotiz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anhangangabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aktenvermerk","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Memorandum","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Briefchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"schriftliche Mitteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"beachten"},{"word":"notieren"},{"word":"vermerken","l":1},{"word":"bemerken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk merken","l":1},{"word":"ber\xfccksichtigen","l":1},{"word":"feststellen","l":1},{"word":"beobachten","l":1},{"word":"anmerken","l":1}]},{"id":320,"question":"number","answers":[{"word":"Anzahl","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zahl","gender":"f"},{"word":"Nummer","gender":"f"},{"word":"Reihe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausgabe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kennzahl","gender":"f"},{"word":"Startnummer","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ziffer","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Numerus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"z\xe4hlen"},{"word":"nummerieren"},{"word":"etw.Akk beziffern","l":1},{"word":"benummern","l":1}]},{"id":321,"question":"observation","answers":[{"word":"Beobachtung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Einhaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beobachten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Feststellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xdcberwachung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beachtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ber\xfccksichtigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erfassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xdcberlegung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Betrachtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Observation","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bemerkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erlebnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"\xc4u\xdferung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"beobachten"},{"word":"beachten"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) einhalten"},{"word":"etw.Akk ber\xfccksichtigen"},{"word":"feststellen"},{"word":"befolgen"},{"word":"wahrnehmen","l":1},{"word":"betrachten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verfolgen","l":1},{"word":"bemerken","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberwachen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk respektieren","l":1},{"word":"jdm./etw.Dat zusehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk wahren","l":1},{"word":"auf etw.Akk achten","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk ansehen","l":1},{"word":"observieren","l":1}]},{"id":322,"question":"offer","answers":[{"word":"Angebot","gender":"n"},{"word":"Offerte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anbot","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vorschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Antrag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gebot","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Offert","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anerbieten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Briefkurs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verkaufsgebot","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) anbieten"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) bieten"},{"word":"darbringen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) offerieren","l":1},{"word":"zeigen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk erbieten","l":1},{"word":"aussetzen","l":1},{"word":"ausbieten","l":1}]},{"id":323,"question":"oil","answers":[{"word":"Erd\xf6l","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"\xd6lgem\xe4lde","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Mineral\xf6l","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"\xd6lbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"\xf6len"},{"word":"schmieren","l":1},{"word":"einfetten","l":1}]},{"id":324,"question":"operation","answers":[{"word":"Betrieb","gender":"m"},{"word":"Betreiben","gender":"n"},{"word":"Unternehmen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Vorgang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bedienung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Operation","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verfahren","gender":"n"},{"word":"Eingriff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einsatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Funktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"T\xe4tigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsbereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Arbeitsgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Arbeitsweise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Funktionieren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Handhabung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Betreibung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ablauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bet\xe4tigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahrweise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Laufen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Betriebsablauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Arbeitsablauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verkn\xfcpfung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Transaktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Handlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Maschinenbedienung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Arbeitsvorgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unternehmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kampfhandlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Arbeitsverrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":325,"question":"opinion","answers":[{"word":"Meinung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stellungnahme","gender":"f"},{"word":"Auffassung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ansicht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gutachten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Urteil","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erachten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anschauung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Befinden","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Urteilsbegr\xfcndung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erachtung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":326,"question":"order","answers":[{"word":"Bestellung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Auftrag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Reihenfolge","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anordnung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anweisung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Order","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auftragserteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verf\xfcgung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Orden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Befehl","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Folge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gr\xf6\xdfenordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gebot","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Grad","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kommando","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Rangstufe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Glaubensorden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stufenreihe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"S\xe4ulenordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk bestellen"},{"word":"verf\xfcgen"},{"word":"gliedern"},{"word":"anordnen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ordern","l":1},{"word":"befehlen","l":1},{"word":"in Auftrag geben","l":1},{"word":"anweisen","l":1},{"word":"verordnen","l":1},{"word":"kommandieren","l":1}]},{"id":327,"question":"organization","answers":[{"word":"Organisation","gender":"f"},{"word":"Unternehmen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Einrichtung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gliederung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gestaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Veranstaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Organisierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vereinigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verband","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) organisieren"},{"word":"veranstalten"},{"word":"ausrichten"},{"word":"gestalten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk koordinieren","l":1},{"word":"einteilen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk einrichten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk gliedern","l":1},{"word":"mitgestalten","l":1},{"word":"anordnen","l":1},{"word":"aufziehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ausgestalten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verwalten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk strukturieren","l":1}]},{"id":328,"question":"ornament","answers":[{"word":"Ornament","gender":"n"},{"word":"Verzierung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schmuck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dekor","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zierde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zier","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"verzieren","l":1},{"word":"ausschm\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"dekorieren","l":1},{"word":"schm\xfccken","l":1}]},{"id":329,"question":"owner","answers":[{"word":"Eigent\xfcmer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Inhaber","gender":"m"},{"word":"Besitzer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Inhaberin","gender":"f"},{"word":"Eigent\xfcmerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Eigner","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Halter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bauherr","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Eignerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Halterin","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":330,"question":"page","answers":[{"word":"Seite","gender":"f"},{"word":"Blatt","gender":"n"},{"word":"Page","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Buchseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Knappe","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Speicherseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hoteljunge","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"jdn. ausrufen"},{"word":"etw.Akk paginieren","l":1},{"word":"anpiepsen","l":1},{"word":"anpiepen","l":1}]},{"id":331,"question":"pain","answers":[{"word":"Schmerz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kummer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Leid","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Leiden","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Qual","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"M\xfche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dolor","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"schmerzen"},{"word":"jdm. weh tun"}]},{"id":332,"question":"paint","answers":[{"word":"Farbe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Lack","gender":"m"},{"word":"Lackierung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anstrich","gender":"m"},{"word":"Farbanstrich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anstrichfarbe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"malen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) bemalen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) streichen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) anstreichen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) lackieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bepinseln","l":1},{"word":"ausmalen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) pinseln","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) anmalen","l":1},{"word":"schmerzen"},{"word":"jdm. weh tun","l":1}]},{"id":333,"question":"paper","answers":[{"word":"Papier","gender":"n"},{"word":"Arbeit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeitung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abhandlung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Blatt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dokument","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Referat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tapete","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Akte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schrift","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schriftst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Handelspapier","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Klausur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Klausurarbeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"papieren","l":1},{"word":"broschiert","l":1},{"word":"tapezieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk in Papier einwickeln","l":1}]},{"id":334,"question":"part","answers":[{"word":"Teil","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bestandteil","gender":"m"},{"word":"Rolle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bauteil","gender":"n"},{"word":"St\xfcck","gender":"n"},{"word":"Folge","gender":"f"},{"word":"Einzelteil","gender":"n"},{"word":"Part","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anteil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Werkst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Teilst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Teilbetrag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Teilaspekt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bauelement","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Glied","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"sichAkk teilen","l":1},{"word":"weggehen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk l\xf6sen","l":1},{"word":"scheiden","l":1},{"word":"scheiteln","l":1}]},{"id":335,"question":"paste","answers":[{"word":"Paste","gender":"f"},{"word":"Teig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kleister","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Strass","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Brei","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leim","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kuchenteig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Similistein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Papp","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klebstoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk einf\xfcgen"},{"word":"einf\xfcgen"},{"word":"kleben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk kleistern","l":1},{"word":"einkleistern","l":1},{"word":"leimen","l":1},{"word":"ankleben","l":1}]},{"id":336,"question":"payment","answers":[{"word":"Zahlung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bezahlung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verg\xfctung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Leistung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bezahlen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Auszahlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Begleichung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einzahlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entgelt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Einl\xf6sung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verg\xfctungen","l":1},{"word":"Entlohnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abf\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geldleistung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Honorierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lohn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abzahlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abfindungssumme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anweisung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":337,"question":"peace","answers":[{"word":"Frieden","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ruhe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Friede","gender":"m"}]},{"id":338,"question":"person","answers":[{"word":"Person","gender":"f"},{"word":"Mensch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Wesen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Individuum","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":339,"question":"place","answers":[{"word":"Ort","gender":"m"},{"word":"Platz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Statt","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Position","gender":"f"},{"word":"Standort","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ortschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"St\xe4tte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Platzierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fleck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xd6rtlichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Winkel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"legen"},{"word":"aufgeben"},{"word":"platzieren","l":1},{"word":"t\xe4tigen","l":1},{"word":"unterbringen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk anbringen","l":1}]},{"id":340,"question":"plant","answers":[{"word":"Anlage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Pflanze","gender":"f"},{"word":"Werk","gender":"n"},{"word":"Betrieb","gender":"m"},{"word":"Fabrik","gender":"f"},{"word":"Maschinenpark","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fertigungsanlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Betriebsgeb\xe4ude","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gew\xe4chs","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Werksanlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Baumaschinen","l":1},{"word":"Betriebsanlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fabrikanlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Apparatur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spitzel","gender":"m"},{"word":"pflanzen"},{"word":"etw.Akk anpflanzen"},{"word":"stecken","l":1},{"word":"setzen","l":1},{"word":"errichten","l":1},{"word":"gr\xfcnden","l":1},{"word":"legen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk einpflanzen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk anbauen","l":1},{"word":"bepflanzen","l":1},{"word":"auslegen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk schmuggeln","l":1},{"word":"schleusen","l":1},{"word":"einschleusen","l":1}]},{"id":341,"question":"play","answers":[{"word":"abspielen"},{"word":"mitspielen","l":1},{"word":"ausspielen","l":1},{"word":"musizieren","l":1},{"word":"aufspielen","l":1},{"word":"nachspielen","l":1},{"word":"blasen","l":1},{"word":"mimen","l":1},{"word":"Spiel","gender":"n"},{"word":"St\xfcck","gender":"n"},{"word":"Theaterst\xfcck","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schauspiel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Drama","gender":"n"},{"word":"Spielweise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Play","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Spielraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"B\xfchnenst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Spielzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lagerspiel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Theaterschauspiel","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":342,"question":"pleasure","answers":[{"word":"Freude","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vergn\xfcgen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Genuss","gender":"m"},{"word":"Lust","gender":"f"},{"word":"Spa\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gefallen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wohlgefallen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wohlbehagen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vergn\xfcgung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wonne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lustgewinn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gaudi","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reiz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Behagen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Pl\xe4sier","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":343,"question":"point","answers":[{"word":"Punkt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Spitze","gender":"f"},{"word":"Moment","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sinn","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zeitpunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Platz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ende","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aspekt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zipfel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tatsache","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Standpunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Steckdose","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zweck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"der springende Punkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pointe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Z\xe4hler","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Landspitze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zacke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Strich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"zeigen"},{"word":"deuten"},{"word":"hinweisen","l":1},{"word":"hindeuten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk richten","l":1},{"word":"spitzen","l":1},{"word":"sich zuspitzen","l":1},{"word":"anspitzen","l":1},{"word":"ausfugen","l":1}]},{"id":344,"question":"poison","answers":[{"word":"Gift","gender":"n"},{"word":"Giftstoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Toxin","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"vergiften"},{"word":"verpesten"},{"word":"etw.Akk verderben","l":1}]},{"id":345,"question":"polish","answers":[{"word":"Polnisch","gender":"n"},{"word":"polnisch"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) polieren"},{"word":"putzen"},{"word":"gl\xe4tten"},{"word":"verfeinern","l":1},{"word":"blank reiben","l":1},{"word":"vervollkommnen","l":1},{"word":"ausfeilen","l":1},{"word":"wichsen","l":1},{"word":"wienern","l":1},{"word":"abschleifen","l":1},{"word":"Politur","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hochglanz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schliff","gender":"m"},{"word":"Poliermittel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verfeinerung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Eleganz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Putzmittel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vervollkommnung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":346,"question":"porter","answers":[{"word":"Porter","gender":"n"},{"word":"Portier","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gep\xe4cktr\xe4ger","gender":"m"},{"word":"Pf\xf6rtner","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tr\xe4ger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Koffertr\xe4ger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lastentr\xe4ger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dienstmann","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schlafwagenschaffner","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gep\xe4cktr\xe4gerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Portiersfrau","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pedell","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pf\xf6rtnerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lasttr\xe4ger","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":347,"question":"position","answers":[{"word":"Lage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Position","gender":"f"},{"word":"Posten","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Arbeitsplatz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Standpunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Situation","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rolle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Platz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Standort","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Funktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Platzierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Haltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ort","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Amt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Arbeitsstelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufenthaltsort","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schachstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"platzieren"},{"word":"aufstellen"},{"word":"positionieren"},{"word":"etw.Akk anordnen","l":1},{"word":"ansetzen","l":1},{"word":"in Stellung bringen","l":1},{"word":"stationieren","l":1},{"word":"postieren","l":1}]},{"id":348,"question":"powder","answers":[{"word":"Pulver","gender":"n"},{"word":"Pulverschnee","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Staub","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"P\xfclverchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"bestreuen"},{"word":"best\xe4uben","l":1},{"word":"pulverisieren","l":1},{"word":"zermahlen","l":1},{"word":"zu Staub zerfallen","l":1},{"word":"einpudern","l":1},{"word":"zerfallen","l":1}]},{"id":349,"question":"power","answers":[{"word":"Power","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kraft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Macht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Leistung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Strom","gender":"m"},{"word":"Energie","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gewalt","gender":"f"},{"word":"Befugnis","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vollmacht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xe4rke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leistungsf\xe4higkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wucht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Potenz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Elektrizit\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verm\xf6gen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Berechtigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"M\xe4chtigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Herrschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Machtf\xfclle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Antriebskraft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Netzstrom","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"antreiben"},{"word":"mit Energie versorgen"}]},{"id":350,"question":"price","answers":[{"word":"Preis","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kurs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"bewerten"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) auszeichnen"},{"word":"etw.Akk bepreisen","l":1},{"word":"auspreisen","l":1},{"word":"einen Preis festsetzen","l":1},{"word":"den Preis von etw.Dat festsetzen","l":1},{"word":"mit einem Preis versehen","l":1}]},{"id":351,"question":"print","answers":[{"word":"Drucken","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ausdruck","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abdruck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Druckschrift","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kopie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Blatt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Eindruck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ablichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fotoabzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Druckmuster","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"drucken"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) ausdrucken"},{"word":"abdrucken","l":1},{"word":"kopieren","l":1},{"word":"abziehen","l":1}]},{"id":352,"question":"process","answers":[{"word":"Prozess","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verfahren","gender":"n"},{"word":"Vorgang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ablauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verlauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Arbeitsgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Arbeitsvorgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Arbeitsverfahren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Fortsatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"verarbeiten"},{"word":"bearbeiten"},{"word":"abwickeln"},{"word":"entwickeln","l":1},{"word":"aufbereiten","l":1},{"word":"weiterverarbeiten","l":1},{"word":"abarbeiten","l":1},{"word":"veredeln","l":1},{"word":"prozessieren","l":1},{"word":"aufarbeiten","l":1}]},{"id":353,"question":"produce","answers":[{"word":"produzieren"},{"word":"erzeugen"},{"word":"fertigen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) herstellen"},{"word":"etw.Akk ergeben"},{"word":"anfertigen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) verursachen"},{"word":"f\xf6rdern"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) vorlegen"},{"word":"etw.Akk bewirken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erzielen","l":1},{"word":"vorweisen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk generieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk hervorbringen","l":1},{"word":"fabrizieren","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) erbringen","l":1},{"word":"hervorrufen","l":1},{"word":"vorzeigen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erwirtschaften","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ausl\xf6sen","l":1},{"word":"herausbringen","l":1},{"word":"inszenieren","l":1},{"word":"beibringen","l":1},{"word":"drehen","l":1},{"word":"vorbringen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) hervorholen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zustande bringen","l":1},{"word":"vorf\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"Produkte"},{"word":"Produkt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Erzeugnisse","l":1},{"word":"Erzeugnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Warenmarkt","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":354,"question":"profit","answers":[{"word":"Gewinn","gender":"m"},{"word":"Profit","gender":"m"},{"word":"Nutzen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ertrag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorteil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verdienst","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xdcberschuss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Mehrerl\xf6s","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausbeute","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Plus","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Nutzen bringen"},{"word":"Nutzen ziehen"}]},{"id":355,"question":"property","answers":[{"word":"Eigentum","gender":"n"},{"word":"Immobilie","gender":"f"},{"word":"Besitz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Grund","gender":"m"},{"word":"Merkmal","gender":"n"},{"word":"Eigenschaft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Grundst\xfcck","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gut","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sachanlagen","l":1},{"word":"Liegenschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verm\xf6gen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Grundbesitz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Objekt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anwesen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Grundeigentum","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Habe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Besitztum","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":356,"question":"prose","answers":[{"word":"Prosa","gender":"f"}]},{"id":357,"question":"protest","answers":[{"word":"Protest","gender":"m"},{"word":"Einspruch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Demonstration","gender":"f"},{"word":"Protestaktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Widerspruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Widerstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Reklamation","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"protestieren"},{"word":"demonstrieren","l":1},{"word":"aufbegehren","l":1},{"word":"beteuern","l":1},{"word":"reklamieren","l":1},{"word":"rumoren","l":1},{"word":"gegen etw.Akk Verwahrung einlegen","l":1},{"word":"Einspruch erheben","l":1},{"word":"Widerspruch erheben","l":1}]},{"id":358,"question":"pull","answers":[{"word":"ziehen"},{"word":"zerren"},{"word":"anziehen"},{"word":"rudern","l":1},{"word":"anbaggern","l":1},{"word":"zupfen","l":1},{"word":"baggern","l":1},{"word":"schleifen","l":1},{"word":"raufen","l":1},{"word":"rei\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"Anziehungskraft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schluck","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einfluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sog","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zugkraft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anstrengung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sogwirkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anziehung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schr\xe4gziehen","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":359,"question":"punishment","answers":[{"word":"Strafe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bestrafung","gender":"f"},{"word":"bestrafen"},{"word":"etw.Akk ahnden"},{"word":"strafen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. abstrafen","l":1}]},{"id":360,"question":"purpose","answers":[{"word":"Zweck","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ziel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Aufgabe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sinn","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bestimmung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorsatz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Absicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verwendungszweck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einsatzzweck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zielsetzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zweckbestimmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wille","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Intention","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"bezwecken","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) beabsichtigen","l":1}]},{"id":361,"question":"push","answers":[{"word":"dr\xfccken"},{"word":"schieben"},{"word":"dr\xe4ngen"},{"word":"anschieben"},{"word":"schubsen"},{"word":"treiben","l":1},{"word":"(jdn./etw.Akk) vorantreiben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verschieben","l":1},{"word":"forcieren","l":1},{"word":"dr\xe4ngeln","l":1},{"word":"pressen","l":1},{"word":"puschen","l":1},{"word":"antreiben","l":1},{"word":"sto\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"rempeln","l":1},{"word":"propagieren","l":1},{"word":"Schubs","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schub","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ansto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorsto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unternehmungsgeist","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tatkraft","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":362,"question":"quality","answers":[{"word":"Qualit\xe4t","gender":"f"},{"word":"Beschaffenheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Eigenschaft","gender":"f"},{"word":"G\xfcte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausf\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Natur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"G\xfcteklasse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"G\xfctegrad","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":363,"question":"question","answers":[{"word":"Frage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zweifel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Fragestellung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anfrage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufgabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zwischenfrage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(jdn./etw.Akk) fragen"},{"word":"hinterfragen"},{"word":"befragen"},{"word":"etw.Akk bezweifeln"},{"word":"etw.Akk anzweifeln"},{"word":"verh\xf6ren"},{"word":"etw.Akk in Frage stellen","l":1},{"word":"ausfragen","l":1},{"word":"vernehmen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk in Zweifel ziehen","l":1}]},{"id":364,"question":"rain","answers":[{"word":"Regen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Regenfall","gender":"m"},{"word":"Niederschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Regenwetter","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"regnen"}]},{"id":365,"question":"range","answers":[{"word":"Bereich","gender":"m"},{"word":"Angebot","gender":"n"},{"word":"Reihe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sortiment","gender":"n"},{"word":"Spektrum","gender":"n"},{"word":"Vielfalt","gender":"f"},{"word":"Palette","gender":"f"},{"word":"Reichweite","gender":"f"},{"word":"Herd","gender":"m"},{"word":"Auswahl","gender":"f"},{"word":"Programm","gender":"n"},{"word":"Produktpalette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Umfang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aktionsradius","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verbreitungsgebiet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Spielraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bandbreite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Serie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Strecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Angebotspalette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Baureihe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kollektion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Skala","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xfclle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spanne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entfernung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gebirgskette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wertebereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tonumfang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spannweite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Raum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tragweite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gr\xf6\xdfenordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kochherd","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"K\xfcchenherd","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausbreitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Intervall","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Stimmumfang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bildbereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schussentfernung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schussweite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schwankungsbereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Operationsradius","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schussbereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Entfernung zum Ziel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wertemenge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weideland","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kursbereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"durchstreifen"},{"word":"schwanken","l":1},{"word":"aufstellen","l":1},{"word":"durchziehen","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk klassifizieren","l":1},{"word":"anordnen","l":1},{"word":"umherstreifen","l":1}]},{"id":366,"question":"rate","answers":[{"word":"Rate","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wechselkurs","gender":"m"},{"word":"Quote","gender":"f"},{"word":"Geb\xfchr","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zinssatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tarif","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kurs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verh\xe4ltnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Satz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anteil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zahl","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Devisenkurs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tempo","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Frequenz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grad","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Steuersatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kostensatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geb\xfchrensatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zins","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einzeltarif","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kommunalsteuer","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.) bewerten"},{"word":"sch\xe4tzen","l":1},{"word":"einsch\xe4tzen","l":1},{"word":"einstufen","l":1},{"word":"gewichten","l":1},{"word":"absch\xe4tzen","l":1}]},{"id":367,"question":"ray","answers":[{"word":"Strahl","gender":"m"},{"word":"Lichtstrahl","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rochen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schimmer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk durchleuchten"},{"word":"bestrahlen","l":1},{"word":"ausstrahlen","l":1}]},{"id":368,"question":"reaction","answers":[{"word":"Reaktion","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stellungnahme","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verhalten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Antwort","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"R\xfcckwirkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Echo","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Photoreaktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gegenwirkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ansprechen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Erwiderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gegenschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xfcckkopplung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":369,"question":"reading","answers":[{"word":"Lesen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Lekt\xfcre","gender":"f"},{"word":"Lesung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Messwert","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ablesen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ablesung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lesestoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Messung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anzeige","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lesart","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leseprobe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ableseergebnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dichterlesung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"abgelesener Messwert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Belesenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorlesung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"lesend","l":1},{"word":"nachlesend","l":1},{"word":"lesen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) ablesen"},{"word":"vorlesen"},{"word":"deuten"},{"word":"auslesen","l":1},{"word":"nachlesen","l":1},{"word":"studieren","l":1},{"word":"schm\xf6kern","l":1},{"word":"er\xf6ffnen","l":1},{"word":"gelesen"},{"word":"eingelesen","l":1},{"word":"abgelesen","l":1},{"word":"vorgelesen","l":1},{"word":"nachgelesen","l":1},{"word":"jdm. vorlesen"}]},{"id":370,"question":"reason","answers":[{"word":"Grund","gender":"m"},{"word":"Vernunft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anlass","gender":"m"},{"word":"Argument","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ratio","gender":"f"},{"word":"Motiv","gender":"n"},{"word":"Begr\xfcndung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ursache","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Veranlassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beweggrund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hinderungsgrund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"gesunder Verstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"folgern"},{"word":"argumentieren"},{"word":"schlie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk begr\xfcnden","l":1},{"word":"schlussfolgern","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberlegen","l":1},{"word":"er\xf6rtern","l":1},{"word":"vern\xfcnftig urteilen","l":1},{"word":"durchdenken","l":1},{"word":"vern\xfcnftig reden","l":1}]},{"id":371,"question":"record","answers":[{"word":"Rekord","gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufzeichnung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Datensatz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Platte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Eintrag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schallplatte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Akte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufnahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Protokoll","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Erfassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Satz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Urkunde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Niederschrift","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dokument","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Rekordmarke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bestmarke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Eintragung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bestleistung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorgeschichte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beleg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verzeichnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Unterlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mitschrift","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gerichtsakte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"H\xf6chstleistung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"erfassen"},{"word":"aufnehmen"},{"word":"aufzeichnen"},{"word":"etw.Akk notieren"},{"word":"speichern"},{"word":"verzeichnen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) festhalten"},{"word":"dokumentieren"},{"word":"eintragen"},{"word":"protokollieren"},{"word":"registrieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk schreiben","l":1},{"word":"mitschneiden","l":1},{"word":"niederschreiben","l":1},{"word":"fixieren","l":1},{"word":"Tonbandaufnahmen machen","l":1},{"word":"schriftlich niederlegen","l":1}]},{"id":372,"question":"regret","answers":[{"word":"(etw.Akk) bedauern"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) bereuen","l":1},{"word":"nachtrauern","l":1},{"word":"reuen","l":1},{"word":"Bedauern","gender":"n"},{"word":"Reue","gender":"f"}]},{"id":373,"question":"relation","answers":[{"word":"Zusammenhang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verh\xe4ltnis","gender":"n"},{"word":"Beziehung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Relation","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kontakt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verbindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verwandte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verwandtschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verwandter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Erz\xe4hlung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":374,"question":"religion","answers":[{"word":"Religion","gender":"f"},{"word":"Glaube","gender":"m"},{"word":"Religionszugeh\xf6rigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Religionsbekenntnis","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":375,"question":"representative","answers":[{"word":"Vertreter","gender":"m"},{"word":"Repr\xe4sentant","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stellvertreter","gender":"m"},{"word":"Vertretung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vertreterin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beauftragter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abgeordneter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bevollm\xe4chtigter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Repr\xe4sentantin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vertrauensperson","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Obmann","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vertrauensmann","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bevollm\xe4chtigte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abgeordnete","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stellvertreterin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Obm\xe4nnin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Obfrau","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftstr\xe4ger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"repr\xe4sentativ"},{"word":"typisch","l":1},{"word":"stellvertretend","l":1},{"word":"bezeichnend","l":1},{"word":"charakteristisch","l":1},{"word":"kennzeichnend","l":1}]},{"id":376,"question":"request","answers":[{"word":"Anfrage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wunsch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Antrag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bitte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anliegen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Anforderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufforderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Nachfrage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ersuchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gesuch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ansuchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Abfrage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Forderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abruf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ansinnen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) verlangen"},{"word":"bitten"},{"word":"etw.Akk beantragen"},{"word":"anfordern"},{"word":"erbitten"},{"word":"ersuchen","l":1},{"word":"anfragen","l":1},{"word":"fordern","l":1},{"word":"abfragen","l":1},{"word":"fragen","l":1},{"word":"auffordern","l":1},{"word":"abrufen","l":1},{"word":"begehren","l":1},{"word":"herbeiholen","l":1},{"word":"abfordern","l":1},{"word":"um etw.Akk nachsuchen","l":1}]},{"id":377,"question":"respect","answers":[{"word":"Respekt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Achtung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hinsicht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Beziehung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anerkennung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hochachtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Respektierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ansehen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"respektieren"},{"word":"beachten"},{"word":"achten"},{"word":"ber\xfccksichtigen"},{"word":"ansehen","l":1},{"word":"anerkennen","l":1}]},{"id":378,"question":"rest","answers":[{"word":"Rest","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ruhe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Erholung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Pause","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausruhen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Rast","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ruhepause","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"ein \xdcbriges","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Auflage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schonung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lehne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verschnaufpause","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xfctze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterbrechung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auszeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Restbestand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pausenzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gabel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"ruhen"},{"word":"ausruhen"},{"word":"rasten","l":1},{"word":"liegen","l":1},{"word":"beruhen","l":1},{"word":"lagern","l":1},{"word":"Pause machen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk st\xfctzen","l":1},{"word":"basieren","l":1},{"word":"eine Pause einlegen","l":1},{"word":"aufst\xfctzen","l":1}]},{"id":379,"question":"reward","answers":[{"word":"Lohn","gender":"m"},{"word":"Belohnung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verg\xfctung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anerkennung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gegenleistung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Honorierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pr\xe4mie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entlohnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entgelt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"belohnen"},{"word":"honorieren"},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk entlohnen"},{"word":"vergelten","l":1}]},{"id":380,"question":"rhythm","answers":[{"word":"Rhythmus","gender":"m"},{"word":"Rhythmik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Takt","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":382,"question":"river","answers":[{"word":"Strom","gender":"m"}]},{"id":383,"question":"road","answers":[{"word":"Stra\xdfe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Weg","gender":"m"},{"word":"Landstra\xdfe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Strecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahrbahn","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahrweg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verkehrsstra\xdfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Autostra\xdfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahrdamm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Reede","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":384,"question":"roll","answers":[{"word":"rollen"},{"word":"etw.Akk ausrollen"},{"word":"w\xe4lzen"},{"word":"grollen"},{"word":"wirbeln"},{"word":"walzen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk walzen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk w\xe4lzen","l":1},{"word":"drehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk aufrollen","l":1},{"word":"schlingern","l":1},{"word":"kugeln","l":1},{"word":"kullern","l":1},{"word":"eine Rolle machen","l":1},{"word":"wickeln","l":1},{"word":"Rolle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Br\xf6tchen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Walze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Semmel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wirbel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xf6llchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schrippe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schaukeln","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"B\xfcndel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Register","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wiegen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Brausen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Liste","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wecken","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schlingern","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Roulade","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ballen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rundst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":385,"question":"room","answers":[{"word":"Zimmer","gender":"n"},{"word":"Raum","gender":"m"},{"word":"Platz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Saal","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stube","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"R\xe4umlichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kammer","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gemach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gelass","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"wohnen"}]},{"id":386,"question":"rub","answers":[{"word":"reiben"},{"word":"abreiben","l":1},{"word":"verreiben","l":1},{"word":"rubbeln","l":1},{"word":"scheuern","l":1},{"word":"frottieren","l":1},{"word":"Reiben","gender":"n"},{"word":"Scheuern","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":387,"question":"rule","answers":[{"word":"Regel","gender":"f"},{"word":"Herrschaft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorschrift","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bestimmung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Regelfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Regelung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Richtlinie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gebot","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Norm","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Linie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Regiment","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Spielregel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rechtsvorschrift","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ma\xdfstab","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Regierungszeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"bestimmen"},{"word":"regieren"},{"word":"herrschen"},{"word":"entscheiden"},{"word":"verf\xfcgen"},{"word":"regeln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk linieren","l":1},{"word":"beherrschen","l":1},{"word":"walten","l":1}]},{"id":388,"question":"run","answers":[{"word":"laufen"},{"word":"betreiben"},{"word":"fahren"},{"word":"verlaufen"},{"word":"rennen"},{"word":"durchf\xfchren"},{"word":"str\xf6men"},{"word":"ausf\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"starten","l":1},{"word":"laufen lassen","l":1},{"word":"ablaufen","l":1},{"word":"verkehren","l":1},{"word":"ausgehen","l":1},{"word":"treiben","l":1},{"word":"springen","l":1},{"word":"ablaufen lassen","l":1},{"word":"abfahren","l":1},{"word":"rinnen","l":1},{"word":"jagen","l":1},{"word":"schnell laufen","l":1},{"word":"auseinander laufen","l":1},{"word":"f\xe4rben","l":1},{"word":"zerflie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"Run","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ablauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auflage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahrt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Durchlauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verlauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Laufzeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Serie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ansturm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Andrang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Reihe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bahn","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Folge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sequenz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spielzeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"H\xfchnerhof","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gehege","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Startbefehl","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Laufmasche","gender":"f"},{"word":"gelaufen"},{"word":"gerannt","l":1},{"word":"kandidiert","l":1},{"word":"geflossen","l":1},{"word":"zerflossen","l":1},{"word":"gestr\xf6mt","l":1}]},{"id":389,"question":"salt","answers":[{"word":"Salz","gender":"n"},{"word":"Streusalz","gender":"n"},{"word":"etw.Akk salzen"},{"word":"einsalzen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk einp\xf6keln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk p\xf6keln","l":1},{"word":"salzig"}]},{"id":390,"question":"sand","answers":[{"word":"Sand","gender":"m"},{"word":"schleifen"},{"word":"schmirgeln"},{"word":"abschmirgeln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abschleifen","l":1},{"word":"absanden","l":1}]},{"id":391,"question":"scale","answers":[{"word":"Skala","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ma\xdfstab","gender":"m"},{"word":"Dimension","gender":"f"},{"word":"Umfang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Waage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tonleiter","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Skalierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausma\xdf","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Mensur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bandbreite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zunder","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gr\xf6\xdfenordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Waagschale","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kesselstein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Staffel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ma\xdfeinteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tabelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kesselsteine","l":1},{"word":"Reichweite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schuppe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Brennzunder","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gradeinteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tongeschlecht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"skalieren"},{"word":"wiegen"},{"word":"erklimmen"},{"word":"anpassen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk dimensionieren","l":1},{"word":"staffeln","l":1},{"word":"Schuppen entfernen","l":1},{"word":"ersteigen","l":1},{"word":"normieren","l":1}]},{"id":392,"question":"science","answers":[{"word":"Wissenschaft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Naturwissenschaft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Lehre","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":393,"question":"sea","answers":[{"word":"Meer","gender":"n"},{"word":"See","gender":"f"}]},{"id":394,"question":"seat","answers":[{"word":"Sitz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Platz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sitzplatz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Mandat","gender":"n"},{"word":"Sitzfl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sitzbank","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sitzschale","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sitzgelegenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stuhl","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bank","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auflagefl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Amtssitz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abgeordnetensitz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hosenboden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"hinsetzen"}]},{"id":395,"question":"secretary","answers":[{"word":"Sekret\xe4r","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sekret\xe4rin","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schriftf\xfchrer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Protokollf\xfchrer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Minister","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":396,"question":"selection","answers":[{"word":"Auswahl","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sortiment","gender":"n"},{"word":"Wahl","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Selektion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auslese","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anwahl","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Markierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Selektierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auslesung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aussonderung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":397,"question":"self","answers":[{"word":"Selbst","gender":"n"},{"word":"ich"},{"word":"selber"}]},{"id":398,"question":"sense","answers":[{"word":"Sinn","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gef\xfchl","gender":"n"},{"word":"Bedeutung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesp\xfcr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wahrnehmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Empfindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einsicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Empfindungsverm\xf6gen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"sp\xfcren"},{"word":"f\xfchlen"},{"word":"etw.Akk ahnen"},{"word":"empfinden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erahnen","l":1},{"word":"wahrnehmen","l":1},{"word":"wittern","l":1},{"word":"abf\xfchlen","l":1},{"word":"abtasten","l":1},{"word":"herausf\xfchlen","l":1}]},{"id":399,"question":"servant","answers":[{"word":"Knecht","gender":"m"},{"word":"Dienerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dienstmagd","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bediensteter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dienstbotin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dienstbote","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dienstm\xe4dchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dienstknecht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zofe","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":400,"question":"sex","answers":[{"word":"Geschlecht","gender":"n"},{"word":"Sex","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geschlechtsverkehr","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"anmachen","l":1},{"word":"stimulieren","l":1}]},{"id":401,"question":"shade","answers":[{"word":"Schatten","gender":"m"},{"word":"Farbton","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schirm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schattierung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Nuance","gender":"f"},{"word":"Rollladen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Farbe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lampenschirm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Jalousie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abschattung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xe4rbung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beschattung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"T\xf6nung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Farbnuance","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abstufung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Blende","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Farbt\xf6nung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Farbschattierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Blendschutz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zwischenton","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abt\xf6nung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rouleau","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"schraffieren"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) beschatten"},{"word":"abschirmen"},{"word":"Schatten werfen","l":1},{"word":"abdunkeln","l":1},{"word":"abstufen","l":1},{"word":"abt\xf6nen","l":1},{"word":"abschattieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk sch\xfctteln"},{"word":"(jdn./etw.Akk) ersch\xfcttern"},{"word":"zittern"},{"word":"bewegen"},{"word":"etw.Akk r\xfctteln","l":1},{"word":"wackeln","l":1},{"word":"beben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk durchsch\xfctteln","l":1},{"word":"schlottern","l":1},{"word":"ins Wanken bringen","l":1},{"word":"erzittern","l":1},{"word":"erbeben","l":1}]},{"id":402,"question":"shake","answers":[{"word":"Shake","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sch\xfctteln","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Beben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ersch\xfctterung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Riss durch nat\xfcrlichen Wuchs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Erdriss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Moment","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Augenblick","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk sch\xfctteln"},{"word":"bewegen"},{"word":"(jdn./etw.Akk) ersch\xfcttern"},{"word":"zittern"},{"word":"etw.Akk r\xfctteln","l":1},{"word":"beben","l":1},{"word":"wackeln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk durchsch\xfctteln","l":1},{"word":"erbeben","l":1},{"word":"ins Wanken bringen","l":1},{"word":"schlottern","l":1},{"word":"erzittern","l":1}]},{"id":403,"question":"shame","answers":[{"word":"Scham","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schande","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schmach","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schamgef\xfchl","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Jammer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schandfleck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Besch\xe4mung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"jdn. besch\xe4men"}]},{"id":404,"question":"shock","answers":[{"word":"Schock","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sto\xdf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Elektroschock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schreck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufprall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ersch\xfctterung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erdsto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Betroffenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schockreaktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Docke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Garbenb\xfcndel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Getreideb\xfcndel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Hocke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"schockieren"},{"word":"entsetzen","l":1},{"word":"schocken","l":1},{"word":"ersch\xfcttern","l":1},{"word":"emp\xf6ren","l":1},{"word":"Ansto\xdf erregen","l":1},{"word":"best\xfcrzen","l":1}]},{"id":405,"question":"side","answers":[{"word":"Seite","gender":"f"},{"word":"Rand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Beilage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Flanke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wand","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Seitenteil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stirnseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Team","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schenkel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Mannschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Seitenfl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bordwand","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Effet","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":406,"question":"sign","answers":[{"word":"Zeichen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schild","gender":"n"},{"word":"Anzeichen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Wert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wegweiser","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kennzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Spur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hinweisschild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sternzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Signal","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Signum","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Indiz","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aush\xe4ngeschild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Hinweistafel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wink","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Symptom","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Abzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sternbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Andeutung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"unterzeichnen"},{"word":"unterschreiben"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) signieren","l":1},{"word":"ein Zeichen geben","l":1},{"word":"zeichnen","l":1},{"word":"unterfertigen","l":1},{"word":"winken","l":1}]},{"id":407,"question":"silk","answers":[{"word":"Seide","gender":"f"},{"word":"Seidenstoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kronanwalt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"seiden"}]},{"id":408,"question":"silver","answers":[{"word":"Silber","gender":"n"},{"word":"Silberbesteck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tafelsilber","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Silbergeschirr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Silbergeld","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"silbern"},{"word":"silberfarben"},{"word":"etw.Akk versilbern"}]},{"id":409,"question":"sister","answers":[{"word":"Schwester","gender":"f"}]},{"id":410,"question":"size","answers":[{"word":"Gr\xf6\xdfe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Format","gender":"n"},{"word":"Umfang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Baugr\xf6\xdfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gr\xf6\xdfenordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"H\xf6he","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dimension","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Konfektionsgr\xf6\xdfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Nummer","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausma\xdf","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schlichte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dicke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kleidergr\xf6\xdfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leim","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auftragleim","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk ausmessen"},{"word":"beschichten"},{"word":"schlichten","l":1},{"word":"grundieren","l":1},{"word":"von etw.Dat die Gr\xf6\xdfe bestimmen","l":1}]},{"id":411,"question":"sky","answers":[{"word":"Himmel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Firmament","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":412,"question":"sleep","answers":[{"word":"Schlaf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Nachtruhe","gender":"f"},{"word":"schlummern"},{"word":"pennen","l":1},{"word":"knacken","l":1}]},{"id":413,"question":"slip","answers":[{"word":"rutschen"},{"word":"schl\xfcpfen"},{"word":"verrutschen"},{"word":"gleiten"},{"word":"ausrutschen"},{"word":"gleiten lassen","l":1},{"word":"entfallen","l":1},{"word":"abrutschen","l":1},{"word":"stecken","l":1},{"word":"abgleiten","l":1},{"word":"entgleiten","l":1},{"word":"schleichen","l":1},{"word":"Schlupf haben","l":1},{"word":"fallen","l":1},{"word":"schleifen lassen","l":1},{"word":"absinken","l":1},{"word":"einen Fehltritt begehen","l":1},{"word":"flutschen","l":1},{"word":"nachlassen","l":1},{"word":"\xfcbersehen","l":1},{"word":"jdm. etw.Akk zustecken","l":1},{"word":"verpassen","l":1},{"word":"schleudern","l":1},{"word":"entschwinden","l":1},{"word":"ausgleiten","l":1},{"word":"jdm. etw.Akk unterschieben","l":1},{"word":"glitschen","l":1},{"word":"witschen","l":1},{"word":"zur\xfcckgehen","l":1},{"word":"Slip","gender":"m"},{"word":"Rutschen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Rutsch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gleiten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schlupf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausrutschen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Versehen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zettel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Beleg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schlicker","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausrutscher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Panne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Versprecher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fehlleistung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fehler","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Missgeschick","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kassenzettel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fehltritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterrock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Trieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Beguss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sch\xf6ssling","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Erdrutsch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spross","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spr\xf6ssling","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Deckungszusage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lapsus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Setzling","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schnitzer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Irrtum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterkleid","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ungl\xfccksfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausgleiten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Unfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fl\xfcchtigkeitsfehler","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Papier","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Patzer","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":414,"question":"slope","answers":[{"word":"Piste","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Neigung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gef\xe4lle","gender":"n"},{"word":"Abhang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Skipiste","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Steigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hanglage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"B\xf6schung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hangneigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schr\xe4ge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anstieg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Flanke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abfahrt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Neigungsgrad","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lehne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rain","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Halde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Absch\xfcssigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"abfallen"},{"word":"geneigt sein","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk neigen","l":1},{"word":"abschr\xe4gen","l":1},{"word":"schr\xe4g abfallen","l":1},{"word":"schr\xe4g legen","l":1},{"word":"abb\xf6schen","l":1}]},{"id":415,"question":"smash","answers":[{"word":"etw.Akk zerschlagen"},{"word":"schmettern"},{"word":"schlagen","l":1},{"word":"prallen","l":1},{"word":"zerst\xf6ren","l":1},{"word":"zerbrechen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zertr\xfcmmern","l":1},{"word":"zerschellen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zerschmettern","l":1},{"word":"zerdeppern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk kaputtschlagen","l":1},{"word":"einwerfen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zusammenschlagen","l":1},{"word":"eindr\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"schwer treffen","l":1},{"word":"Zerbrechen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Krachen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schmetterschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zerkrachen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schmetterball","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"heftiger Schlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unfall","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":416,"question":"smell","answers":[{"word":"Geruch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Duft","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gestank","gender":"m"},{"word":"Duftnote","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Odor","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dunst","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"riechen"},{"word":"duften"},{"word":"schmecken","l":1},{"word":"stinken","l":1},{"word":"wittern","l":1},{"word":"beriechen","l":1},{"word":"m\xfcffeln","l":1}]},{"id":417,"question":"smile","answers":[{"word":"l\xe4cheln"},{"word":"schmunzeln","l":1},{"word":"L\xe4cheln","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schmunzeln","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":418,"question":"smoke","answers":[{"word":"Rauch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Nebel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dampf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dunst","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Qualm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Glimmst\xe4ngel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schmok","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"rauchen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) r\xe4uchern","l":1},{"word":"qualmen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk selchen","l":1},{"word":"selchen","l":1},{"word":"schm\xf6ken","l":1}]},{"id":419,"question":"sneeze","answers":[{"word":"niesen"},{"word":"Niesen","gender":"n"}]},{"id":420,"question":"snow","answers":[{"word":"Schnee","gender":"m"},{"word":"Hintergrundrauschen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Flimmern","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Koks","gender":"m"},{"word":"schneien"}]},{"id":421,"question":"soap","answers":[{"word":"Seife","gender":"f"},{"word":"einseifen","l":1},{"word":"abseifen","l":1}]},{"id":422,"question":"society","answers":[{"word":"Gesellschaft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verbindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vereinigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verband","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kulturkreis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Soziet\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":423,"question":"son","answers":[{"word":"Sohn","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sohnemann","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Filius","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":424,"question":"song","answers":[{"word":"Lied","gender":"n"},{"word":"Song","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gesang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sang","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":425,"question":"sort","answers":[{"word":"Art","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sorte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sortierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Qualit\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gattung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Typ","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Marke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"sortieren"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) verlesen","l":1},{"word":"einsortieren","l":1},{"word":"auslesen","l":1}]},{"id":426,"question":"sound","answers":[{"word":"Sound","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schall","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ger\xe4usch","gender":"n"},{"word":"Laut","gender":"m"},{"word":"Klangbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Meeresarm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Meerenge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mucks","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sonde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"solide"},{"word":"fundiert"},{"word":"fest"},{"word":"intakt"},{"word":"gesund"},{"word":"vern\xfcnftig"},{"word":"zuverl\xe4ssig"},{"word":"aussagekr\xe4ftig"},{"word":"triftig"},{"word":"unbesch\xe4digt"},{"word":"gut","l":1},{"word":"stark","l":1},{"word":"tief","l":1},{"word":"kr\xe4ftig","l":1},{"word":"stichhaltig","l":1},{"word":"einwandfrei","l":1},{"word":"stabil","l":1},{"word":"tragf\xe4hig","l":1},{"word":"begr\xfcndet","l":1},{"word":"gr\xfcndlich","l":1},{"word":"unversehrt","l":1},{"word":"lebensf\xe4hig","l":1},{"word":"fehlerfrei","l":1},{"word":"fehlerlos","l":1},{"word":"verl\xe4sslich","l":1},{"word":"solvent","l":1},{"word":"kreditf\xe4hig","l":1},{"word":"zahlungsf\xe4hig","l":1},{"word":"gediegen","l":1},{"word":"treffsicher","l":1},{"word":"klingen"},{"word":"ert\xf6nen"},{"word":"lauten"},{"word":"ausloten"},{"word":"sondieren"},{"word":"erklingen","l":1},{"word":"t\xf6nen","l":1},{"word":"einen Klang haben","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk anh\xf6ren","l":1},{"word":"erklingen lassen","l":1},{"word":"loten","l":1},{"word":"abklopfen","l":1},{"word":"erschallen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ert\xf6nen lassen","l":1},{"word":"abhorchen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erschallen lassen","l":1},{"word":"mitklingen","l":1}]},{"id":427,"question":"soup","answers":[{"word":"Suppe","gender":"f"},{"word":"S\xfcppchen","gender":"n"}]},{"id":428,"question":"space","answers":[{"word":"Raum","gender":"m"},{"word":"Platz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Weltall","gender":"n"},{"word":"L\xfccke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weltraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leerzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"All","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Stellplatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zwischenraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leertaste","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"freier Raum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leerstelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeitraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leerschritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Frist","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leerfeld","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ausschlussst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Spatium","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Durchschuss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"verteilen"},{"word":"etw.Akk verteilen"},{"word":"sperren","l":1}]},{"id":429,"question":"stage","answers":[{"word":"B\xfchne","gender":"f"},{"word":"Phase","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stufe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stadium","gender":"n"},{"word":"Etappe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Theaterb\xfchne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Podium","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Abschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schauplatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Station","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Plattform","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grad","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gestell","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Spielst\xe4tte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zwischenstufe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ger\xfcst","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Teilstrecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schichtstufe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) inszenieren"},{"word":"veranstalten"},{"word":"etw.Akk auff\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk auf die B\xfchne bringen","l":1},{"word":"bereitstellen","l":1},{"word":"arrangieren","l":1},{"word":"ausrichten","l":1}]},{"id":430,"question":"start","answers":[{"word":"Beginn","gender":"m"},{"word":"Start","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gr\xfcndung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anfang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufnahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auftakt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einstieg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorsprung","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abfahrt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufbruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Antritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abflug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Startplatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zusammenfahren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aufschrecken","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Abmarsch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ruck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorgabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"beginnen"},{"word":"starten"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) anfangen"},{"word":"gr\xfcnden"},{"word":"anlassen"},{"word":"etw.Akk einschalten"},{"word":"ins Leben rufen"},{"word":"hochfahren"},{"word":"entfachen"},{"word":"aufnehmen","l":1},{"word":"einleiten","l":1},{"word":"er\xf6ffnen","l":1},{"word":"einsetzen","l":1},{"word":"anlaufen","l":1},{"word":"anfahren","l":1},{"word":"losgehen","l":1},{"word":"aufbrechen","l":1},{"word":"ansetzen","l":1},{"word":"angehen","l":1},{"word":"losfahren","l":1},{"word":"aufbringen","l":1},{"word":"anspringen","l":1},{"word":"zucken","l":1},{"word":"abfahren","l":1},{"word":"anwerfen","l":1},{"word":"aufschrecken","l":1},{"word":"den Reigen er\xf6ffnen","l":1},{"word":"auffahren","l":1},{"word":"zusammenzucken","l":1},{"word":"abreisen","l":1}]},{"id":431,"question":"statement","answers":[{"word":"Erkl\xe4rung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stellungnahme","gender":"f"},{"word":"Aussage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Statement","gender":"n"},{"word":"Auszug","gender":"m"},{"word":"Behauptung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Aussagesatz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bericht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Angabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Darstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Begr\xfcndung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beschreibung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bescheinigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausweis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vermerk","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Feststellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kontoauszug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anweisung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Behauptungen","l":1},{"word":"Mitteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abrechnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Presseerkl\xe4rung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bankauszug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xc4u\xdferung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Darlegung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausf\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bankabrechnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rechenschaftsbericht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verlautbarung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einlassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bekundung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":432,"question":"steam","answers":[{"word":"Dampf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Wasserdampf","gender":"m"},{"word":"D\xe4mpfe","l":1},{"word":"Dunst","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) d\xfcnsten"},{"word":"d\xe4mpfen","l":1}]},{"id":433,"question":"steel","answers":[{"word":"Stahl","gender":"m"},{"word":"st\xe4hlern"},{"word":"sichAkk st\xe4hlen","l":1}]},{"id":434,"question":"step","answers":[{"word":"Schritt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stufe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Treppe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ma\xdfnahme","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sprosse","gender":"f"},{"word":"Arbeitsschritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sprung","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Trittstufe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Trittbrett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Takt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Treppenstufe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ablaufschritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Absatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tanzschritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auftragsschritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Trittblech","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"gehen","l":1},{"word":"schreiten","l":1}]},{"id":435,"question":"stitch","answers":[{"word":"Masche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stich","gender":"m"},{"word":"Seitenstechen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Stechen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Nadelstich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"n\xe4hen","l":1},{"word":"sticken","l":1},{"word":"steppen","l":1},{"word":"absteppen","l":1},{"word":"broschieren","l":1},{"word":"sticheln","l":1},{"word":"stopfen","l":1}]},{"id":436,"question":"stone","answers":[{"word":"Kern","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gestein","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"entsteinen"},{"word":"steinigen","l":1}]},{"id":437,"question":"stop","answers":[{"word":"Stopp","gender":"m"},{"word":"Halt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Pause","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stoppen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Station","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stillstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einhalt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Haltestelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einkehr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ende","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aufenthalt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zwischenstation","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Register","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zwischenstopp","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sperre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Haltepunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Blende","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abbruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anlegestelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Registerzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verschlusslaut","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fahrtunterbrechung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"stoppen"},{"word":"etw.Akk einstellen"},{"word":"aufh\xf6ren"},{"word":"anhalten"},{"word":"beenden"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) aufhalten"},{"word":"stehen bleiben"},{"word":"unterbinden"},{"word":"etw.Akk verhindern","l":1},{"word":"abbrechen","l":1},{"word":"bleiben","l":1},{"word":"unterbrechen","l":1},{"word":"stehenbleiben","l":1},{"word":"einhalten","l":1},{"word":"stillstehen","l":1},{"word":"absperren","l":1},{"word":"Halt machen","l":1},{"word":"enden","l":1},{"word":"innehalten","l":1},{"word":"haltmachen","l":1},{"word":"sperren","l":1},{"word":"bremsen","l":1},{"word":"zum Stillstand bringen","l":1},{"word":"hemmen","l":1},{"word":"abstellen","l":1},{"word":"arretieren","l":1},{"word":"abstoppen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk seinlassen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zust\xf6pseln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk sein lassen","l":1},{"word":"zum Stehen bringen","l":1},{"word":"aussetzen","l":1},{"word":"schweigen","l":1},{"word":"spachteln","l":1},{"word":"pfropfen","l":1},{"word":"unterbleiben","l":1}]},{"id":438,"question":"story","answers":[{"word":"Geschichte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Story","gender":"f"},{"word":"Handlung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Erz\xe4hlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Artikel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"M\xe4rchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schwindelei","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schwank","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fabel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Etage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stockwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Geschoss","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":439,"question":"stretch","answers":[{"word":"strecken"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) dehnen"},{"word":"spannen"},{"word":"sichAkk strecken","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk dehnen","l":1},{"word":"ausstrecken","l":1},{"word":"ausdehnen","l":1},{"word":"aufspannen","l":1},{"word":"fordern","l":1},{"word":"weiten","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk recken","l":1},{"word":"gro\xdfz\xfcgig auslegen","l":1},{"word":"lang ziehen","l":1},{"word":"l\xe4ngen","l":1},{"word":"weit fassen","l":1},{"word":"ausbreiten","l":1},{"word":"hinreichen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ausweiten","l":1},{"word":"Strecke","gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xfcck","gender":"n"},{"word":"Strecken","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dehnbarkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dehnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Elastizit\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausdehnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wegstrecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeitraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeitspanne","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":440,"question":"structure","answers":[{"word":"Struktur","gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufbau","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bauwerk","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gliederung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ger\xfcst","gender":"n"},{"word":"Konstruktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gef\xfcge","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Geb\xe4ude","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bauweise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bauk\xf6rper","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rahmen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zusammensetzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gebilde","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bausubstanz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Textur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Organismus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufbauservice","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gerippe","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"strukturieren"},{"word":"aufbauen"},{"word":"gliedern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bauen","l":1},{"word":"regeln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk konstruieren","l":1}]},{"id":441,"question":"substance","answers":[{"word":"Substanz","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stoff","gender":"m"},{"word":"Inhalt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Wirkstoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Material","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gehalt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kern","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Materie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wesentliche","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Droge","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":442,"question":"sugar","answers":[{"word":"Zucker","gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk zuckern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk s\xfc\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk einzuckern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verzuckern","l":1}]},{"id":443,"question":"suggestion","answers":[{"word":"Vorschlag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Anregung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Suggestion","gender":"f"},{"word":"Andeutung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Idee","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hinweis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vermutung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tipp","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ansinnen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wink","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hauch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":444,"question":"summer","answers":[{"word":"Sommer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sommerzeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"sommerlich"}]},{"id":445,"question":"support","answers":[{"word":"Unterst\xfctzung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Betreuung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Halt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Support","gender":"m"},{"word":"Hilfe","gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xfctze","gender":"f"},{"word":"Tr\xe4ger","gender":"m"},{"word":"Beistand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterlage","gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xf6rderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Begleiten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Begleitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xe4rkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zustimmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hilfestellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abst\xfctzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xfctzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Auflage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Halterung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"R\xfcckhalt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lager","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sch\xfctzenhilfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sympathie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterhalt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Halter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auflager","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"R\xfcckendeckung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bef\xfcrwortung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Untermauerung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zutun","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Betreuung von Kunden","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Chassistr\xe4ger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Absteifung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abst\xfctzwinkel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"(jdn.) unterst\xfctzen"},{"word":"f\xf6rdern"},{"word":"st\xfctzen"},{"word":"bef\xfcrworten"},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk begleiten","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk einsetzen","l":1},{"word":"helfen","l":1},{"word":"beg\xfcnstigen","l":1},{"word":"vertreten","l":1},{"word":"abst\xfctzen","l":1},{"word":"unterhalten","l":1},{"word":"ern\xe4hren","l":1},{"word":"hinter jdm. stehen","l":1},{"word":"lagern","l":1},{"word":"bekr\xe4ftigen","l":1},{"word":"jdm. Hilfestellung leisten","l":1},{"word":"unterbauen","l":1},{"word":"durchbringen","l":1}]},{"id":446,"question":"surprise","answers":[{"word":"Erstaunen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verbl\xfcffung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verwunderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xfcberraschen"},{"word":"verwundern"},{"word":"unerwartet"}]},{"id":447,"question":"swim","answers":[{"word":"schwimmen"},{"word":"baden"},{"word":"durchschwimmen","l":1},{"word":"verschwimmen","l":1},{"word":"Schwimmen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Bad","gender":"n"}]},{"id":448,"question":"system","answers":[{"word":"System","gender":"n"},{"word":"Anlage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verfahren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Systematik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Methode","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ordnung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":449,"question":"talk","answers":[{"word":"sprechen"},{"word":"reden"},{"word":"auspacken"},{"word":"erz\xe4hlen","l":1},{"word":"plaudern","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk unterreden","l":1},{"word":"schwatzen","l":1},{"word":"Gespr\xe4ch","gender":"n"},{"word":"Vortrag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Besprechung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Rede","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gerede","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Diskussion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterhaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aussprache","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterredung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":450,"question":"taste","answers":[{"word":"Geschmack","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kostprobe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorgeschmack","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gusto","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geschmackssinn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geschmacksrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"schmecken"},{"word":"kosten"},{"word":"probieren"},{"word":"etw.Akk schmecken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk probieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verkosten","l":1},{"word":"abschmecken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk gustieren","l":1}]},{"id":451,"question":"tax","answers":[{"word":"Steuer","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abgabe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zins","gender":"m"},{"word":"Taxe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geb\xfchr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"steuerlich"},{"word":"besteuern"},{"word":"strapazieren"},{"word":"versteuern","l":1},{"word":"jdn. steuerlich belasten","l":1},{"word":"beschuldigen","l":1},{"word":"bezichtigen","l":1}]},{"id":452,"question":"teaching","answers":[{"word":"Lehren","gender":"n"},{"word":"Lehre","gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterricht","gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterrichten","gender":"n"},{"word":"Lehrt\xe4tigkeit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schuldienst","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lehrbetrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterweisung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"lehrend","l":1},{"word":"beibringend","l":1},{"word":"unterrichtend","l":1},{"word":"anlernend","l":1},{"word":"unterrichten"},{"word":"jdn. schulen","l":1},{"word":"vermitteln","l":1},{"word":"jdn. belehren","l":1},{"word":"jdm. etw.Akk beibringen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. unterweisen","l":1},{"word":"anlernen","l":1}]},{"id":453,"question":"tendency","answers":[{"word":"Tendenz","gender":"f"},{"word":"Neigung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Trend","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Str\xf6mung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Veranlagung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ansatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Absicht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Disposition","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anlage","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":454,"question":"test","answers":[{"word":"(etw.Akk) testen"},{"word":"etw.Akk \xfcberpr\xfcfen"},{"word":"pr\xfcfen"},{"word":"etw.Akk pr\xfcfen"},{"word":"ausprobieren"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) erproben","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) untersuchen","l":1},{"word":"einen Test durchf\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) probieren","l":1},{"word":"jdn. abfragen","l":1},{"word":"austesten","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk auf die Probe stellen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk checken","l":1},{"word":"Test","gender":"m"},{"word":"Pr\xfcfung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kontrolle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Klausur","gender":"f"},{"word":"Probe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xdcberpr\xfcfung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Untersuchung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Versuch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Erprobung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Arbeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Testung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bew\xe4hrungsprobe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Examen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kolloquium","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Klassenarbeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Check","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klausurarbeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schularbeit","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":455,"question":"theory","answers":[{"word":"Theorie","gender":"f"},{"word":"These","gender":"f"},{"word":"Lehre","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":456,"question":"thing","answers":[{"word":"Sache","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gegenstand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ding","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Teil","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dings","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gebilde","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schose","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Chose","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":457,"question":"thought","answers":[{"word":"gedacht"},{"word":"nachgedacht"},{"word":"geglaubt","l":1},{"word":"angenommen","l":1},{"word":"gemeint","l":1},{"word":"gegr\xfcbelt","l":1},{"word":"Gedanke","gender":"m"},{"word":"denken"},{"word":"glauben"},{"word":"nachdenken"},{"word":"finden"},{"word":"\xfcberlegen"},{"word":"mitdenken","l":1},{"word":"gr\xfcbeln","l":1},{"word":"sinnieren","l":1},{"word":"sinnen","l":1},{"word":"knobeln","l":1},{"word":"vermeinen","l":1}]},{"id":458,"question":"thunder","answers":[{"word":"Donner","gender":"m"},{"word":"donnern"}]},{"id":459,"question":"time","answers":[{"word":"Zeitpunkt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Uhrzeit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Frist","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeitraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stunde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spielraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rhythmus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tageszeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Laufzeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Takt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geschwindigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tempo","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zeitma\xdf","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"messen"},{"word":"stoppen"},{"word":"zeitlich bestimmen","l":1},{"word":"zeitlich festlegen","l":1},{"word":"abstoppen","l":1}]},{"id":460,"question":"tin","answers":[{"word":"Zinn","gender":"n"},{"word":"Blech","gender":"n"},{"word":"Wei\xdfblech","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dose","gender":"f"},{"word":"Konserve","gender":"f"},{"word":"Konservenb\xfcchse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"B\xfcchse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Blechdose","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zinnblechb\xfcchse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Blechb\xfcchse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Konservendose","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"verzinnen"},{"word":"etw.Akk konservieren"},{"word":"etw.Akk in B\xfcchsen einlegen","l":1}]},{"id":461,"question":"top","answers":[{"word":"Top","gender":"n"},{"word":"Spitze","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gipfel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Oberteil","gender":"m"},{"word":"Deckel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Oberseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Oberfl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Platte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anfang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verdeck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Oberkante","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Krone","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kopfende","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kopfteil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kreisel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"obere Seite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"oberer Teil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kappe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wipfel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Baumwipfel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spielkreisel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"oberes Ende","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"oberste"},{"word":"h\xf6chste"},{"word":"erstklassig"},{"word":"bestes"},{"word":"beste","l":1},{"word":"bester","l":1},{"word":"oberstes","l":1},{"word":"oberster","l":1},{"word":"kr\xf6nen"},{"word":"etw.Akk \xfcbertreffen"},{"word":"etw.Akk \xfcbersteigen","l":1},{"word":"bedecken","l":1},{"word":"kappen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk \xfcberragen","l":1},{"word":"maximal erreichen","l":1}]},{"id":462,"question":"touch","answers":[{"word":"Kontakt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ber\xfchrung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Touch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verbindung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hauch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Anschlag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gef\xfchl","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anflug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Empfindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"leichter Anfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ansatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Seitenaus","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"ber\xfchren"},{"word":"anfassen"},{"word":"streifen"},{"word":"anr\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"anf\xfchlen","l":1},{"word":"angreifen","l":1},{"word":"befassen","l":1},{"word":"betasten","l":1},{"word":"anschlagen","l":1},{"word":"antasten","l":1},{"word":"anlangen","l":1}]},{"id":463,"question":"trade","answers":[{"word":"Handel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Trade","gender":"m"},{"word":"Handwerk","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gewerbe","gender":"n"},{"word":"Branche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ft","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Berufsstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Beruf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abschluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gewerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Warenaustausch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Handelswesen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wirtschaftszweig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gewerbebetrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sparte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Handwerksberuf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftszweig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gewerbezweig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"handeln"},{"word":"Handel treiben"},{"word":"tauschen"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4fte machen","l":1},{"word":"eintauschen","l":1},{"word":"einhandeln","l":1},{"word":"gewerblich"}]},{"id":464,"question":"transport","answers":[{"word":"Transport","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verkehrsmittel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bef\xf6rderung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fracht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bef\xf6rderungsmittel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verkehrswirtschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xdcberf\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ladung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anfuhr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"transportieren"},{"word":"bef\xf6rdern"}]},{"id":465,"question":"trick","answers":[{"word":"Trick","gender":"m"},{"word":"Streich","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stich","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kniff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Clou","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kunst","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kunstgriff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Winkelzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kunstst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"List","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dreh","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Taschenspielertrick","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Finte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Masche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Falle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ulk","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Man\xf6ver","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dressur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(jdn.) betr\xfcgen"},{"word":"jdn. reinlegen"},{"word":"hereinlegen"},{"word":"jdn. t\xe4uschen","l":1},{"word":"beschwindeln","l":1},{"word":"(jdn.) \xfcberlisten","l":1},{"word":"(jdn.) austricksen","l":1}]},{"id":466,"question":"trouble","answers":[{"word":"Trouble","gender":"m"},{"word":"Problem","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schwierigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xf6rung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Not","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Umstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unannehmlichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"M\xfche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beschwerden","l":1},{"word":"Unruhe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Plage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Malesche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sorge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Defekt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leiden","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Krankheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"M\xfchewaltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"technische St\xf6rung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Knatsch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stunk","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schererei","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zores","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"bel\xe4stigen"},{"word":"Sorgen machen"},{"word":"beunruhigen"},{"word":"jdm. Schwierigkeiten bereiten","l":1},{"word":"bem\xfchen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. gr\xe4men","l":1},{"word":"jdn. plagen","l":1},{"word":"st\xf6ren","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk heimsuchen","l":1},{"word":"jdm. Unannehmlichkeiten bereiten","l":1},{"word":"Kummer machen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. bek\xfcmmern","l":1},{"word":"jdn. qu\xe4len","l":1},{"word":"jdm. Umst\xe4nde bereiten","l":1}]},{"id":467,"question":"turn","answers":[{"word":"abbiegen"},{"word":"biegen"},{"word":"etw.Akk drehen"},{"word":"umdrehen"},{"word":"umlegen"},{"word":"wenden","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk umdrehen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk wandeln","l":1},{"word":"umsetzen","l":1},{"word":"abdrehen","l":1},{"word":"rotieren","l":1},{"word":"bet\xe4tigen","l":1},{"word":"umbiegen","l":1},{"word":"umschlagen","l":1},{"word":"herumdrehen","l":1},{"word":"umwenden","l":1},{"word":"Wendung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Umdrehung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kurve","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wende","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Drehung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Runde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spaziergang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Drehbewegung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tour","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wegbiegung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Neigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reihenfolge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Windung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wendekurve","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Drall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kr\xfcmmung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spazierfahrt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Handelsgewinn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tendenz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Doppelschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":468,"question":"twist","answers":[{"word":"Twist","gender":"m"},{"word":"Dreh","gender":"m"},{"word":"Drehung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wendung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Drall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verdrehung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schraube","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Faden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kurve","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verdrillung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zwirn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xfcberraschende Wendung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Umdrehung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Biegung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Effet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bindfaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wandel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Windung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verwindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Garndrehung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) drehen"},{"word":"verflechten"},{"word":"verdrehen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk drehen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk winden","l":1},{"word":"flechten","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk verschlingen","l":1},{"word":"verdrillen","l":1},{"word":"zwirnen","l":1},{"word":"verziehen","l":1},{"word":"wickeln","l":1},{"word":"Twist tanzen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk schl\xe4ngeln","l":1},{"word":"zusammendrehen","l":1},{"word":"verbiegen","l":1},{"word":"verkr\xfcmmen","l":1},{"word":"zwirbeln","l":1}]},{"id":469,"question":"unit","answers":[{"word":"Einheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ger\xe4t","gender":"n"},{"word":"Anlage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Element","gender":"n"},{"word":"Truppe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ma\xdfeinheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aggregat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"St\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Baugruppe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verband","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lektion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mengeneinheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Baueinheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Truppenteil","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Referat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kraftwerksblock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einzelteil","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Einerstelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Block eines Kraftwerkes","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geb\xfchreneinheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anbauteil","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Betrachtungseinheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bauelement","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":470,"question":"use","answers":[{"word":"Nutzung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Nutzen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Einsatz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gebrauch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verwendung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Benutzung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Anwendung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verwendungszweck","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verwertung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beanspruchung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Inanspruchnahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Handhabung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mitbenutzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Brauch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verwendungsweise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verwendungsm\xf6glichkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mitben\xfctzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) verwenden"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) nutzen"},{"word":"gebrauchen"},{"word":"etw.Akk einsetzen"},{"word":"benutzen"},{"word":"brauchen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) in Anspruch nehmen"},{"word":"ausnutzen"},{"word":"anwenden","l":1},{"word":"belegen","l":1},{"word":"ben\xfctzen","l":1},{"word":"verbrauchen","l":1},{"word":"ausn\xfctzen","l":1},{"word":"ausf\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"befahren","l":1},{"word":"beanspruchen","l":1},{"word":"heranziehen","l":1},{"word":"wahrnehmen","l":1},{"word":"aufbrauchen","l":1},{"word":"begehen","l":1}]},{"id":471,"question":"value","answers":[{"word":"Wert","gender":"m"},{"word":"Nutzen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Betrag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gr\xf6\xdfe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wertsch\xf6pfung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wertigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bedeutung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stellenwert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Valuta","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wichtigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Festwert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Relevanz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kostbarkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bedeutsamkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Werthaftigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"bewerten"},{"word":"den Wert sch\xe4tzen","l":1},{"word":"wertsch\xe4tzen","l":1},{"word":"hoch achten","l":1},{"word":"taxieren","l":1}]},{"id":472,"question":"verse","answers":[{"word":"Vers","gender":"m"},{"word":"Strophe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Lyrik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Versdichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":473,"question":"vessel","answers":[{"word":"Schiff","gender":"n"},{"word":"Beh\xe4lter","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gef\xe4\xdf","gender":"n"},{"word":"Fahrzeug","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kessel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Seefahrzeug","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wasserfahrzeug","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Beh\xe4ltnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Luftschiff","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":474,"question":"view","answers":[{"word":"Bild","gender":"n"},{"word":"Hinblick","gender":"m"},{"word":"Aussicht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ansicht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sichtweise","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausblick","gender":"m"},{"word":"Perspektive","gender":"f"},{"word":"Meinung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Auffassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Betrachtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xdcberblick","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Darstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anblick","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Standpunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anschauung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Betrachtungsweise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufnahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"betrachten"},{"word":"besichtigen"},{"word":"ansehen","l":1},{"word":"anschauen","l":1},{"word":"pr\xfcfen","l":1}]},{"id":475,"question":"voice","answers":[{"word":"Stimme","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sprache","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Organ","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Mitspracherecht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Stimmlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"stimmhafter Laut","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sprachrohr","gender":"n"},{"word":"\xe4u\xdfern"},{"word":"zum Ausdruck bringen"},{"word":"aussprechen"},{"word":"ausdr\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"stimmhaft aussprechen","l":1}]},{"id":476,"question":"walk","answers":[{"word":"laufen"},{"word":"zu Fu\xdf gehen"},{"word":"spazieren","l":1},{"word":"spazieren gehen","l":1},{"word":"wandeln","l":1},{"word":"umgehen","l":1},{"word":"zur\xfccklegen","l":1},{"word":"spuken","l":1},{"word":"tippeln","l":1},{"word":"herumspuken","l":1},{"word":"Spaziergang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Weg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rundgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Runde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Marsch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fu\xdfmarsch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spazierweg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wanderweg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anmarsch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gangart","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":477,"question":"war","answers":[{"word":"Krieg","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kampf","gender":"m"},{"word":"k\xe4mpfen","l":1},{"word":"Krieg f\xfchren","l":1}]},{"id":478,"question":"wash","answers":[{"word":"(etw.Akk) waschen"},{"word":"etw.Akk abwaschen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk sp\xfclen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk reinigen","l":1},{"word":"t\xfcnchen","l":1},{"word":"branden","l":1},{"word":"schwemmen","l":1},{"word":"Waschen","gender":"n"},{"word":"W\xe4sche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"W\xe4sserung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Waschgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"T\xfcnche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Br\xfche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kielwasser","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wassererosion","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":479,"question":"waste","answers":[{"word":"Abfall","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abf\xe4lle"},{"word":"M\xfcll","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verschwendung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abfallstoffe","l":1},{"word":"Ausschuss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abfallprodukt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vergeudung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reste","l":1},{"word":"W\xfcste","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verlust","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ein\xf6de","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"W\xfcstenei","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) verschwenden"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) vergeuden"},{"word":"verw\xfcsten","l":1},{"word":"verbrauchen","l":1},{"word":"verk\xfcmmern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verprassen","l":1},{"word":"verderben","l":1},{"word":"umkommen","l":1},{"word":"schw\xe4chen","l":1},{"word":"verfallen","l":1},{"word":"vertun","l":1},{"word":"verzehren","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberfl\xfcssig"},{"word":"\xfcbersch\xfcssig"},{"word":"unbrauchbar"},{"word":"w\xfcst","l":1},{"word":"\xf6de","l":1},{"word":"ungenutzt","l":1}]},{"id":480,"question":"water","answers":[{"word":"Wasser","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gew\xe4sser","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Nass","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"G\xe4nsewein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"bew\xe4ssern"},{"word":"gie\xdfen"},{"word":"w\xe4ssern","l":1},{"word":"trinken","l":1},{"word":"tr\xe4nken","l":1},{"word":"tr\xe4nen","l":1},{"word":"begie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"sprengen","l":1},{"word":"schwemmen","l":1},{"word":"triefen","l":1},{"word":"beregnen","l":1}]},{"id":481,"question":"wave","answers":[{"word":"Welle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Woge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wink","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"wellen"},{"word":"winken"},{"word":"schwenken"},{"word":"flattern"},{"word":"wehen"},{"word":"wogen","l":1},{"word":"jdm. zuwinken"}]},{"id":482,"question":"wax","answers":[{"word":"wachsen"},{"word":"werden"},{"word":"zunehmen","l":1},{"word":"mit Wachs versehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk einwachsen","l":1},{"word":"Wachs","gender":"n"},{"word":"Enthaarung","gender":"f"}]},{"id":483,"question":"way","answers":[{"word":"Weise","gender":"f"},{"word":"Weg","gender":"m"},{"word":"Art","gender":"f"},{"word":"M\xf6glichkeit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hinsicht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Methode","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Richtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mittel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Strecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahrt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Art und Weise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Platz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gelegenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verfahren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wegstrecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zustand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Manier","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bahn","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xfchrungsbahn","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"viel","l":1},{"word":"weit","l":1}]},{"id":484,"question":"weather","answers":[{"word":"Wetter","gender":"n"},{"word":"Witterung","gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk \xfcberstehen"},{"word":"verwittern","l":1},{"word":"ablagern lassen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk gut \xfcberstehen","l":1},{"word":"dem Wetter aussetzen","l":1},{"word":"verwittern lassen","l":1},{"word":"trocknen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abwettern","l":1},{"word":"auswittern","l":1},{"word":"austrocknen","l":1}]},{"id":485,"question":"week","answers":[{"word":"Woche","gender":"f"},{"word":"pro Woche"}]},{"id":486,"question":"weight","answers":[{"word":"Gewicht","gender":"n"},{"word":"Last","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bedeutung","gender":"f"},{"word":"K\xf6rpergewicht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schwere","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Belastung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stellenwert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"B\xfcrde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wichtigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"beschweren"},{"word":"gewichten","l":1},{"word":"belasten","l":1},{"word":"beeinflussen","l":1},{"word":"verf\xe4lschen","l":1}]},{"id":487,"question":"wind","answers":[{"word":"Wind","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bl\xe4hungen"},{"word":"Windung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Luft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Atem","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk aufwickeln"},{"word":"aufziehen"},{"word":"sichAkk winden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk kurbeln","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk drehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk spulen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk schlingen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abspulen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk aufspulen","l":1},{"word":"rollen","l":1}]},{"id":488,"question":"wine","answers":[{"word":"Wein","gender":"m"},{"word":"Rebensaft","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":489,"question":"winter","answers":[{"word":"Winter","gender":"m"},{"word":"Winterzeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Winterhalbjahr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"\xfcberwintern"}]},{"id":490,"question":"woman","answers":[{"word":"Frau","gender":"f"},{"word":"Weib","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Weibsbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Frauenzimmer","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"weiblich"}]},{"id":491,"question":"wood","answers":[{"word":"Holz","gender":"n"},{"word":"Wald","gender":"m"},{"word":"Geh\xf6lz","gender":"n"}]},{"id":492,"question":"wool","answers":[{"word":"Wolle","gender":"f"}]},{"id":493,"question":"word","answers":[{"word":"Wort","gender":"n"},{"word":"Begriff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Nachricht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Datenwort","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Versprechen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vokabel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Losungswort","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Maschinenwort","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) formulieren"},{"word":"ausdr\xfccken"},{"word":"etw.Akk in Worte fassen","l":1}]},{"id":494,"question":"work","answers":[{"word":"Arbeit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Werk","gender":"n"},{"word":"Arbeitsplatz","gender":"m"},{"word":"T\xe4tigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wirken","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schaffen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bearbeitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Besch\xe4ftigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Oeuvre","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Opus","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"funktionieren"},{"word":"bearbeiten"},{"word":"wirken"},{"word":"laufen"},{"word":"t\xe4tig sein"},{"word":"kneten"},{"word":"schaffen","l":1},{"word":"werken","l":1},{"word":"ziehen","l":1},{"word":"gelingen","l":1},{"word":"klappen","l":1},{"word":"anschlagen","l":1},{"word":"hinhauen","l":1},{"word":"werkt\xe4tig sein","l":1},{"word":"berufst\xe4tig sein","l":1}]},{"id":495,"question":"wound","answers":[{"word":"Wunde","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kr\xe4nkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Blessur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verwundung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"aufgezogen"},{"word":"aufgewickelt","l":1},{"word":"gewickelt","l":1},{"word":"gewunden","l":1},{"word":"gedreht","l":1},{"word":"gekurbelt","l":1},{"word":"gespult","l":1},{"word":"verwunden","l":1},{"word":"verletzen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk aufwickeln"},{"word":"aufziehen"},{"word":"sichAkk winden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk kurbeln","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk drehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk spulen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk schlingen","l":1},{"word":"rollen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abspulen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk aufspulen","l":1}]},{"id":496,"question":"writing","answers":[{"word":"Schreiben","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schrift","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schreibe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schriftzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abfassung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schriftstellerei","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"schreiben"},{"word":"etw.Akk schreiben"},{"word":"verfassen"},{"word":"anschreiben"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) abfassen"},{"word":"texten","l":1},{"word":"dichten","l":1}]},{"id":497,"question":"year","answers":[{"word":"Jahr","gender":"n"},{"word":"Jahrgang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Klasse","gender":"f"},{"word":"Jahreszahl","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Jg.","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"J\xe4hrchen","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":498,"question":"angle","answers":[{"word":"Winkel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Blickwinkel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Standpunkt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gesichtspunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kante","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Perspektive","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesichtswinkel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"angeln"}]},{"id":499,"question":"ant","answers":[{"word":"Ameise","gender":"f"}]},{"id":500,"question":"apple","answers":[{"word":"Apfel","gender":"m"}]},{"id":501,"question":"arch","answers":[{"word":"Bogen","gender":"m"},{"word":"W\xf6lbung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gew\xf6lbe","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Br\xfcckenbogen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bogenform","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Torbogen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bogengew\xf6lbe","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Fu\xdfr\xfccken","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gew\xf6lbebogen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk kr\xfcmmen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk kr\xfcmmen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk w\xf6lben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk beugen","l":1},{"word":"zylindrisch biegen","l":1},{"word":"schelmisch","l":1},{"word":"schalkhaft","l":1},{"word":"verschmitzt","l":1},{"word":"schurkisch","l":1}]},{"id":502,"question":"arm","answers":[{"word":"Arm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Waffe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Armlehne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xc4rmel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zweig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Halterung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Quertr\xe4ger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abzweigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"befestigen","l":1},{"word":"aufr\xfcsten","l":1},{"word":"bewaffnen","l":1},{"word":"r\xfcsten","l":1},{"word":"best\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"mit Waffen ausr\xfcsten","l":1}]},{"id":503,"question":"army","answers":[{"word":"Armee","gender":"f"},{"word":"Heer","gender":"n"},{"word":"Milit\xe4r","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Streitmacht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Landstreitkr\xe4fte","l":1},{"word":"Kommiss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Barras","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":504,"question":"baby","answers":[{"word":"Baby","gender":"n"},{"word":"Kind","gender":"n"},{"word":"S\xe4ugling","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kleinkind","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kindlein","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"S\xfc\xdfer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"S\xfc\xdfe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wickelkind","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schnuckel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schnuckelchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"klein"}]},{"id":505,"question":"bag","answers":[{"word":"Tasche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Beutel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sack","gender":"m"},{"word":"T\xfcte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Tragetasche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sackerl","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Handtasche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Koffer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Reisetasche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Jagdbeute","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Balg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"einsacken","l":1},{"word":"erbeuten","l":1},{"word":"erlegen","l":1},{"word":"in T\xfcten oder S\xe4cken abf\xfcllen","l":1}]},{"id":506,"question":"ball","answers":[{"word":"Ball","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kugel","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ballen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spielball","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kn\xe4uel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tanzball","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leder","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tanz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tanzabend","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tanzfest","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Luppe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bausch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk zu Kugeln formen","l":1},{"word":"bumsen","l":1}]},{"id":507,"question":"band","answers":[{"word":"Band","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gruppe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kapelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Frequenzband","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Truppe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Musikkapelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Frequenzbereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bande","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ring","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bandbreite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Orchester","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Musikgruppe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Streifen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schar","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Balken","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leiste","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Trupp","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kolonne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reifen","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":508,"question":"basin","answers":[{"word":"Waschbecken","gender":"n"},{"word":"Becken","gender":"n"},{"word":"Talkessel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Hafenbecken","gender":"n"},{"word":"Bassin","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sch\xfcssel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kessel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Talbecken","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schale","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wassereinzugsgebiet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wasserbeh\xe4lter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Innenhafen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stromgebiet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Brunnenbecken","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Talmulde","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":509,"question":"basket","answers":[{"word":"Korb","gender":"m"},{"word":"K\xf6rbchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Teller","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ballongondel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gondel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Idiot","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bl\xf6dmann","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":510,"question":"bath","answers":[{"word":"Bad","gender":"n"},{"word":"Badewanne","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wanne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wannenbad","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vollbad","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kurort","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"baden"}]},{"id":511,"question":"bed","answers":[{"word":"Bett","gender":"n"},{"word":"Beet","gender":"n"},{"word":"Grund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lager","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Koje","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ladefl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sohle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fl\xf6z","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fl\xf6z","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Blumenbeet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lagerstatt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bank","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Falle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auflagefl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lagerst\xe4tte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Liegestatt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bettstatt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"betten","l":1},{"word":"setzen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. ins Bett legen","l":1}]},{"id":512,"question":"bee","answers":[{"word":"Biene","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wettbewerb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Imme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kr\xe4nzchen","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":513,"question":"bell","answers":[{"word":"Glocke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Klingel","gender":"f"},{"word":"L\xe4ute","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gl\xf6ckchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schallbecher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schalltrichter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gong","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"L\xe4utewerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Klingelzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kelch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bimmel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Brunftschrei","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verschlusskegel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"r\xf6hren"}]},{"id":514,"question":"berry","answers":[{"word":"Beere","gender":"f"},{"word":"Beeren sammeln","l":1},{"word":"Beeren tragen","l":1}]},{"id":515,"question":"bird","answers":[{"word":"Vogel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Federball","gender":"m"},{"word":"Puppe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Braut","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tussi","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mieze","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":516,"question":"blade","answers":[{"word":"Klinge","gender":"f"},{"word":"Messer","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schneide","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fl\xfcgel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Halm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Blatt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schaufel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schwert","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Stahl","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schaufelblatt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Axtklinge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lamelle einer Jalousie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fl\xfcgelblatt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"inlinen","l":1},{"word":"rollerskaten","l":1},{"word":"inline-skaten","l":1}]},{"id":517,"question":"board","answers":[{"word":"Bord","gender":"n"},{"word":"Vorstand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Brett","gender":"n"},{"word":"Verpflegung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Tafel","gender":"f"},{"word":"Spielbrett","gender":"n"},{"word":"Beh\xf6rde","gender":"f"},{"word":"Platine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Platte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Karton","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rat","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausschuss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gremium","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Baugruppe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kost","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Deck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Diele","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kommission","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Brettchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tisch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Planke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anschlagtafel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bande","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Steckkarte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schultafel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wandtafel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"an Bord gehen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) besteigen"},{"word":"entern"},{"word":"dielen","l":1},{"word":"verschalen","l":1},{"word":"Internatssch\xfcler sein","l":1}]},{"id":518,"question":"boat","answers":[{"word":"Boot","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schiff","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kahn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schiffchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dampfer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Barke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xe4hrschiff","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Boot fahren"}]},{"id":519,"question":"bone","answers":[{"word":"Knochen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bein","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gr\xe4te","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"entbeinen","l":1}]},{"id":520,"question":"book","answers":[{"word":"Buch","gender":"n"},{"word":"Heft","gender":"n"},{"word":"Titel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gesang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Textbuch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schm\xf6ker","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Block","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Heftchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"etw.Akk buchen"},{"word":"etw.Akk reservieren"},{"word":"etw.Akk bestellen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) eintragen","l":1},{"word":"verhaften","l":1},{"word":"jdn. anmelden","l":1},{"word":"jdm. einen Strafzettel verpassen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk vorbestellen","l":1}]},{"id":521,"question":"boot","answers":[{"word":"etw.Akk booten"},{"word":"booten"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) hochfahren"},{"word":"etw.Akk starten","l":1},{"word":"(jdn./etw.Akk) treten","l":1},{"word":"Stiefel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Start","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Faltenbalg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Muffe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schreckschraube","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rausschmiss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kofferraum","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gep\xe4ckraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"obendrein"}]},{"id":522,"question":"bottle","answers":[{"word":"Flasche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fl\xe4schchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Flakon","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Milchflasche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schoppen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ente","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mumm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Krug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pulle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Buddel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"f\xfcllen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk in Flaschen f\xfcllen","l":1},{"word":"abziehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk einmachen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abf\xfcllen","l":1},{"word":"einwecken","l":1}]},{"id":523,"question":"box","answers":[{"word":"Kasten","gender":"m"},{"word":"Feld","gender":"n"},{"word":"Kiste","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schachtel","gender":"f"},{"word":"K\xe4stchen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Karton","gender":"m"},{"word":"Dose","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geh\xe4use","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verpackung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beh\xe4lter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Buchsbaum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Loge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"B\xfcchse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rechteck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kassette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rubrik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Glotze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Buchs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Beh\xe4ltnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Theaterloge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Glotzkiste","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sarg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"boxen"},{"word":"verpacken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk packen","l":1}]},{"id":524,"question":"boy","answers":[{"word":"Junge","gender":"m"},{"word":"Knabe","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Boy","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bub","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bube","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Laufbursche","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bursche","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bengel","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":525,"question":"brain","answers":[{"word":"Gehirn","gender":"n"},{"word":"Hirn","gender":"n"},{"word":"Verstand","gender":"m"},{"word":"Grips","gender":"m"},{"word":"K\xf6pfchen","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":526,"question":"brake","answers":[{"word":"Bremse","gender":"f"},{"word":"Farn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterholz","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Radschuh","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dickicht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"bremsen"},{"word":"abbremsen"}]},{"id":527,"question":"branch","answers":[{"word":"Branche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Niederlassung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Filiale","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zweig","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zweigstelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ast","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zweigniederlassung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abzweig","gender":"m"},{"word":"Seitenarm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Arm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Au\xdfenstelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verzweigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sparte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsstelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zweigwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dependance","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Teilgebiet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Expositur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abzweigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Filialbetrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Nebenstelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zweigbetrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Handelszweig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ableger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sprung","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Waffengattung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Filialgesch\xe4ft","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gezweig","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gabelung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kontor","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zweiggesch\xe4ft","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schenkel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterabteilung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Nebenarm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"springen","l":1},{"word":"abspringen","l":1},{"word":"Zweige treiben","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk gabeln","l":1}]},{"id":528,"question":"brick","answers":[{"word":"Ziegel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Backstein","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ziegelstein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klinker","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Baustein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Mauerziegel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tonziegel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klotz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pfundskerl","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"prima Kumpel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Mauerstein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"ziegelrot"}]},{"id":529,"question":"bridge","answers":[{"word":"Br\xfccke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Steg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Br\xfcckenbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kommandobr\xfccke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xdcberleitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einschraubbr\xfccke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sattel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xfcberbr\xfccken"},{"word":"eine Br\xfccke schlagen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk \xfcberwinden","l":1},{"word":"eine Br\xfccke errichten","l":1}]},{"id":530,"question":"brush","answers":[{"word":"Pinsel","gender":"m"},{"word":"B\xfcrste","gender":"f"},{"word":"Unterholz","gender":"n"},{"word":"Besen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gestr\xfcpp","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dickicht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Buschwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Strauchwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zusammensto\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lunte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schwanz des Fuchses","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) b\xfcrsten"},{"word":"streifen"},{"word":"abb\xfcrsten","l":1},{"word":"ausb\xfcrsten","l":1},{"word":"fegen","l":1},{"word":"kehren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk durchb\xfcrsten","l":1}]},{"id":531,"question":"bucket","answers":[{"word":"Eimer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schaufel","gender":"f"},{"word":"K\xfcbel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Beh\xe4lter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wassereimer","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":532,"question":"bulb","answers":[{"word":"Gl\xfchbirne","gender":"f"},{"word":"Birne","gender":"f"},{"word":"Lampe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zwiebel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gl\xfchlampe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kolben","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Knolle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Glaskolben","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bulbus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Blumenknolle","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":533,"question":"button","answers":[{"word":"Taste","gender":"f"},{"word":"Button","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schaltfl\xe4che","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schalter","gender":"m"},{"word":"Knopf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Druckknopf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Taster","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schaltknopf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"kn\xf6pfen","l":1},{"word":"zukn\xf6pfen","l":1}]},{"id":534,"question":"cake","answers":[{"word":"Kuchen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Torte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Teilchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Riegel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klumpen bilden","l":1},{"word":"sintern","l":1},{"word":"zusammenbacken","l":1}]},{"id":535,"question":"camera","answers":[{"word":"Kamera","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fotoapparat","gender":"m"},{"word":"Richterzimmer","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gew\xf6lbe","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":536,"question":"card","answers":[{"word":"Karte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Visitenkarte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Spielkarte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausweis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Steckkarte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Karton","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leiterplatte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pappe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Karde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Steckplatine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftskarte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Platine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Baugruppe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lochkarte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kard\xe4tsche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kratze","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":537,"question":"cart","answers":[{"word":"Einkaufswagen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Wagen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Karren","gender":"m"},{"word":"Karre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fuhrwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Rollwagen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leiterwagen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pferdewagen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Laufwagen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"transportieren"},{"word":"bef\xf6rdern"},{"word":"karren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk schleppen","l":1}]},{"id":538,"question":"carriage","answers":[{"word":"Bef\xf6rderung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kutsche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wagen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Waggon","gender":"m"},{"word":"Transport","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schlitten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fahrgestell","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Laufwagen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lafette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fracht","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Transportkosten","l":1},{"word":"Rollgeld","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anfuhr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Personenwagen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"G\xfctertransport","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Eisenbahnwagen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gabelschlitten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fuhrlohn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abfuhr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schreibwagen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schreibmaschinenwagen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wagenvorschub","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zuggraben","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fuhrwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Haltung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Frachtgeb\xfchr","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":539,"question":"cat","answers":[{"word":"Katze","gender":"f"},{"word":"Katalysator","gender":"m"},{"word":"Hauskatze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kat","gender":"m"}]},{"id":540,"question":"chain","answers":[{"word":"Kette","gender":"f"},{"word":"Handelskette","gender":"f"},{"word":"Verkettung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Reihe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einzelhandelskette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Knotenkette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fessel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Absperrkette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schlange","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"ketten"},{"word":"anketten"},{"word":"verbinden","l":1},{"word":"verketten","l":1}]},{"id":541,"question":"cheese","answers":[{"word":"K\xe4se","gender":"m"}]},{"id":542,"question":"chest","answers":[{"word":"Brust","gender":"f"},{"word":"Brustkorb","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kiste","gender":"f"},{"word":"Truhe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kasten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lade","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Koffer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Busen","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":543,"question":"chin","answers":[{"word":"Kinn","gender":"n"}]},{"id":544,"question":"church","answers":[{"word":"Kirche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kirchengemeinde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kirchenbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gotteshaus","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"kirchlich"}]},{"id":545,"question":"circle","answers":[{"word":"Kreis","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kreislauf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zirkel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Runde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Personenkreis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gesellschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kreisform","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ring","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zyklus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kreislinie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Felge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kranz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ronde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Soziet\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"kreisen","l":1},{"word":"umkreisen","l":1},{"word":"umfahren","l":1},{"word":"kurven","l":1},{"word":"Warteschleifen drehen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk um etw.Akk bewegen","l":1}]},{"id":546,"question":"clock","answers":[{"word":"Uhr","gender":"f"},{"word":"Takt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wanduhr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Taktrate","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeituhr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Taktgeber","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Taktfrequenz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Taktgenerator","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Turmuhr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stoppuhr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pusteblume","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Taxameter","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"z\xe4hlen","l":1},{"word":"stoppen","l":1},{"word":"die Zeit nehmen","l":1},{"word":"die Zeit messen","l":1}]},{"id":547,"question":"cloud","answers":[{"word":"Wolke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schwaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"W\xf6lkchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schatten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tr\xfcbung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"tr\xfcben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk vernebeln","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk bew\xf6lken","l":1}]},{"id":548,"question":"coat","answers":[{"word":"Mantel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Fell","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schicht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Jacke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Belag","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kittel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Beschichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Haarkleid","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anstrich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xdcberzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pelz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Federkleid","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bedeckung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"H\xfclle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Jackett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Decke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reitfrack","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"beschichten"},{"word":"etw.Akk lackieren"},{"word":"\xfcberziehen"},{"word":"streichen","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberstreichen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk umh\xfcllen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bedecken","l":1},{"word":"anstreichen","l":1},{"word":"verg\xfcten","l":1},{"word":"kaschieren","l":1},{"word":"belegen","l":1},{"word":"ummanteln","l":1}]},{"id":549,"question":"collar","answers":[{"word":"Kragen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Halsband","gender":"n"},{"word":"Bund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Manschette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hals","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kummet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Halskragen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kollier","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Reif","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schulter","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":550,"question":"comb","answers":[{"word":"Kamm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Wabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weberkamm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Messrechen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"durchforsten"},{"word":"durchk\xe4mmen"},{"word":"ausk\xe4mmen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) k\xe4mmen","l":1},{"word":"abk\xe4mmen","l":1}]},{"id":551,"question":"cord","answers":[{"word":"Schnur","gender":"f"},{"word":"Cord","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kordel","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kabel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Leine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Band","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Seil","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Strick","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Strang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kord","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"gerippter Stoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bindfaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Litze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Raumma\xdf f\xfcr Holz","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Cordsamt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klafter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Leitungsschnur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"binden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk mit Schnur festmachen","l":1},{"word":"verschn\xfcren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zuschn\xfcren","l":1}]},{"id":552,"question":"cow","answers":[{"word":"Kuh","gender":"f"},{"word":"Rind","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zicke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weibsst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zimtzicke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"jdn. bedrohen","l":1},{"word":"einsch\xfcchtern","l":1}]},{"id":553,"question":"cup","answers":[{"word":"Tasse","gender":"f"},{"word":"Becher","gender":"m"},{"word":"Pokal","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kelch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schale","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"K\xf6rbchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Napf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Haferl","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Au\xdfenring","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abendmahlskelch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dichtungshalter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sportpokal","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk schr\xf6pfen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk umschlie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"einlochen","l":1}]},{"id":554,"question":"curtain","answers":[{"word":"Vorhang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gardine","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schleier","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Behang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xdcbergardine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk verstecken"},{"word":"etw.Akk verh\xfcllen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verschleiern","l":1}]},{"id":555,"question":"cushion","answers":[{"word":"polstern"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) abfedern"},{"word":"etw.Akk d\xe4mpfen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk auffangen","l":1},{"word":"abmildern","l":1},{"word":"bremsen","l":1},{"word":"Kissen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Polsterung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sitzkissen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Polster","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bande","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Puffer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"D\xe4mpfer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auflager","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":556,"question":"dog","answers":[{"word":"Hund","gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xfcde","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Haushund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Mitnehmer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Knagge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auflagebock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"verfolgen"}]},{"id":557,"question":"door","answers":[{"word":"T\xfcr","gender":"f"},{"word":"Tor","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"T\xfcre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Klappe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Eingangst\xfcr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"T\xfcrfl\xfcgel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fl\xfcgel","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":558,"question":"drain","answers":[{"word":"Drain","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kanal","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abfluss","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abflie\xdfen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Austrocknen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ablauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Belastung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abwasserkanal","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rinne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Entw\xe4ssern","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Abflussrohr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ableitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ablass","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abzugskanal","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gully","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausguss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ablassleitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Senke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"allm\xe4hliche Ersch\xf6pfung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gosse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kanalschacht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Entw\xe4sserungsgraben","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abwasserleitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schacht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ablasskanal","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abflussgraben","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abflussrinne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dole","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"entleeren"},{"word":"ablassen"},{"word":"ablaufen"},{"word":"ableiten","l":1},{"word":"abtropfen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abgie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"weichen","l":1},{"word":"leeren","l":1},{"word":"auslaufen","l":1},{"word":"trockenlegen","l":1},{"word":"drainieren","l":1},{"word":"entw\xe4ssern","l":1},{"word":"leerlaufen lassen","l":1},{"word":"abpumpen","l":1},{"word":"dr\xe4nieren","l":1},{"word":"aufzehren","l":1}]},{"id":559,"question":"drawer","answers":[{"word":"Schublade","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bezieher","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schubkasten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lade","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeichner","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aussteller","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schubfach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Einschub","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Trassant","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schub","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":560,"question":"dress","answers":[{"word":"Dress","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kleid","gender":"n"},{"word":"Tracht","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kleidung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kluft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"kleiden"},{"word":"abrichten"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) verbinden","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk anziehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zubereiten","l":1},{"word":"dekorieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk anrichten","l":1},{"word":"ankleiden","l":1},{"word":"jdn. einkleiden","l":1},{"word":"zurichten","l":1},{"word":"ausnehmen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk bekleiden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk anmachen","l":1},{"word":"dressieren","l":1},{"word":"aufbereiten","l":1}]},{"id":561,"question":"drop","answers":[{"word":"Tropfen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Fallen","gender":"n"},{"word":"R\xfcckgang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Fall","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abfall","gender":"m"},{"word":"Spannungsabfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sinken","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Abwurf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Senkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abnahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Absenkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einbruch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sturz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"H\xf6henunterschied","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gef\xe4lle","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Talfahrt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schl\xfcckchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wasserspiegeldifferenz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wasserspiegelunterschied","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"tropfen"},{"word":"fallen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) fallen lassen"},{"word":"sinken"},{"word":"ablegen"},{"word":"nachlassen"},{"word":"weglassen"},{"word":"streichen"},{"word":"zusammenbrechen"},{"word":"hinwerfen"},{"word":"absinken","l":1},{"word":"abnehmen","l":1},{"word":"verlieren","l":1},{"word":"absetzen","l":1},{"word":"zur\xfcckgehen","l":1},{"word":"umfallen","l":1},{"word":"absacken","l":1},{"word":"nachgeben","l":1},{"word":"tr\xf6pfeln","l":1},{"word":"abwerfen","l":1},{"word":"st\xfcrzen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. sausenlassen","l":1},{"word":"abflauen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. sausen lassen","l":1},{"word":"schw\xe4cher werden","l":1},{"word":"umsinken","l":1},{"word":"herabtropfen","l":1}]},{"id":562,"question":"ear","answers":[{"word":"Ohr","gender":"n"},{"word":"Geh\xf6r","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ohrmuschel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xd6se","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"L\xf6ffel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lauscher","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":563,"question":"egg","answers":[{"word":"Ei","gender":"n"},{"word":"Eizelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"aufreizen","l":1},{"word":"aufhetzen","l":1},{"word":"anstacheln","l":1}]},{"id":564,"question":"engine","answers":[{"word":"Motor","gender":"m"},{"word":"Lokomotive","gender":"f"},{"word":"Maschine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Triebwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Antriebsmaschine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kraftmaschine","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":565,"question":"eye","answers":[{"word":"Auge","gender":"n"},{"word":"\xd6se","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Nadel\xf6hr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"\xd6hr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Knospe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Triebansatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Seher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pfauenauge","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"betrachten"},{"word":"be\xe4ugen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) mustern","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) anstarren","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk kritisch betrachten","l":1},{"word":"glotzen","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk im Visier haben","l":1}]},{"id":566,"question":"face","answers":[{"word":"Gesicht","gender":"n"},{"word":"Zifferblatt","gender":"n"},{"word":"Oberfl\xe4che","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fl\xe4che","gender":"f"},{"word":"Antlitz","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Angesicht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Seite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fassade","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorderseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Miene","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Seitenfl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wand","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anschein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schriftbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bildseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"begegnen"},{"word":"gegen\xfcbertreten"},{"word":"sehen","l":1},{"word":"gehen","l":1},{"word":"gegen\xfcberstehen","l":1},{"word":"entgegensehen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. konfrontieren","l":1},{"word":"plandrehen","l":1},{"word":"gegen\xfcber sein","l":1},{"word":"Trotz bieten","l":1},{"word":"verkleiden","l":1},{"word":"verblenden","l":1},{"word":"auskleiden","l":1},{"word":"abflachen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk beschichten","l":1},{"word":"gegen\xfcberliegen","l":1},{"word":"entgegengehen","l":1}]},{"id":567,"question":"farm","answers":[{"word":"Bauernhof","gender":"m"},{"word":"Farm","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hof","gender":"m"},{"word":"Landwirtschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gutshof","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Landwirtschaftsbetrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bauerngut","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"landwirtschaftlicher Betrieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"bebauen"},{"word":"bewirtschaften"},{"word":"Landwirtschaft betreiben","l":1},{"word":"z\xfcchten","l":1},{"word":"eine Farm betreiben","l":1}]},{"id":568,"question":"feather","answers":[{"word":"Feder","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gefieder","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vogelfeder","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":569,"question":"finger","answers":[{"word":"Finger","gender":"m"},{"word":"betasten","l":1},{"word":"bef\xfchlen","l":1},{"word":"befummeln","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) befingern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk anfassen","l":1}]},{"id":570,"question":"fish","answers":[{"word":"Fisch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Fische"},{"word":"fischen"},{"word":"angeln"}]},{"id":571,"question":"flag","answers":[{"word":"Flagge","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahne","gender":"f"},{"word":"Merker","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"F\xe4hnchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Impressum","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kennzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Markierung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Platte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Steinplatte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fliese","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schwertlilie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lichtabdeckschirm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"markieren"},{"word":"kennzeichnen"},{"word":"nachlassen"},{"word":"beflaggen","l":1},{"word":"erlahmen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk mit Steinplatten belegen","l":1},{"word":"Merker setzen","l":1},{"word":"stocken","l":1},{"word":"abflauen","l":1},{"word":"erschlaffen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk fliesen","l":1},{"word":"m\xfcde werden","l":1},{"word":"welken","l":1},{"word":"abbauen","l":1}]},{"id":572,"question":"floor","answers":[{"word":"Boden","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stock","gender":"m"},{"word":"Etage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fu\xdfboden","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stockwerk","gender":"n"},{"word":"Geschoss","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Grund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Untergrenze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sohle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mindestpreis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Mindestkurs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Plenarsaal","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schiffsboden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"umlegen"},{"word":"jdn. umhauen"},{"word":"jdn. verbl\xfcffen"}]},{"id":573,"question":"fly","answers":[{"word":"fliegen"},{"word":"flattern"},{"word":"verfliegen","l":1},{"word":"fl\xfcchten","l":1},{"word":"spr\xfchen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk befliegen","l":1},{"word":"stieben","l":1},{"word":"fliehen","l":1},{"word":"Fliege","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hosenschlitz","gender":"m"},{"word":"\xdcberzelt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schlitz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hosenlatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hosenstall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"gerissen","l":1},{"word":"clever","l":1},{"word":"gewieft","l":1},{"word":"flink","l":1}]},{"id":574,"question":"foot","answers":[{"word":"Fu\xdf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bein","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Fu\xdfende","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tritt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Standfu\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Basis","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fu\xdfpunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Standvorrichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Versfu\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Haxe","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":575,"question":"fork","answers":[{"word":"Gabel","gender":"f"},{"word":"Weggabelung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abzweigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gabelung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Radgabel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stra\xdfengabelung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gabelst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verzweigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"gabeln"},{"word":"sichAkk teilen","l":1},{"word":"abzweigen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk aufspalten","l":1},{"word":"wenden","l":1}]},{"id":576,"question":"fowl","answers":[{"word":"Gefl\xfcgel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Federvieh","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":577,"question":"frame","answers":[{"word":"rahmen"},{"word":"etw.Akk rahmen"},{"word":"formulieren"},{"word":"entwerfen"},{"word":"bilden","l":1},{"word":"formen","l":1},{"word":"entwickeln","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) umrahmen","l":1},{"word":"einrahmen","l":1},{"word":"gestalten","l":1},{"word":"jdn. reinlegen","l":1},{"word":"zusammensetzen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. f\xe4lschlich bezichtigen","l":1},{"word":"ausarbeiten","l":1},{"word":"Rahmen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Einzelbild","gender":"n"},{"word":"Fassung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Frame","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Figur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gestell","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zarge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ger\xfcst","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gerippe","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Untergestell","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"B\xfcgel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gest\xe4nge","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Spant","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Daten\xfcbertragungsblock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vollbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gestalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Statur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fr\xfchbeet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"K\xf6rperbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Erhebungsgrundlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rasterbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Rahmentragwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bildfeld","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":578,"question":"garden","answers":[{"word":"Garten","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gartenanlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hausgarten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"g\xe4rtnern"}]},{"id":579,"question":"girl","answers":[{"word":"M\xe4dchen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Tochter","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Girl","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"M\xe4del","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Fr\xe4ulein","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tussi","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Braut","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dirndl","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":580,"question":"glove","answers":[{"word":"Handschuh","gender":"m"}]},{"id":581,"question":"goat","answers":[{"word":"Ziege","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gei\xdf","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":582,"question":"gun","answers":[{"word":"Pistole","gender":"f"},{"word":"Waffe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gewehr","gender":"n"},{"word":"Kanone","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schusswaffe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Flinte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Knarre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xfctz","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Revolver","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schie\xdfgewehr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"B\xfcchse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rohrwaffe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Feuerwaffe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ballermann","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":583,"question":"hair","answers":[{"word":"Haar","gender":"n"},{"word":"Haare"},{"word":"Haarwuchs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Haupthaar","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kopfhaar","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":584,"question":"hammer","answers":[{"word":"Hammer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schl\xe4gel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hahn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Malleus","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"h\xe4mmern"}]},{"id":585,"question":"hand","answers":[{"word":"Hand","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeiger","gender":"m"},{"word":"Handschrift","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Blatt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schriftzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Arbeiter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Uhrzeiger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Arbeitskraft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xfcberreichen"},{"word":"einh\xe4ndigen","l":1},{"word":"her\xfcberreichen","l":1},{"word":"hinreichen","l":1}]},{"id":586,"question":"hat","answers":[{"word":"Hut","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kappe","gender":"f"}]},{"id":587,"question":"head","answers":[{"word":"Kopf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Leiter","gender":"m"},{"word":"Chef","gender":"m"},{"word":"Leitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spitze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leiterin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Haupt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Oberhaupt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Direktor","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Toilette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Magnetkopf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sch\xe4del","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Chefin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorsitzende","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorsitzender","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kopfende","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vorsteher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Landspitze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xfchrung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xfchrer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Obmann","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Heimleiterin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"St\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kap","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Titel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schaumkrone","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fu\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Blume","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"oberstes Teil","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wipfel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Baumwipfel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Obm\xe4nnin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gipfel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Obfrau","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"oberes Ende","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kesselboden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Boss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Heimleiter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Eiterpfropf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"F\xfchrerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"steuern"},{"word":"k\xf6pfen"},{"word":"etw.Akk anf\xfchren"},{"word":"an der Spitze von etw.Dat stehen","l":1},{"word":"lenken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Dat vorstehen","l":1},{"word":"stauchen","l":1}]},{"id":588,"question":"heart","answers":[{"word":"Herz","gender":"n"},{"word":"Herzst\xfcck","gender":"n"},{"word":"Zentrum","gender":"n"},{"word":"Kern","gender":"m"},{"word":"Mittelpunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Brust","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Innerstes","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":589,"question":"hook","answers":[{"word":"Haken","gender":"m"},{"word":"Hook","gender":"m"},{"word":"H\xe4kchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aufh\xe4nger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sichel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk haken"},{"word":"etw.Akk anhaken","l":1},{"word":"festhaken","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk kr\xfcmmen","l":1},{"word":"sichDat jdn. angeln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk klauen"}]},{"id":590,"question":"horn","answers":[{"word":"Horn","gender":"n"},{"word":"Hupe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sonotrode","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Signalhorn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schalltrichter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"F\xfchler","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Auflaufhorn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"h\xf6ren"},{"word":"anh\xf6ren"},{"word":"etw.Akk erfahren"},{"word":"erh\xf6ren"},{"word":"Bescheid bekommen"}]},{"id":591,"question":"horse","answers":[{"word":"Pferd","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ross","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gaul","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sprungpferd","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bock","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":592,"question":"hospital","answers":[{"word":"Krankenhaus","gender":"n"},{"word":"Hospital","gender":"n"},{"word":"Klinik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spital","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lazarett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Krankenanstalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Krankenrevier","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":593,"question":"house","answers":[{"word":"Haus","gender":"n"},{"word":"Familie","gender":"f"},{"word":"Geschlecht","gender":"n"},{"word":"Geb\xe4ude","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"unterbringen"},{"word":"aufnehmen","l":1},{"word":"beherbergen","l":1}]},{"id":594,"question":"island","answers":[{"word":"Insel","gender":"f"}]},{"id":595,"question":"jewel","answers":[{"word":"Juwel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schmuckst\xfcck","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schmuck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kleinod","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Edelstein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stein","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":596,"question":"kettle","answers":[{"word":"Wasserkocher","gender":"m"},{"word":"Wasserkessel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kessel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Teekessel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kochkessel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Siedekessel","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":597,"question":"key","answers":[{"word":"Schl\xfcssel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Taste","gender":"f"},{"word":"Tonart","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Passfeder","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Klappe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Legende","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeichenerkl\xe4rung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Korallenriff","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"kleine Insel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Chiffre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"wichtig"},{"word":"wesentlich"},{"word":"eingeben"},{"word":"tippen"},{"word":"eintasten","l":1}]},{"id":598,"question":"knee","answers":[{"word":"Knie","gender":"n"}]},{"id":599,"question":"knife","answers":[{"word":"Messer","gender":"n"}]},{"id":600,"question":"knot","answers":[{"word":"Knoten","gender":"m"},{"word":"Verwachsung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stek","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Knorren","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Krawattenknoten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"knoten"},{"word":"sichAkk verknoten","l":1},{"word":"verknoten","l":1},{"word":"einen Knoten machen","l":1},{"word":"einen Knoten binden","l":1},{"word":"verschn\xfcren","l":1},{"word":"zuknoten","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk verkrampfen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk verwirren","l":1},{"word":"verkn\xfcpfen","l":1},{"word":"kn\xfcpfen","l":1}]},{"id":601,"question":"leaf","answers":[{"word":"Blatt","gender":"n"},{"word":"T\xfcrblatt","gender":"n"},{"word":"Fl\xfcgel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Platte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tischplatte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Baumblatt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Doppelseite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bl\xe4ttchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"T\xfcrfl\xfcgel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Laubblatt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lamelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Folie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Klappe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ausziehplatte","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":602,"question":"leg","answers":[{"word":"Etappe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schenkel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Abschnitt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Teilstrecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Strecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schaft","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Flugstrecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lauf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Teilst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kratzfu\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Keule","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Programmzweig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schl\xf6gel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Haxe","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":603,"question":"library","answers":[{"word":"Bibliothek","gender":"f"},{"word":"B\xfccherei","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sammlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hausbibliothek","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Programmbibliothek","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Buchreihe","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":604,"question":"line","answers":[{"word":"Linie","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeile","gender":"f"},{"word":"Serie","gender":"f"},{"word":"Leitung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Produktlinie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Strecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verbindung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grenze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Strich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Richtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schnur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bahnstrecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Band","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Trasse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftszweig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Branche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Eisenbahnstrecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anschluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Route","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kurs","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"W\xe4scheleine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Richtschnur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Falte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Artikel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Grenzlinie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kolonne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vers","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schienenstrang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spalier","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gleis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Geschlechterfolge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reihe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schlange","gender":"f"},{"word":"Warteschlange","gender":"f"},{"word":"s\xe4umen"},{"word":"auskleiden"},{"word":"auslegen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) f\xfcttern"},{"word":"ausschlagen","l":1},{"word":"ums\xe4umen","l":1},{"word":"abf\xfcttern","l":1},{"word":"kaschieren","l":1},{"word":"ausf\xfcttern","l":1}]},{"id":605,"question":"lip","answers":[{"word":"Lippe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Rand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lefze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unversch\xe4mtheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"T\xfclle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schnauze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Randabschluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schnabel","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":606,"question":"lock","answers":[{"word":"Schloss","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schleuse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verschluss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sperre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"T\xfcrschloss","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Verriegelung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Haarlocke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Riegel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Locke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wendekreis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Siel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fesselgriff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk sperren"},{"word":"verriegeln"},{"word":"abschlie\xdfen"},{"word":"blockieren"},{"word":"verschlie\xdfen"},{"word":"absperren"},{"word":"feststellen"},{"word":"schlie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"zuschlie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"schleusen","l":1},{"word":"arretieren","l":1},{"word":"sichern","l":1},{"word":"einrasten","l":1},{"word":"zusperren","l":1}]},{"id":607,"question":"map","answers":[{"word":"Karte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Landkarte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Plan","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stadtplan","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xdcbersichtskarte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lageplan","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Abbildung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"abbilden"},{"word":"etw.Akk kartieren"},{"word":"entwerfen"},{"word":"planen"},{"word":"kartographieren","l":1},{"word":"kartografieren","l":1},{"word":"ausarbeiten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk einzeichnen","l":1},{"word":"von etw.Dat eine Karte anfertigen","l":1}]},{"id":608,"question":"match","answers":[{"word":"passen"},{"word":"\xfcbereinstimmen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) entsprechen"},{"word":"zusammenpassen"},{"word":"zuordnen"},{"word":"gleich sein"},{"word":"etw.Akk zusammenf\xfcgen"},{"word":"abstimmen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) abgleichen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) anpassen","l":1},{"word":"vergleichen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk decken","l":1},{"word":"paaren","l":1},{"word":"gleichkommen","l":1},{"word":"jdm. ebenb\xfcrtig sein","l":1},{"word":"angleichen","l":1},{"word":"Match","gender":"n"},{"word":"Spiel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Streichholz","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gegenst\xfcck","gender":"n"},{"word":"Wettkampf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Partie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kampf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pendant","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Entsprechung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Z\xfcndholz","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lunte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"dazu passende Person","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"zusammenpassendes Paar","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"dazu passende Sache","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wettspiel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ebenbild","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":609,"question":"monkey","answers":[{"word":"Affe","gender":"m"},{"word":"Rammb\xe4r","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rammklotz","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":610,"question":"moon","answers":[{"word":"Mond","gender":"m"},{"word":"mit offenen Augen schlafen","l":1}]},{"id":611,"question":"mouth","answers":[{"word":"Mund","gender":"m"},{"word":"Maul","gender":"n"},{"word":"M\xfcndung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xd6ffnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Eingang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klappe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einm\xfcndung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schnauze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Mundloch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kopf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rachen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ventilmund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ventileingang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gosche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"\xc4ser","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Mundwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":612,"question":"muscle","answers":[{"word":"Muskel","gender":"m"},{"word":"St\xe4rke","gender":"f"}]},{"id":613,"question":"nail","answers":[{"word":"Nagel","gender":"m"},{"word":"nageln","l":1},{"word":"jdn. festnageln","l":1},{"word":"annageln","l":1}]},{"id":614,"question":"neck","answers":[{"word":"Hals","gender":"m"},{"word":"Nacken","gender":"m"},{"word":"Genick","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ausschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Halsst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zapfen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Walzenhals","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kamm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"schmusen"},{"word":"knutschen","l":1}]},{"id":615,"question":"needle","answers":[{"word":"Nadel","gender":"f"},{"word":"N\xe4hnadel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeiger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xe4rgern","l":1},{"word":"sticheln","l":1}]},{"id":616,"question":"nerve","answers":[{"word":"Nerv","gender":"m"},{"word":"Mut","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Nervenbahn","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Frechheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Unversch\xe4mtheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"kr\xe4ftigen","l":1},{"word":"ermutigen","l":1},{"word":"st\xe4rken","l":1}]},{"id":617,"question":"net","answers":[{"word":"Netz","gender":"n"},{"word":"Netto","gender":"n"},{"word":"Internet","gender":"n"},{"word":"T\xfcll","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fangnetz","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Netzgewebe","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Netzball","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"netto"},{"word":"netzartig"},{"word":"vernetzen","l":1},{"word":"saldieren","l":1},{"word":"netto abwerfen","l":1},{"word":"netto verdienen","l":1},{"word":"einbringen","l":1}]},{"id":618,"question":"nose","answers":[{"word":"Nase","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bug","gender":"m"},{"word":"Riecher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bukett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sp\xfcrnase","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sp\xfcrsinn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schnauze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesp\xfcr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sporn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schneidenecke","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":619,"question":"nut","answers":[{"word":"Mutter","gender":"f"},{"word":"Nuss","gender":"f"},{"word":"Spinner","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sattel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schraubenmutter","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Birne","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":620,"question":"office","answers":[{"word":"B\xfcro","gender":"n"},{"word":"Kanzlei","gender":"f"},{"word":"Amt","gender":"n"},{"word":"Firmensitz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Arbeitsplatz","gender":"m"},{"word":"B\xfcroraum","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sekretariat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Funktion","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beh\xf6rde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufgabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dienst","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dienststelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Amtsstube","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Amtszimmer","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ausgabe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dienstsitz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Amtssitz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kontor","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Dienstzimmer","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Handelskontor","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftszimmer","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Obliegenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Dienstraum","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":621,"question":"orange","answers":[{"word":"orange"},{"word":"orangefarben","l":1},{"word":"Orangenbaum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Apfelsine","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":622,"question":"oven","answers":[{"word":"Ofen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Backofen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Backrohr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Rohr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"R\xf6hre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bratr\xf6hre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bratofen","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":623,"question":"parcel","answers":[{"word":"Grundst\xfcck","gender":"n"},{"word":"Paket","gender":"n"},{"word":"P\xe4ckchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Parzelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sendung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Partie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Postpaket","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"verpacken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk parzellieren","l":1}]},{"id":624,"question":"pen","answers":[{"word":"Stift","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kugelschreiber","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stall","gender":"m"},{"word":"F\xfcller","gender":"m"},{"word":"Koppel","gender":"f"},{"word":"Feder","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"F\xfcllfederhalter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gehege","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Pferch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schreibstift","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schreiber","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schreibfeder","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Griffel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lichtgriffel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Knast","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"eingez\xe4untes Areal","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Koben","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"H\xfcrde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"weiblicher Schwan","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"schreiben"},{"word":"verfassen"},{"word":"einsperren","l":1}]},{"id":625,"question":"pencil","answers":[{"word":"Bleistift","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stift","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zeichenstift","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schreibstift","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"B\xfcndel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"B\xfcschel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"etw.Akk mit Bleistift zeichnen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk mit Bleistift schreiben","l":1}]},{"id":626,"question":"picture","answers":[{"word":"Bild","gender":"n"},{"word":"Foto","gender":"n"},{"word":"Abbildung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufnahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Darstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gem\xe4lde","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Fotografie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ablichtung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Formatbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) darstellen"},{"word":"beschreiben"},{"word":"zeichnen","l":1},{"word":"malen","l":1},{"word":"schildern","l":1},{"word":"abbilden","l":1}]},{"id":627,"question":"pig","answers":[{"word":"Schwein","gender":"n"},{"word":"Bulle","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ferkel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Molch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wutz","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Massel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Borstentier","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":628,"question":"pin","answers":[{"word":"PIN","gender":"f"},{"word":"Geheimzahl","gender":"f"},{"word":"pers\xf6nliche Geheimzahl","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stift","gender":"m"},{"word":"Nadel","gender":"f"},{"word":"Brosche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Kegel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kolbenbolzen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kontakt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zylinderstift","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pol","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bolzen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zapfen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Metallstift","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anstecknadel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stecknadel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Belegnagel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anschlussstift","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rei\xdfzwecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zwecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pinne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"klemmen"},{"word":"befestigen"},{"word":"anheften"},{"word":"aufstecken","l":1},{"word":"feststecken","l":1},{"word":"abstecken","l":1},{"word":"pinnen","l":1},{"word":"dr\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"dreipolig"}]},{"id":629,"question":"pipe","answers":[{"word":"Pipe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Rohr","gender":"n"},{"word":"Pfeife","gender":"f"},{"word":"Leitung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fl\xf6te","gender":"f"},{"word":"Rohrleitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schlauch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xf6hre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"R\xf6hrchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Leitungsrohr","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tabakspfeife","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rotzkocher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lunker","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Signalpfeife","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weiterleitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Saugtrichter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Trichterlunker","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tabakpfeife","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verkettungszeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"pfeifen"},{"word":"fl\xf6ten","l":1},{"word":"Rohre verlegen","l":1},{"word":"piepsen","l":1},{"word":"paspelieren","l":1},{"word":"piepsend sprechen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk in Rohren leiten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk durch ein Rohr leiten","l":1},{"word":"Fl\xf6te spielen","l":1}]},{"id":630,"question":"plane","answers":[{"word":"Ebene","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fl\xe4che","gender":"f"},{"word":"Flugzeug","gender":"n"},{"word":"Flieger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hobel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Niveau","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Platane","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Maschine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stufe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"eben"},{"word":"flach"},{"word":"zweidimensional","l":1},{"word":"hobeln"},{"word":"gleiten","l":1},{"word":"planieren","l":1},{"word":"gl\xe4tten","l":1},{"word":"segeln","l":1},{"word":"abrichten","l":1}]},{"id":631,"question":"plate","answers":[{"word":"Platte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Teller","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Platine","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tafel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grobblech","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Scheibe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bildtafel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lasche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Klischee","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lagerplatte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"R\xe4hm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bordwand","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Steintafel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"plattieren","l":1},{"word":"belegen","l":1},{"word":"ausplattieren","l":1}]},{"id":632,"question":"plough","answers":[{"word":"Pflug","gender":"m"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) pfl\xfcgen"},{"word":"ackern"},{"word":"beackern","l":1},{"word":"umpfl\xfcgen","l":1},{"word":"durchrasseln","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk durchpfl\xfcgen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk durchackern","l":1}]},{"id":633,"question":"plow","answers":[{"word":"Pflug","gender":"m"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) pfl\xfcgen","l":1},{"word":"umpfl\xfcgen","l":1},{"word":"thesaurieren","l":1},{"word":"umw\xfchlen","l":1},{"word":"ackern","l":1},{"word":"durchrasseln","l":1},{"word":"beackern","l":1},{"word":"reinvestieren","l":1},{"word":"weitermachen","l":1}]},{"id":634,"question":"pocket","answers":[{"word":"Tasche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Geldbeutel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ablagefach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kessel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ablage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aussparung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Insel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Loch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"einstreichen","l":1},{"word":"vereinnahmen","l":1},{"word":"kassieren","l":1},{"word":"in die eigene Tasche schieben","l":1},{"word":"in die Tasche stecken","l":1},{"word":"einheimsen","l":1},{"word":"sichDat etw.akk aneignen","l":1}]},{"id":635,"question":"pot","answers":[{"word":"Topf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Pot","gender":"n"},{"word":"Kochtopf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pott","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"K\xe4nnchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kanne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tiegel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gef\xe4\xdf","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kessel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Krug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Becher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wampe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"T\xf6pfchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Hasch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Pokal","gender":"m"},{"word":"Marihuana","gender":"n"},{"word":"eintopfen","l":1},{"word":"einlegen","l":1}]},{"id":636,"question":"potato","answers":[{"word":"Kartoffel","gender":"f"},{"word":"Erdapfel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Erdbirne","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":637,"question":"prison","answers":[{"word":"Gef\xe4ngnis","gender":"n"},{"word":"Kerker","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Haftanstalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Strafanstalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Justizvollzugsanstalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Knast","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zuchthaus","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":638,"question":"pump","answers":[{"word":"pumpen"},{"word":"aufpumpen"},{"word":"Pumpe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Turnschuh","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sportschuh","gender":"m"}]},{"id":639,"question":"rail","answers":[{"word":"Schiene","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bahn","gender":"f"},{"word":"Eisenbahn","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gel\xe4nder","gender":"n"},{"word":"Laufschiene","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Reling","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leiste","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stange","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gleis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Holm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"einzelne Schiene","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Eisenbahnschiene","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Umz\xe4unung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Treppengel\xe4nder","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Deckskante","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Querfries","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ralle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"schimpfen"},{"word":"wettern","l":1},{"word":"fluchen","l":1},{"word":"geifern","l":1},{"word":"schm\xe4hen","l":1}]},{"id":640,"question":"rat","answers":[{"word":"Ratte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Petze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ratz","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":641,"question":"receipt","answers":[{"word":"Erhalt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Eingang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Empfang","gender":"m"},{"word":"Quittung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Beleg","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kassenbon","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bon","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zugang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Entgegennahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Annahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Empfangsbest\xe4tigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Empfangsschein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einnahme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zettel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kassenzettel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Empfangsbescheinigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abrechnungsbeleg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Aufgabeschein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"empfangen"},{"word":"quittieren"},{"word":"den Empfang best\xe4tigen","l":1}]},{"id":642,"question":"ring","answers":[{"word":"Ring","gender":"m"},{"word":"Klingeln","gender":"n"},{"word":"Manege","gender":"f"},{"word":"L\xe4uten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kreis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fingerring","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rufzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Hof","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ringel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vereinigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Klingelzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Anruf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Telefonanruf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"klingeln"},{"word":"klingen","l":1},{"word":"schellen","l":1},{"word":"schallen","l":1},{"word":"einkreisen","l":1},{"word":"klirren","l":1},{"word":"umringen","l":1},{"word":"bimmeln","l":1},{"word":"t\xf6nen","l":1},{"word":"gellen","l":1},{"word":"erklingen","l":1},{"word":"beringen","l":1},{"word":"anrufen"},{"word":"telefonieren"}]},{"id":643,"question":"rod","answers":[{"word":"Stange","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stab","gender":"m"},{"word":"Rute","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gest\xe4nge","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"St\xe4bchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Brennstab","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kanone","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Knarre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wumme","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"lesen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) ablesen"},{"word":"vorlesen"},{"word":"deuten"},{"word":"auslesen","l":1},{"word":"nachlesen","l":1},{"word":"studieren","l":1},{"word":"er\xf6ffnen","l":1},{"word":"schm\xf6kern","l":1},{"word":"gelesen"},{"word":"eingelesen","l":1},{"word":"abgelesen","l":1},{"word":"vorgelesen","l":1},{"word":"nachgelesen","l":1},{"word":"jdm. vorlesen"}]},{"id":644,"question":"roof","answers":[{"word":"Dach","gender":"n"},{"word":"Bedachung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Hangende","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Himmel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wagendach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"First","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"\xdcberdach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) \xfcberdachen"},{"word":"dachdecken","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bedachen","l":1},{"word":"eindecken","l":1}]},{"id":645,"question":"root","answers":[{"word":"Wurzel","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ursprung","gender":"m"},{"word":"Ursache","gender":"f"},{"word":"Grund","gender":"m"},{"word":"Grundton","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stamm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Nullstelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"wurzeln"},{"word":"Wurzeln schlagen","l":1},{"word":"w\xfchlen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk bewurzeln","l":1},{"word":"rummachen","l":1},{"word":"pimpern","l":1},{"word":"ficken","l":1},{"word":"v\xf6geln","l":1},{"word":"bumsen","l":1},{"word":"poppen","l":1}]},{"id":646,"question":"sail","answers":[{"word":"fahren"},{"word":"segeln"},{"word":"etw.Akk befahren"},{"word":"auslaufen"},{"word":"besegeln","l":1},{"word":"schippern","l":1},{"word":"rauschen","l":1},{"word":"abfahren","l":1},{"word":"ablegen","l":1},{"word":"Segel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Segelschiff","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Segelt\xf6rn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Windm\xfchlenfl\xfcgel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"T\xf6rn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Segelfahrt","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":647,"question":"school","answers":[{"word":"Schule","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gruppe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Institut","gender":"n"},{"word":"Unterricht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fakult\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schulgeb\xe4ude","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schulhaus","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Fachbereich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lehranstalt","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schwarm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Penne","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"schulen"},{"word":"jdn. erziehen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. lehren","l":1},{"word":"jdn. tadeln","l":1},{"word":"schw\xe4rmen","l":1},{"word":"schulisch"}]},{"id":648,"question":"scissors","answers":[{"word":"Schere","gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk schneiden"}]},{"id":649,"question":"screw","answers":[{"word":"Schraube","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schnecke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schiffsschraube","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Propeller","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Nummer","gender":"f"},{"word":"Polizist","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bulle","gender":"m"},{"word":"schrauben"},{"word":"etw.Akk verschrauben"},{"word":"jdn. linken","l":1},{"word":"knausern","l":1},{"word":"mausen","l":1},{"word":"rummachen","l":1},{"word":"beschei\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"pimpern","l":1},{"word":"poppen","l":1},{"word":"eine Nummer schieben","l":1},{"word":"bumsen","l":1},{"word":"v\xf6geln","l":1}]},{"id":650,"question":"seed","answers":[{"word":"Samen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Saat","gender":"f"},{"word":"Same","gender":"m"},{"word":"Korn","gender":"n"},{"word":"Saatgut","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aussaat","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Samenkorn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Keim","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Saatkorn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kern","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"setzen","l":1},{"word":"s\xe4en","l":1},{"word":"auss\xe4en","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk ansehen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) erkennen"},{"word":"verstehen"},{"word":"aufsuchen"},{"word":"einsehen","l":1},{"word":"begreifen","l":1},{"word":"ersehen","l":1},{"word":"erblicken","l":1},{"word":"zusehen","l":1},{"word":"miterleben","l":1},{"word":"nachsehen","l":1}]},{"id":651,"question":"sheep","answers":[{"word":"Schaf","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schafe"},{"word":"Herdenmensch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Herdentier","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":652,"question":"shelf","answers":[{"word":"Regal","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ablage","gender":"f"},{"word":"B\xfccherregal","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Fach","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Regalboden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einlegeboden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bord","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ablagefl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schelf","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Brett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"B\xfccherbrett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Felsbank","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sandbank","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Felsenriff","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bordbrett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Felsvorsprung","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Untiefe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesims","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":653,"question":"ship","answers":[{"word":"Schiff","gender":"n"},{"word":"Pott","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"schiffen"},{"word":"bef\xf6rdern"},{"word":"ausliefern"},{"word":"versenden"},{"word":"verschicken"},{"word":"etw.Akk verschiffen"},{"word":"etw.Akk senden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verladen","l":1},{"word":"verfrachten","l":1},{"word":"abfertigen","l":1},{"word":"einschiffen","l":1}]},{"id":654,"question":"shirt","answers":[{"word":"Shirt","gender":"n"},{"word":"Hemd","gender":"n"},{"word":"Trikot","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Oberhemd","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Hemdbluse","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":655,"question":"shoe","answers":[{"word":"Schuh","gender":"m"},{"word":"Hufeisen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gleitschuh","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bremsschuh","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Halbschuh","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Backe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"etw.Akk beschlagen","l":1},{"word":"beschuhen","l":1}]},{"id":656,"question":"skin","answers":[{"word":"Haut","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schale","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fell","gender":"n"},{"word":"Skin","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Au\xdfenhaut","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erscheinungsbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Darm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Pelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schlauch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Balg","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"h\xe4uten"},{"word":"sch\xe4len"},{"word":"enth\xe4uten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Dat das Fell abziehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk entpellen","l":1},{"word":"abh\xe4uten","l":1},{"word":"pellen","l":1},{"word":"abbalgen","l":1},{"word":"abziehen","l":1}]},{"id":657,"question":"skirt","answers":[{"word":"Rock","gender":"m"},{"word":"Sch\xfcrze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Jupe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Damenrock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Unterteil","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Frauenrock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"umgehen"},{"word":"herumgehen"}]},{"id":658,"question":"snake","answers":[{"word":"Schlange","gender":"f"}]},{"id":659,"question":"sock","answers":[{"word":"Socken","gender":"m"},{"word":"Socke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Strumpf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einlegesohle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Faustschlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"schlagen","l":1},{"word":"hauen","l":1}]},{"id":660,"question":"spade","answers":[{"word":"Pik","gender":"n"},{"word":"Spaten","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schaufel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gr\xfcn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schippe","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":661,"question":"sponge","answers":[{"word":"Schwamm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Biskuit","gender":"n"},{"word":"Badeschwamm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schaumstoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schmarotzer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk aufsaugen","l":1},{"word":"schmarotzen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk schnorren","l":1}]},{"id":662,"question":"spoon","answers":[{"word":"L\xf6ffel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Blinker","gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk l\xf6ffeln"}]},{"id":663,"question":"spring","answers":[{"word":"Fr\xfchjahr","gender":"n"},{"word":"Fr\xfchling","gender":"m"},{"word":"Feder","gender":"f"},{"word":"Quelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Born","gender":"m"},{"word":"Druckfeder","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Brunnen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Quell","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sprung","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Triebfeder","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lenz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sprungfeder","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Elastizit\xe4t","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Antriebsfeder","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"federn","l":1},{"word":"schnellen","l":1},{"word":"quellen","l":1},{"word":"sprie\xdfen","l":1}]},{"id":664,"question":"square","answers":[{"word":"Platz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Quadrat","gender":"n"},{"word":"Hauptplatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vierkant","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Viereck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Feld","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Rechteck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"K\xe4stchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Winkel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Karree","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Karo","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Quadratzahl","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geviert","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Winkelma\xdf","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Langweiler","gender":"m"},{"word":"Spie\xdfer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"quadratisch"},{"word":"viereckig"},{"word":"eckig","l":1},{"word":"direkt","l":1},{"word":"rechtwinklig","l":1},{"word":"vierkantig","l":1},{"word":"ordentlich","l":1},{"word":"vierschr\xf6tig","l":1},{"word":"spie\xdfig"},{"word":"anst\xe4ndig"},{"word":"abgleichen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) quadrieren"},{"word":"abrechnen"},{"word":"\xfcbereinstimmen","l":1},{"word":"glattstellen","l":1},{"word":"begleichen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) ausgleichen","l":1},{"word":"zusammenpassen","l":1},{"word":"rechtwinklig machen","l":1},{"word":"quadratisch machen","l":1},{"word":"gleichziehen","l":1},{"word":"schmieren"}]},{"id":665,"question":"stamp","answers":[{"word":"Stempel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Briefmarke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Marke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pr\xe4gung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stempelabdruck","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wertzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Steuermarke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stanze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kennzeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wertmarke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fallwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Beitragsmarke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Pochstempel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"stempeln"},{"word":"abstempeln"},{"word":"stampfen"},{"word":"etw.Akk pr\xe4gen","l":1},{"word":"stanzen","l":1},{"word":"trampeln","l":1},{"word":"zerstampfen","l":1},{"word":"aufstampfen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk auspr\xe4gen","l":1},{"word":"frankieren","l":1}]},{"id":666,"question":"star","answers":[{"word":"Star","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stern","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gestirn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Diva","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":667,"question":"station","answers":[{"word":"Bahnhof","gender":"m"},{"word":"Station","gender":"f"},{"word":"Haltestelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sender","gender":"m"},{"word":"Wache","gender":"f"},{"word":"Haltepunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Farm","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stelle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Posten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"stationieren","l":1},{"word":"aufstellen","l":1},{"word":"positionieren","l":1}]},{"id":668,"question":"stem","answers":[{"word":"Stamm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stiel","gender":"m"},{"word":"St\xe4ngel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schaft","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Halm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bl\xfctenstiel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wortstamm","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lenkervorbau","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Strunk","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"St\xf6\xdfel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Notenhals","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stammwort","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Hauptzweig","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hauptlinie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wurzel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vordersteven","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"stammen"},{"word":"abstammen"},{"word":"aufhalten"},{"word":"etw.Akk stemmen","l":1},{"word":"Einhalt gebieten","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) eind\xe4mmen","l":1},{"word":"zum Stillstand bringen","l":1}]},{"id":669,"question":"stick","answers":[{"word":"haften"},{"word":"kleben"},{"word":"klemmen"},{"word":"haften bleiben","l":1},{"word":"h\xe4ngen bleiben","l":1},{"word":"kleben bleiben","l":1},{"word":"befestigen","l":1},{"word":"stecken","l":1},{"word":"ankleben","l":1},{"word":"zusammenhalten","l":1},{"word":"anhaften","l":1},{"word":"festkleben","l":1},{"word":"anh\xe4ngen","l":1},{"word":"stechen","l":1},{"word":"stecken bleiben","l":1},{"word":"festsitzen","l":1},{"word":"haftenbleiben","l":1},{"word":"abstechen","l":1},{"word":"picken","l":1},{"word":"binden","l":1},{"word":"Stock","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stab","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stiel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Steuerkn\xfcppel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stift","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stecken","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stange","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schl\xe4gel","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":670,"question":"stocking","answers":[{"word":"Bevorratung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Strumpf","gender":"m"},{"word":"Damenstrumpf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk auf Lager haben"},{"word":"ausstatten"},{"word":"etw.Akk bevorraten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk am Lager haben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk am Lager f\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk auf Lager halten","l":1}]},{"id":671,"question":"stomach","answers":[{"word":"Magen","gender":"m"},{"word":"Bauch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Leib","gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk verdauen"},{"word":"etw.Akk ertragen"}]},{"id":672,"question":"store","answers":[{"word":"lagern"},{"word":"speichern"},{"word":"aufbewahren"},{"word":"etw.Akk verstauen"},{"word":"etw.Akk verwahren","l":1},{"word":"abspeichern","l":1},{"word":"einlagern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk hinterlegen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk unterbringen","l":1},{"word":"einspeichern","l":1},{"word":"auf Lager nehmen","l":1},{"word":"stapeln","l":1},{"word":"Lager","gender":"n"},{"word":"Speicher","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ft","gender":"n"},{"word":"Kaufhaus","gender":"n"},{"word":"Filiale","gender":"f"},{"word":"Laden","gender":"m"},{"word":"Warenhaus","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lagerraum","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Vorrat","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Lagerhaus","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":673,"question":"street","answers":[{"word":"Stra\xdfe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gasse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Stra\xdfenzug","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":674,"question":"sun","answers":[{"word":"Sonne","gender":"f"}]},{"id":675,"question":"table","answers":[{"word":"Tabelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Tisch","gender":"m"},{"word":"Tafel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufstellung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Liste","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Tafelrunde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verzeichnis","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Tischrunde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sims","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"vertagen"},{"word":"etw.Akk verschieben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk aufschieben","l":1},{"word":"zur\xfcck stellen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk in Tabellenform zusammenstellen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verlegen","l":1}]},{"id":676,"question":"tail","answers":[{"word":"Schwanz","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schweif","gender":"m"},{"word":"Heck","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ende","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schwanzflosse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zipfel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fluke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Spiel","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ausl\xe4ufer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hemdzipfel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rest","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hals","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"B\xfcrzel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sterz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stert","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Beschatter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"jdm. folgen"},{"word":"jdn. beschatten"},{"word":"jdn. verfolgen","l":1}]},{"id":677,"question":"thread","answers":[{"word":"Thread","gender":"m"},{"word":"Faden","gender":"m"},{"word":"Gewinde","gender":"n"},{"word":"Thema","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"roter Faden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Faser","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Garn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"N\xe4hgarn","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Strang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zwirn","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gewindegang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gespr\xe4chsfaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Zwirnsfaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Diskussionsfaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kette","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gedankengang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gespr\xe4chsgegenstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Themenstrang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"F\xe4dchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Beitragsstrang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Forumsfaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Forumsthread","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gespr\xe4chsthema","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aktivit\xe4tstr\xe4ger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Bindfaden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) einf\xe4deln"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) auff\xe4deln"},{"word":"etw.Akk aufziehen"},{"word":"etw.Akk f\xe4deln","l":1}]},{"id":678,"question":"throat","answers":[{"word":"Kehle","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hals","gender":"m"},{"word":"Rachen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schlund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gurgel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wassernase","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ventilkehle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ventilbohrungskehle","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":679,"question":"thumb","answers":[{"word":"Daumen","gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk abgreifen"}]},{"id":680,"question":"ticket","answers":[{"word":"Ticket","gender":"n"},{"word":"Eintrittskarte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Karte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahrkarte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Flugticket","gender":"n"},{"word":"Fahrschein","gender":"m"},{"word":"Strafzettel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Flugkarte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fahrausweis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Flugschein","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Los","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Liste","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Billett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kn\xf6llchen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kinokarte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Strafmandat","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"angeklebter Strafzettel f\xfcr Verkehrss\xfcnden","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wertmarke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zettel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Etikett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"etw.Akk mit einem Zettel versehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk kennzeichnen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk etikettieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk mit einem Etikett versehen","l":1},{"word":"auspreisen","l":1}]},{"id":681,"question":"toe","answers":[{"word":"Zehe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zeh","gender":"m"},{"word":"Spitze","gender":"f"},{"word":"Parallelit\xe4t","gender":"f"}]},{"id":682,"question":"tongue","answers":[{"word":"Zunge","gender":"f"},{"word":"Feder","gender":"f"},{"word":"Lasche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Landzunge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weichenzunge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Deichsel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zapfen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spund","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Glockenschwengel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schwengel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kl\xf6ppel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Glockenkl\xf6ppel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Z\xfcnglein","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Sprache","gender":"f"}]},{"id":683,"question":"tooth","answers":[{"word":"Zahn","gender":"m"},{"word":"Zinke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zacke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"verzahnen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk mit Zacken versehen","l":1}]},{"id":684,"question":"town","answers":[{"word":"Stadt","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ortschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kleinstadt","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":685,"question":"train","answers":[{"word":"Bahn","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schleppe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Eisenbahn","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Folge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"R\xe4derwerk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Eisenbahnzug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"langer Zug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Karawane","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schweif","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"trainieren"},{"word":"schulen"},{"word":"(jdn.) ausbilden"},{"word":"anlernen"},{"word":"erziehen"},{"word":"einweisen"},{"word":"abrichten"},{"word":"\xfcben","l":1},{"word":"lernen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. unterrichten","l":1},{"word":"heranbilden","l":1},{"word":"jdn. qualifizieren","l":1},{"word":"dressieren","l":1},{"word":"unterweisen","l":1},{"word":"einarbeiten","l":1}]},{"id":686,"question":"tray","answers":[{"word":"Tablett","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schale","gender":"f"},{"word":"Ablage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schublade","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einsatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tableau","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Brett","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Ablagekasten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ablagekorb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Servierbrett","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":687,"question":"tree","answers":[{"word":"Baum","gender":"m"},{"word":"Baumstruktur","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verzeichnisbaum","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":688,"question":"trousers","answers":[{"word":"Hose","gender":"f"},{"word":"Hosen"},{"word":"lange Hosen","l":1},{"word":"lange Hose","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beinkleid","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":689,"question":"umbrella","answers":[{"word":"Schirm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Regenschirm","gender":"m"}]},{"id":690,"question":"wall","answers":[{"word":"Mauer","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wall","gender":"m"},{"word":"Seitenwand","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wandung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erdwall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Damm","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":691,"question":"watch","answers":[{"word":"beobachten"},{"word":"anschauen"},{"word":"zuschauen"},{"word":"etw.Akk schauen"},{"word":"\xfcberwachen"},{"word":"etw.Akk betrachten"},{"word":"aufpassen"},{"word":"aufpassen auf"},{"word":"ansehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verfolgen","l":1},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk erleben","l":1},{"word":"achten","l":1},{"word":"wachen","l":1},{"word":"bewachen","l":1},{"word":"Acht geben","l":1},{"word":"\xfcber jdn./etw.Akk Wache halten","l":1},{"word":"abwarten","l":1},{"word":"Uhr","gender":"f"},{"word":"Armbanduhr","gender":"f"},{"word":"Wache","gender":"f"},{"word":"Taschenuhr","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wachdienst","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Turmw\xe4chter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Wachmannschaft","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schiffswache","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":692,"question":"wheel","answers":[{"word":"Rad","gender":"n"},{"word":"Steuerrad","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Laufrad","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Drehscheibe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ruder","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"rollen"},{"word":"wenden","l":1},{"word":"kreisen","l":1},{"word":"kehrtmachen","l":1},{"word":"schwenken","l":1},{"word":"herumdrehen","l":1}]},{"id":693,"question":"whip","answers":[{"word":"Peitsche","gender":"f"},{"word":"Gerte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Fraktionsvorsitzender","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gei\xdfel","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gesch\xe4ftsf\xfchrer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Einpeitscher","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fraktionsf\xfchrer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fraktionsf\xfchrerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ziemer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"peitschen"},{"word":"schlagen"},{"word":"auspeitschen"},{"word":"flitzen"},{"word":"rennen","l":1},{"word":"rasen","l":1}]},{"id":694,"question":"whistle","answers":[{"word":"Trillerpfeife","gender":"f"},{"word":"Pfeife","gender":"f"},{"word":"Pfiff","gender":"m"},{"word":"Pfeifton","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Anpfiff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fl\xf6te","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"pfeifen"},{"word":"fl\xf6ten","l":1},{"word":"sausen","l":1},{"word":"ein Signal geben","l":1}]},{"id":695,"question":"window","answers":[{"word":"Fenster","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schaufenster","gender":"n"},{"word":"Auslage","gender":"f"},{"word":"Scheibe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Sichtfenster","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Fensterscheibe","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":696,"question":"wing","answers":[{"word":"Fl\xfcgel","gender":"m"},{"word":"Tragfl\xe4che","gender":"f"},{"word":"Trakt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Seitenfl\xfcgel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tragfl\xfcgel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Geschwader","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kotfl\xfcgel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schwinge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Geb\xe4udefl\xfcgel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fittich","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kulisse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Flanke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"T\xfcrfl\xfcgel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"fliegen"}]},{"id":697,"question":"wire","answers":[{"word":"Draht","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kabel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Leitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ader","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Leitungsdraht","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Drahtschlinge","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Telegramm","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"\xfcberweisen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) verkabeln"},{"word":"wickeln","l":1},{"word":"verdrahten","l":1},{"word":"mit Draht befestigen","l":1},{"word":"mit Draht zusammenbinden","l":1},{"word":"mit Stacheldraht eingrenzen","l":1},{"word":"elektrische Leitung legen","l":1},{"word":"adrig"}]},{"id":698,"question":"worm","answers":[{"word":"Wurm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schnecke","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schneckengewinde","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schraubengewinde","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Made","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"sichAkk schl\xe4ngeln","l":1},{"word":"mit einem Wurmmittel behandeln","l":1},{"word":"zw\xe4ngen","l":1}]},{"id":699,"question":"able","answers":[{"word":"f\xe4hig"},{"word":"berechtigt","l":1},{"word":"kompetent","l":1},{"word":"begabt","l":1},{"word":"geschickt","l":1},{"word":"t\xfcchtig","l":1},{"word":"talentiert","l":1},{"word":"potent","l":1},{"word":"klug","l":1},{"word":"anstellig","l":1}]},{"id":700,"question":"acid","answers":[{"word":"S\xe4ure","gender":"f"},{"word":"Acid","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"LSD","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"sauer"}]},{"id":701,"question":"angry","answers":[{"word":"w\xfctend"},{"word":"\xe4rgerlich"},{"word":"ver\xe4rgert"},{"word":"aufgebracht","l":1},{"word":"zornig","l":1},{"word":"b\xf6se","l":1},{"word":"erz\xfcrnt","l":1},{"word":"sauer","l":1},{"word":"entz\xfcndet","l":1},{"word":"erbost","l":1},{"word":"st\xfcrmisch","l":1}]},{"id":702,"question":"automatic","answers":[{"word":"automatisch"},{"word":"selbstt\xe4tig","l":1},{"word":"maschinell","l":1},{"word":"unwillk\xfcrlich","l":1},{"word":"Automatik","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Selbstladepistole","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Automatikwagen","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":703,"question":"beautiful","answers":[{"word":"sch\xf6n"},{"word":"wundersch\xf6n"},{"word":"herrlich","l":1},{"word":"h\xfcbsch","l":1},{"word":"bildh\xfcbsch","l":1},{"word":"bildsch\xf6n","l":1}]},{"id":704,"question":"black","answers":[{"word":"Schwarz","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schwarze","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schwarzer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schw\xe4rze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schmutzbuchstabe","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"schwarz"},{"word":"d\xfcster","l":1},{"word":"schmutzig","l":1},{"word":"unsauber","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk schw\xe4rzen"}]},{"id":705,"question":"boiling","answers":[{"word":"Kochen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Sieden","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Aufkochen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"siedend","l":1},{"word":"brodelnd","l":1},{"word":"aufwallend","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk kochen"},{"word":"sieden"},{"word":"etw.Akk aufkochen","l":1},{"word":"abkochen","l":1},{"word":"brodeln","l":1},{"word":"br\xfchen","l":1},{"word":"auskochen","l":1},{"word":"wallen","l":1}]},{"id":706,"question":"bright","answers":[{"word":"hell"},{"word":"helle"},{"word":"licht"},{"word":"gl\xe4nzend"},{"word":"fr\xf6hlich"},{"word":"gescheit"},{"word":"aufgeweckt"},{"word":"intelligent"},{"word":"lichtstark","l":1},{"word":"lebhaft","l":1},{"word":"schlau","l":1},{"word":"strahlend","l":1},{"word":"blank","l":1},{"word":"brillant","l":1},{"word":"klar","l":1},{"word":"grell","l":1},{"word":"heiter","l":1},{"word":"viel versprechend","l":1},{"word":"g\xfcnstig","l":1},{"word":"hell leuchtend","l":1},{"word":"munter","l":1},{"word":"helllicht","l":1},{"word":"klug","l":1},{"word":"gl\xfccklich","l":1},{"word":"froh","l":1},{"word":"freudig","l":1},{"word":"clever","l":1}]},{"id":707,"question":"broken","answers":[{"word":"gebrochen"},{"word":"kaputt"},{"word":"zerbrochen"},{"word":"unterbrochen","l":1},{"word":"besch\xe4digt","l":1},{"word":"verletzt","l":1},{"word":"zerr\xfcttet","l":1},{"word":"defekt","l":1},{"word":"aufgebrochen","l":1},{"word":"geknickt","l":1},{"word":"kaputtgemacht","l":1},{"word":"nicht eingehalten","l":1},{"word":"zerrissen","l":1},{"word":"zersplittert","l":1},{"word":"kaputtgeschlagen","l":1},{"word":"au\xdfer Betrieb","l":1},{"word":"entzwei","l":1},{"word":"brechen"},{"word":"aufbrechen"},{"word":"zerbrechen"},{"word":"unterbrechen"},{"word":"rei\xdfen"},{"word":"sichAkk brechen","l":1},{"word":"abbrechen","l":1},{"word":"sprengen","l":1},{"word":"abschalten","l":1},{"word":"knicken","l":1},{"word":"trennen","l":1},{"word":"zusammenbrechen","l":1},{"word":"anbrechen","l":1},{"word":"platzen","l":1},{"word":"zerspringen","l":1},{"word":"zerrei\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"kaputtgehen","l":1},{"word":"aufheben","l":1},{"word":"losbrechen","l":1},{"word":"beugen","l":1},{"word":"hereinbrechen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk nicht einhalten","l":1},{"word":"erbrechen","l":1},{"word":"entsperren","l":1},{"word":"springen","l":1},{"word":"stoppen","l":1},{"word":"einwerfen","l":1},{"word":"branden","l":1},{"word":"kontern","l":1},{"word":"zersplittern","l":1},{"word":"entzweigehen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk kaputtschlagen","l":1}]},{"id":708,"question":"brown","answers":[{"word":"Braun","gender":"n"},{"word":"braun"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) br\xe4unen"},{"word":"anbraten","l":1},{"word":"braun werden","l":1},{"word":"anbr\xe4unen","l":1},{"word":"br\xfcnieren","l":1}]},{"id":709,"question":"cheap","answers":[{"word":"billig"},{"word":"g\xfcnstig"},{"word":"geizig"},{"word":"minderwertig"},{"word":"kosteng\xfcnstig","l":1},{"word":"preiswert","l":1},{"word":"preisg\xfcnstig","l":1},{"word":"wohlfeil","l":1},{"word":"wertlos","l":1},{"word":"knauserig","l":1},{"word":"gemein","l":1}]},{"id":710,"question":"chemical","answers":[{"word":"chemisch"},{"word":"Chemikalie","gender":"f"}]},{"id":711,"question":"chief","answers":[{"word":"Chef","gender":"m"},{"word":"Leiter","gender":"m"},{"word":"H\xe4uptling","gender":"m"},{"word":"Anf\xfchrer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Oberhaupt","gender":"n"},{"word":"Leiterin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Chefin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorgesetzter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"F\xfchrer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Meister","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Boss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"F\xfchrerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anf\xfchrerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorgesetze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"oberste"},{"word":"haupts\xe4chlich"},{"word":"erste","l":1},{"word":"erstes","l":1},{"word":"oberster","l":1},{"word":"Haupt...","l":1},{"word":"erster","l":1},{"word":"oberstes","l":1},{"word":"f\xfchrend","l":1},{"word":"bedeutendste","l":1}]},{"id":712,"question":"clean","answers":[{"word":"sauber"},{"word":"rein"},{"word":"einwandfrei"},{"word":"r\xfcckstandsfrei"},{"word":"anst\xe4ndig"},{"word":"reinlich"},{"word":"gereinigt","l":1},{"word":"v\xf6llig","l":1},{"word":"glatt","l":1},{"word":"steril","l":1},{"word":"stubenrein","l":1},{"word":"ohne Einschr\xe4nkung","l":1},{"word":"reinigen"},{"word":"s\xe4ubern"},{"word":"putzen"},{"word":"saubermachen","l":1},{"word":"sauber machen","l":1},{"word":"reinemachen","l":1},{"word":"abputzen","l":1}]},{"id":713,"question":"clear","answers":[{"word":"klar"},{"word":"eindeutig"},{"word":"deutlich"},{"word":"verst\xe4ndlich"},{"word":"hell"},{"word":"\xfcbersichtlich"},{"word":"rein"},{"word":"wolkenlos"},{"word":"durchsichtig"},{"word":"frei","l":1},{"word":"transparent","l":1},{"word":"anschaulich","l":1},{"word":"scharf","l":1},{"word":"netto","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberschaubar","l":1},{"word":"einleuchtend","l":1},{"word":"offenkundig","l":1},{"word":"evident","l":1},{"word":"ohne Zweifel","l":1},{"word":"durchschaubar","l":1},{"word":"\xfcbersehbar","l":1},{"word":"heiter","l":1},{"word":"vernehmlich","l":1},{"word":"ungetr\xfcbt","l":1},{"word":"unbehindert","l":1},{"word":"prononciert","l":1},{"word":"unzweideutig","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) l\xf6schen"},{"word":"kl\xe4ren"},{"word":"freimachen"},{"word":"reinigen"},{"word":"leeren"},{"word":"abholzen"},{"word":"aufr\xe4umen"},{"word":"aufkl\xe4ren","l":1},{"word":"frei machen","l":1},{"word":"roden","l":1},{"word":"verschwinden","l":1},{"word":"beseitigen","l":1},{"word":"abdecken","l":1},{"word":"abkl\xe4ren","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) abr\xe4umen","l":1},{"word":"ausr\xe4umen","l":1},{"word":"s\xe4ubern","l":1},{"word":"verrechnen","l":1},{"word":"genehmigen","l":1},{"word":"aufklaren","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk aufhellen","l":1},{"word":"freigeben","l":1},{"word":"abfertigen","l":1},{"word":"abwehren","l":1},{"word":"aushauen","l":1},{"word":"gegeneinander aufrechnen","l":1},{"word":"entblocken","l":1},{"word":"freir\xe4umen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk aufheitern","l":1},{"word":"ausverkaufen","l":1}]},{"id":714,"question":"common","answers":[{"word":"gemeinsam"},{"word":"\xfcblich"},{"word":"h\xe4ufig"},{"word":"gebr\xe4uchlich"},{"word":"gel\xe4ufig"},{"word":"allgemein","l":1},{"word":"gemein","l":1},{"word":"einfach","l":1},{"word":"allgemein bekannt","l":1},{"word":"g\xe4ngig","l":1},{"word":"normal","l":1},{"word":"gew\xf6hnlich","l":1},{"word":"allt\xe4glich","l":1},{"word":"gemeinschaftlich","l":1},{"word":"vulg\xe4r","l":1},{"word":"weitverbreitet","l":1},{"word":"herk\xf6mmlich","l":1},{"word":"landl\xe4ufig","l":1},{"word":"unmond\xe4n","l":1},{"word":"ordin\xe4r","l":1},{"word":"Allmende","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anger","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":715,"question":"complex","answers":[{"word":"komplex"},{"word":"aufw\xe4ndig"},{"word":"kompliziert","l":1},{"word":"vielschichtig","l":1},{"word":"un\xfcbersichtlich","l":1},{"word":"schwierig","l":1},{"word":"ausgefeilt","l":1},{"word":"Komplex","gender":"m"},{"word":"Anlage","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":716,"question":"conscious","answers":[{"word":"bewusst"},{"word":"wach","l":1},{"word":"wissentlich","l":1}]},{"id":717,"question":"cut","answers":[{"word":"geschnitten"},{"word":"zugeschnitten","l":1},{"word":"abgeschnitten","l":1},{"word":"ausgeschnitten","l":1},{"word":"gek\xfcrzt","l":1},{"word":"geschliffen","l":1},{"word":"beschnitten","l":1},{"word":"gem\xe4ht","l":1},{"word":"angeschnitten","l":1},{"word":"gekappt","l":1},{"word":"Schnitt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Reduzierung","gender":"f"},{"word":"K\xfcrzung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Abbau","gender":"m"},{"word":"Schnittwunde","gender":"f"},{"word":"Zuschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Ausschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schliff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Senkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Verschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Herabsetzung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einschr\xe4nkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Filmschnitt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hieb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Streichung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Platzwunde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schmarre","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Bildstock","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Blechabfall","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk schneiden"},{"word":"senken"},{"word":"reduzieren"},{"word":"m\xe4hen"},{"word":"etw.Akk k\xfcrzen"},{"word":"ausschneiden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abschneiden","l":1},{"word":"zuschneiden","l":1},{"word":"streichen","l":1},{"word":"einschneiden","l":1},{"word":"beschneiden","l":1},{"word":"schleifen","l":1},{"word":"durchschneiden","l":1},{"word":"abscheren","l":1},{"word":"zerschneiden","l":1},{"word":"kappen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk hauen","l":1},{"word":"herabsetzen","l":1},{"word":"verschneiden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk anschneiden","l":1},{"word":"spanen","l":1}]},{"id":718,"question":"deep","answers":[{"word":"Tiefe","gender":"f"},{"word":"tief"},{"word":"innig"},{"word":"tiefgehend"},{"word":"satt","l":1},{"word":"dunkel","l":1},{"word":"tiefgr\xfcndig","l":1},{"word":"unergr\xfcndlich","l":1},{"word":"tief gehend","l":1},{"word":"tiefsinnig","l":1}]},{"id":719,"question":"dependent","answers":[{"word":"abh\xe4ngig"},{"word":"angewiesen","l":1},{"word":"unselbstst\xe4ndig","l":1},{"word":"unselbst\xe4ndig","l":1},{"word":"unfrei","l":1},{"word":"Abh\xe4ngige","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Abh\xe4ngiger","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":720,"question":"early","answers":[{"word":"fr\xfch"},{"word":"vorzeitig"},{"word":"vorgezogen"},{"word":"anf\xe4nglich","l":1},{"word":"baldig","l":1},{"word":"fr\xfchzeitig"},{"word":"fr\xfcher"},{"word":"verfr\xfcht","l":1},{"word":"zu fr\xfch","l":1},{"word":"zeitig","l":1}]},{"id":721,"question":"elastic","answers":[{"word":"elastisch"},{"word":"federnd","l":1},{"word":"dehnbar","l":1},{"word":"biegsam","l":1},{"word":"nachgiebig","l":1},{"word":"Gummizug","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gummi","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gummiband","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Elastik","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":722,"question":"electric","answers":[{"word":"elektrisch"}]},{"id":723,"question":"equal","answers":[{"word":"gleich"},{"word":"gleichberechtigt"},{"word":"gleichm\xe4\xdfig","l":1},{"word":"gleichgestellt","l":1},{"word":"gleichwertig","l":1},{"word":"ebenb\xfcrtig","l":1},{"word":"entsprechend","l":1},{"word":"parit\xe4tisch","l":1},{"word":"gleichen"},{"word":"(etw.Dat) gleichkommen"},{"word":"gleichziehen","l":1}]},{"id":724,"question":"fat","answers":[{"word":"fett"},{"word":"dick"},{"word":"feist"},{"word":"Fett","gender":"n"},{"word":"m\xe4sten"}]},{"id":725,"question":"fertile","answers":[{"word":"fruchtbar"},{"word":"ertragreich","l":1},{"word":"ergiebig","l":1},{"word":"geb\xe4rf\xe4hig","l":1},{"word":"sch\xf6pferisch","l":1},{"word":"zeugungsf\xe4hig","l":1}]},{"id":726,"question":"first","answers":[{"word":"Erste","gender":"f"},{"word":"Eins","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"erste"},{"word":"erster"},{"word":"erstes"},{"word":"erstmalig","l":1},{"word":"erstrangig","l":1},{"word":"zuerst"},{"word":"erstmals","l":1},{"word":"zuvor","l":1},{"word":"zun\xe4chst","l":1},{"word":"erstens","l":1},{"word":"erst einmal","l":1},{"word":"voran","l":1},{"word":"erst mal","l":1},{"word":"vorneweg","l":1},{"word":"vornweg","l":1}]},{"id":727,"question":"fixed","answers":[{"word":"fest"},{"word":"fixiert"},{"word":"befestigt"},{"word":"fix"},{"word":"verabredet"},{"word":"festgesetzt","l":1},{"word":"angebracht","l":1},{"word":"station\xe4r","l":1},{"word":"starr","l":1},{"word":"feststehend","l":1},{"word":"festgemacht","l":1},{"word":"eingespannt","l":1},{"word":"vorgegeben","l":1},{"word":"aufgeh\xe4ngt","l":1},{"word":"unbeweglich","l":1},{"word":"ortsfest","l":1},{"word":"fest angebracht","l":1},{"word":"haltbar gemacht","l":1},{"word":"abgemacht","l":1},{"word":"unver\xe4nderlich","l":1},{"word":"feststellen"},{"word":"fixieren"},{"word":"festlegen"},{"word":"befestigen"},{"word":"reparieren"},{"word":"vereinbaren"},{"word":"in Ordnung bringen"},{"word":"bestimmen","l":1},{"word":"beheben","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) festsetzen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk l\xf6sen","l":1},{"word":"arretieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk korrigieren","l":1},{"word":"anbringen","l":1},{"word":"binden","l":1},{"word":"fixen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) festmachen","l":1},{"word":"bemessen","l":1},{"word":"ansetzen","l":1},{"word":"haltbar machen","l":1},{"word":"einspannen","l":1},{"word":"abmachen","l":1},{"word":"aufpflanzen","l":1},{"word":"aufh\xe4ngen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zubereiten","l":1}]},{"id":728,"question":"flat","answers":[{"word":"Wohnung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Apartment","gender":"n"},{"word":"Mietwohnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Etagenwohnung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Appartement","gender":"n"},{"word":"Ebene","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Platten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Fl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schl\xfcsselfl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Plattfu\xdf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Niederung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"flach"},{"word":"eben"},{"word":"plan"},{"word":"schal"},{"word":"matt","l":1},{"word":"glatt","l":1},{"word":"leer","l":1},{"word":"platt","l":1},{"word":"fl\xe4chig","l":1},{"word":"kontrastarm","l":1},{"word":"geschmacklos","l":1},{"word":"abgestanden","l":1},{"word":"kategorisch","l":1},{"word":"tonlos","l":1},{"word":"lustlos","l":1},{"word":"flach"}]},{"id":729,"question":"free","answers":[{"word":"frei"},{"word":"kostenlos"},{"word":"unentgeltlich","l":1},{"word":"kostenfrei","l":1},{"word":"ungebunden","l":1},{"word":"uneingeschr\xe4nkt","l":1},{"word":"offenherzig","l":1},{"word":"unbesetzt","l":1},{"word":"abk\xf6mmlich","l":1},{"word":"freilassen"},{"word":"befreien","l":1},{"word":"freigeben","l":1},{"word":"entblocken","l":1},{"word":"umsonst"}]},{"id":730,"question":"frequent","answers":[{"word":"h\xe4ufig"},{"word":"regelm\xe4\xdfig","l":1},{"word":"zahlreich","l":1},{"word":"oftmalig","l":1},{"word":"frequentieren","l":1},{"word":"h\xe4ufig besuchen","l":1},{"word":"aufsuchen","l":1}]},{"id":731,"question":"full","answers":[{"word":"voll"},{"word":"vollst\xe4ndig"},{"word":"rund"},{"word":"umfassend"},{"word":"gesamt"},{"word":"ausgebucht"},{"word":"v\xf6llig","l":1},{"word":"gef\xfcllt","l":1},{"word":"satt","l":1},{"word":"belegt","l":1},{"word":"vollinhaltlich","l":1},{"word":"bauschig","l":1},{"word":"drall","l":1},{"word":"inhaltsreich","l":1}]},{"id":732,"question":"general","answers":[{"word":"allgemein"},{"word":"generell"},{"word":"global"},{"word":"Haupt-","l":1},{"word":"durchg\xe4ngig","l":1},{"word":"gew\xf6hnlich","l":1},{"word":"\xfcbergreifend","l":1},{"word":"\xfcblich","l":1},{"word":"normal","l":1},{"word":"allseitig","l":1},{"word":"landl\xe4ufig","l":1},{"word":"allgemein g\xfcltig","l":1},{"word":"gebr\xe4uchlich","l":1},{"word":"General","gender":"m"},{"word":"Feldherr","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Heerf\xfchrer","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Generalin","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":733,"question":"good","answers":[{"word":"Gute","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gut","gender":"n"},{"word":"Heil","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wohlergehen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"gut"},{"word":"sch\xf6n"},{"word":"brav"},{"word":"lieb"},{"word":"g\xfcltig"},{"word":"triftig"},{"word":"g\xfcnstig","l":1},{"word":"geh\xf6rig","l":1},{"word":"zutr\xe4glich","l":1},{"word":"artig","l":1}]},{"id":734,"question":"great","answers":[{"word":"gro\xdf"},{"word":"gro\xdfartig"},{"word":"super"},{"word":"toll"},{"word":"prima"},{"word":"stark","l":1},{"word":"ausgezeichnet","l":1},{"word":"hoch","l":1},{"word":"enorm","l":1},{"word":"klasse","l":1},{"word":"wunderbar","l":1},{"word":"herrlich","l":1},{"word":"spitze","l":1},{"word":"riesig","l":1},{"word":"betr\xe4chtlich","l":1},{"word":"bedeutend","l":1},{"word":"pfundig","l":1},{"word":"knorke","l":1},{"word":"b\xe4rig","l":1},{"word":"fantastisch"}]},{"id":735,"question":"grey","answers":[{"word":"grau"},{"word":"d\xfcster","l":1},{"word":"tr\xfcbe","l":1},{"word":"Grau","gender":"n"},{"word":"Schimmel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Grauschimmel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"etw.Akk grau machen","l":1}]},{"id":736,"question":"gray","answers":[{"word":"Grau","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gray","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schimmel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"grau"}]},{"id":737,"question":"hanging","answers":[{"word":"h\xe4ngend"},{"word":"freih\xe4ngend","l":1},{"word":"aufh\xe4ngend","l":1},{"word":"absch\xfcssig","l":1},{"word":"Aufh\xe4ngen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Aufh\xe4ngung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Einh\xe4ngen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Behang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Erh\xe4ngen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Wandbehang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hinrichtung durch Erh\xe4ngen","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorhang","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":738,"question":"happy","answers":[{"word":"gl\xfccklich"},{"word":"zufrieden"},{"word":"fr\xf6hlich"},{"word":"happy","l":1},{"word":"froh","l":1},{"word":"erfreut","l":1},{"word":"freudig","l":1},{"word":"unbeschwert","l":1},{"word":"begl\xfcckt","l":1},{"word":"vergn\xfcgt","l":1},{"word":"freudvoll","l":1},{"word":"treffend","l":1},{"word":"gl\xfcckselig","l":1}]},{"id":739,"question":"hard","answers":[{"word":"hart"},{"word":"schwer"},{"word":"schwierig"},{"word":"fest"},{"word":"m\xfchevoll"},{"word":"unnachgiebig"},{"word":"stark","l":1},{"word":"anstrengend","l":1},{"word":"kr\xe4ftig","l":1},{"word":"heftig","l":1},{"word":"m\xfchsam","l":1},{"word":"streng","l":1},{"word":"scharf","l":1},{"word":"kraftvoll","l":1},{"word":"kalkhaltig","l":1},{"word":"prall","l":1},{"word":"diffizil","l":1},{"word":"verzwickt","l":1}]},{"id":740,"question":"healthy","answers":[{"word":"gesund"},{"word":"gesundheitsf\xf6rdernd","l":1},{"word":"wohlbehalten","l":1},{"word":"fit","l":1}]},{"id":741,"question":"high","answers":[{"word":"hoch"},{"word":"hohe"},{"word":"gro\xdf"},{"word":"hohes"},{"word":"hoher"},{"word":"hochgradig","l":1},{"word":"vornehm","l":1},{"word":"langsch\xe4ftig","l":1},{"word":"angeheitert"},{"word":"im Rausch","l":1},{"word":"Hoch","gender":"n"},{"word":"H\xf6chststand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Hochdruckgebiet","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Antizyklone","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"hoch"}]},{"id":742,"question":"hollow","answers":[{"word":"Hohlraum","gender":"m"},{"word":"Mulde","gender":"f"},{"word":"H\xf6hle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vertiefung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Senke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aush\xf6hlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grube","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"H\xf6hlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Loch","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Kuhle","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"schmales Tal","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bodensenke","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weitung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Talkessel","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"hohl"},{"word":"unaufrichtig","l":1},{"word":"eingefallen","l":1},{"word":"leer","l":1},{"word":"dumpf","l":1},{"word":"aush\xf6hlen","l":1},{"word":"vertiefen","l":1}]},{"id":743,"question":"important","answers":[{"word":"wichtig"},{"word":"wesentlich"},{"word":"bedeutend"},{"word":"bedeutsam","l":1},{"word":"erheblich","l":1},{"word":"ma\xdfgeblich","l":1},{"word":"einflussreich","l":1},{"word":"belangvoll","l":1},{"word":"nennenswert","l":1}]},{"id":744,"question":"kind","answers":[{"word":"Art","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sorte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Weise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gattung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Beschaffenheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schlag","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Klasse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"freundlich"},{"word":"nett"},{"word":"lieb"},{"word":"liebensw\xfcrdig"},{"word":"g\xfctig"},{"word":"entgegenkommend"},{"word":"herzlich","l":1}]},{"id":745,"question":"like","answers":[{"word":"wie"},{"word":"\xe4hnlich","l":1},{"word":"gleich","l":1},{"word":"gleichnamig","l":1},{"word":"m\xf6gen"},{"word":"gefallen"},{"word":"lieben","l":1},{"word":"sch\xe4tzen","l":1},{"word":"(jdn./etw.Akk) gernhaben","l":1},{"word":"goutieren","l":1},{"word":"als ob"},{"word":"genau wie","l":1},{"word":"irgendwie"}]},{"id":746,"question":"living","answers":[{"word":"Leben","gender":"n"},{"word":"Lebensunterhalt","gender":"m"},{"word":"Wohnen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Lebensweise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Lebenshaltungskosten","l":1},{"word":"Broterwerb","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"lebend","l":1},{"word":"lebendig","l":1},{"word":"wohnend","l":1},{"word":"rezent","l":1},{"word":"belebt","l":1},{"word":"leben"},{"word":"wohnen"},{"word":"weiterleben","l":1},{"word":"live"},{"word":"aktiv"},{"word":"lebendig","l":1},{"word":"lebend","l":1},{"word":"spannungsf\xfchrend","l":1},{"word":"stromf\xfchrend","l":1},{"word":"scharf","l":1},{"word":"geladen","l":1},{"word":"Strom f\xfchrend","l":1}]},{"id":747,"question":"long","answers":[{"word":"lange"},{"word":"lang"},{"word":"gro\xdf"},{"word":"langwierig"},{"word":"l\xe4nglich"},{"word":"weit","l":1},{"word":"l\xe4ngst"}]},{"id":748,"question":"male","answers":[{"word":"m\xe4nnlich"},{"word":"M\xe4nnchen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Mann","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stecker","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"R\xfcde","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"m\xe4nnliches Wesen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Mannsbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Hengst","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"m\xe4nnliche Person","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":749,"question":"married","answers":[{"word":"verheiratet"},{"word":"geheiratet"},{"word":"verehelicht","l":1},{"word":"ehelich","l":1},{"word":"heiraten"},{"word":"verheiraten"},{"word":"ehelichen","l":1},{"word":"eine Ehe eingehen","l":1},{"word":"freien","l":1},{"word":"eine Ehe schlie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk trauen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk verm\xe4hlen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk verehelichen","l":1},{"word":"jdn. zur Frau nehmen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk mit jdm. verheiraten","l":1},{"word":"jdn. trauen","l":1},{"word":"sichDat das Ja-Wort geben","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verbinden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk vereinen","l":1}]},{"id":750,"question":"material","answers":[{"word":"Material","gender":"n"},{"word":"Werkstoff","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Baustoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Materie","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Wissensstoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"wesentlich"},{"word":"materiell"},{"word":"wichtig","l":1},{"word":"k\xf6rperlich","l":1},{"word":"stofflich","l":1},{"word":"real","l":1},{"word":"von Belang","l":1},{"word":"dinglich","l":1}]},{"id":751,"question":"medical","answers":[{"word":"medizinisch"},{"word":"\xe4rztlich"},{"word":"\xe4rztliche Untersuchung","gender":"f"}]},{"id":752,"question":"military","answers":[{"word":"milit\xe4risch"},{"word":"soldatisch","l":1},{"word":"kriegerisch","l":1},{"word":"Milit\xe4r","gender":"n"},{"word":"Vielseitigkeitspr\xfcfung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Military-Reiten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Vielseitigkeitsreiten","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":753,"question":"natural","answers":[{"word":"nat\xfcrlich"},{"word":"naturbelassen"},{"word":"urspr\xfcnglich","l":1},{"word":"normal","l":1},{"word":"selbstverst\xe4ndlich","l":1},{"word":"naturgem\xe4\xdf","l":1},{"word":"naturgetreu","l":1},{"word":"naturbedingt","l":1},{"word":"naturhaft","l":1},{"word":"ungek\xfcnstelt","l":1},{"word":"naturw\xfcchsig","l":1},{"word":"angeboren","l":1},{"word":"urw\xfcchsig","l":1},{"word":"naturgegeben","l":1},{"word":"urt\xfcmlich","l":1},{"word":"unbefangen","l":1},{"word":"kreat\xfcrlich","l":1},{"word":"leiblich","l":1},{"word":"Naturtalent","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"nat\xfcrliche Zahl","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Aufl\xf6sungszeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":754,"question":"necessary","answers":[{"word":"erforderlich"},{"word":"notwendig"},{"word":"n\xf6tig"},{"word":"ben\xf6tigt","l":1},{"word":"wichtig","l":1},{"word":"unerl\xe4sslich","l":1},{"word":"vonn\xf6ten","l":1},{"word":"dazugeh\xf6rig","l":1}]},{"id":755,"question":"new","answers":[{"word":"neu"},{"word":"ungewohnt"},{"word":"frisch","l":1},{"word":"fremd","l":1},{"word":"neuartig","l":1},{"word":"unbekannt","l":1},{"word":"fremdartig","l":1}]},{"id":756,"question":"normal","answers":[{"word":"normal"},{"word":"gew\xf6hnlich"},{"word":"\xfcblich","l":1},{"word":"typisch","l":1},{"word":"gewohnt","l":1},{"word":"regul\xe4r","l":1},{"word":"allgemein \xfcblich","l":1},{"word":"gebr\xe4uchlich","l":1},{"word":"unverstellt","l":1},{"word":"konventionell","l":1},{"word":"Normale","gender":"f"}]},{"id":757,"question":"open","answers":[{"word":"offen"},{"word":"frei"},{"word":"ge\xf6ffnet"},{"word":"zug\xe4nglich"},{"word":"aufgeschlossen"},{"word":"ungekl\xe4rt"},{"word":"ungel\xf6st"},{"word":"aufrichtig"},{"word":"einsehbar","l":1},{"word":"durchbrochen","l":1},{"word":"offenherzig","l":1},{"word":"ungesch\xfctzt","l":1},{"word":"ehrlich","l":1},{"word":"\xfcbersichtlich","l":1},{"word":"unverhohlen","l":1},{"word":"durchl\xe4ssig","l":1},{"word":"ungedeckt","l":1},{"word":"\xf6ffnen"},{"word":"etw.Akk er\xf6ffnen"},{"word":"erschlie\xdfen"},{"word":"aufmachen"},{"word":"aufklappen"},{"word":"aufschlagen"},{"word":"einrichten","l":1},{"word":"anfangen","l":1},{"word":"entfalten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk aufdrehen","l":1},{"word":"anbrechen","l":1},{"word":"einleiten","l":1},{"word":"einweihen","l":1},{"word":"aufbl\xe4ttern","l":1},{"word":"aufklinken","l":1},{"word":"entsperren","l":1},{"word":"aufziehen","l":1}]},{"id":758,"question":"parallel","answers":[{"word":"parallel"},{"word":"gleichlaufend","l":1},{"word":"nebenl\xe4ufig","l":1},{"word":"Parallele","gender":"f"},{"word":"Breitengrad","gender":"m"},{"word":"Breitenkreis","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Entsprechung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gegenst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"parallel laufen"},{"word":"etw.Dat entsprechen","l":1},{"word":"nebeneinander"}]},{"id":759,"question":"past","answers":[{"word":"nach"},{"word":"\xfcber"},{"word":"vorbei an","l":1},{"word":"Vergangenheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Geschichte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorgeschichte","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorleben","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"vergangen"},{"word":"letzte"},{"word":"bisherig","l":1},{"word":"beendet","l":1},{"word":"einstig","l":1},{"word":"ehemalig","l":1},{"word":"vorbei"},{"word":"vor\xfcber","l":1}]},{"id":760,"question":"physical","answers":[{"word":"physisch"},{"word":"physikalisch"},{"word":"k\xf6rperlich"},{"word":"technisch","l":1},{"word":"real","l":1},{"word":"leiblich","l":1},{"word":"materiell","l":1},{"word":"leibhaftig","l":1},{"word":"k\xf6rperbetont","l":1},{"word":"\xe4rztliche Untersuchung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Musterung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Vorsorgeuntersuchung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":761,"question":"political","answers":[{"word":"politisch"}]},{"id":762,"question":"poor","answers":[{"word":"arm"},{"word":"schlecht"},{"word":"gering"},{"word":"mangelhaft","l":1},{"word":"billig","l":1},{"word":"d\xfcrftig","l":1},{"word":"armselig","l":1},{"word":"mager","l":1},{"word":"notd\xfcrftig","l":1},{"word":"geringwertig","l":1},{"word":"\xe4rmlich","l":1}]},{"id":763,"question":"possible","answers":[{"word":"m\xf6glich"},{"word":"eventuell"},{"word":"realisierbar"},{"word":"etwaig","l":1},{"word":"allf\xe4llig","l":1},{"word":"denkbar","l":1},{"word":"machbar","l":1},{"word":"tunlich","l":1}]},{"id":764,"question":"present","answers":[{"word":"darstellen"},{"word":"zeigen"},{"word":"etw.Akk \xfcbergeben"},{"word":"vortragen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) pr\xe4sentieren"},{"word":"jdn./etw.Akk vorstellen"},{"word":"bieten"},{"word":"etw.Akk vorlegen"},{"word":"darlegen"},{"word":"aufweisen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk unterbreiten","l":1},{"word":"anbieten","l":1},{"word":"vorf\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"darbieten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk \xfcberreichen","l":1},{"word":"auff\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) moderieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk einreichen","l":1},{"word":"ausstellen","l":1},{"word":"ansagen","l":1},{"word":"anwesend"},{"word":"derzeitig"},{"word":"vorliegend"},{"word":"heutig"},{"word":"vorhanden","l":1},{"word":"gegenw\xe4rtig","l":1},{"word":"momentan","l":1},{"word":"bestehend","l":1},{"word":"laufend","l":1},{"word":"bisherig","l":1},{"word":"pr\xe4sent","l":1},{"word":"aktuell","l":1},{"word":"zugegen","l":1},{"word":"augenblicklich","l":1},{"word":"jetzig","l":1},{"word":"vorfindlich","l":1},{"word":"nunmehrig","l":1},{"word":"Gegenwart","gender":"f"},{"word":"Geschenk","gender":"n"},{"word":"Pr\xe4sens","gender":"n"},{"word":"Pr\xe4sent","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Jetzt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Jetztzeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gastgeschenk","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Schenkung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gabe","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":765,"question":"private","answers":[{"word":"privat"},{"word":"vertraulich"},{"word":"pers\xf6nlich"},{"word":"eigen"},{"word":"geheim","l":1},{"word":"reserviert","l":1},{"word":"nicht \xf6ffentlich","l":1},{"word":"zur\xfcckhaltend","l":1},{"word":"Gefreiter","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gefreite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Grenadier","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sch\xfctze","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Landser","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"einfacher Soldat","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":766,"question":"probable","answers":[{"word":"wahrscheinlich"},{"word":"voraussichtlich","l":1},{"word":"vermutlich","l":1},{"word":"glaubw\xfcrdig","l":1},{"word":"mutma\xdflich","l":1},{"word":"glaubhaft","l":1}]},{"id":767,"question":"quick","answers":[{"word":"schnell"},{"word":"rasch"},{"word":"kurz"},{"word":"z\xfcgig"},{"word":"fix"},{"word":"flink"},{"word":"lebendig","l":1},{"word":"flott","l":1},{"word":"hurtig","l":1},{"word":"wach","l":1},{"word":"schleunig","l":1},{"word":"geschwind","l":1},{"word":"gewandt","l":1},{"word":"fl\xfcchtig","l":1},{"word":"aufgeweckt","l":1}]},{"id":768,"question":"quiet","answers":[{"word":"Ruhe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stille","gender":"f"},{"word":"ruhig"},{"word":"leise"},{"word":"still"},{"word":"heimlich"},{"word":"ger\xe4uscharm","l":1},{"word":"dezent","l":1},{"word":"ger\xe4uschlos","l":1},{"word":"friedlich","l":1},{"word":"halblaut","l":1},{"word":"unbelebt","l":1},{"word":"geruhsam","l":1},{"word":"(jdn./etw.Akk) beruhigen","l":1},{"word":"zur Ruhe bringen","l":1}]},{"id":769,"question":"ready","answers":[{"word":"bereit"},{"word":"fertig"},{"word":"einsatzbereit","l":1},{"word":"betriebsbereit","l":1},{"word":"gebrauchsfertig","l":1},{"word":"ger\xfcstet","l":1},{"word":"parat","l":1},{"word":"verf\xfcgbar","l":1},{"word":"einsatzf\xe4hig","l":1},{"word":"in Bereitschaft","l":1},{"word":"startklar","l":1},{"word":"geschafft","l":1},{"word":"schlagfertig","l":1},{"word":"betriebsklar","l":1},{"word":"vorbereiten"},{"word":"bereiten","l":1},{"word":"r\xfcsten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bereitmachen","l":1}]},{"id":770,"question":"red","answers":[{"word":"Rot","gender":"n"},{"word":"R\xf6te","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"rot"},{"word":"fuchsrot","l":1}]},{"id":771,"question":"regular","answers":[{"word":"regelm\xe4\xdfig"},{"word":"normal"},{"word":"fest"},{"word":"laufend","l":1},{"word":"st\xe4ndig","l":1},{"word":"regul\xe4r","l":1},{"word":"periodisch","l":1},{"word":"gleichm\xe4\xdfig","l":1},{"word":"regelrecht","l":1},{"word":"turnusm\xe4\xdfig","l":1},{"word":"aktiv","l":1},{"word":"geregelt","l":1},{"word":"ordnungsgem\xe4\xdf","l":1},{"word":"regelgerecht","l":1},{"word":"\xfcblich","l":1},{"word":"ordentlich","l":1},{"word":"allt\xe4glich","l":1},{"word":"gew\xf6hnlich","l":1},{"word":"vorschriftsm\xe4\xdfig","l":1},{"word":"herk\xf6mmlich","l":1},{"word":"gleichf\xf6rmig","l":1},{"word":"ausgesprochen","l":1},{"word":"ebenm\xe4\xdfig","l":1},{"word":"richtiggehend","l":1},{"word":"Stammgast","gender":"m"},{"word":"Stammkunde","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stammkundin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Berufssoldat","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Stammspieler","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Berufssoldatin","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":772,"question":"responsible","answers":[{"word":"verantwortlich"},{"word":"zust\xe4ndig"},{"word":"haftbar"},{"word":"verantwortungsvoll"},{"word":"verantwortungsbewusst"},{"word":"federf\xfchrend"},{"word":"kompetent","l":1},{"word":"zuverl\xe4ssig","l":1},{"word":"verantwortbar","l":1},{"word":"m\xfcndig","l":1}]},{"id":773,"question":"right","answers":[{"word":"recht"},{"word":"richtig"},{"word":"rechte","l":1},{"word":"direkt","l":1},{"word":"rechter","l":1},{"word":"rechtes","l":1},{"word":"gut","l":1},{"word":"voll","l":1},{"word":"gerecht","l":1},{"word":"zutreffend","l":1},{"word":"Recht","gender":"n"},{"word":"rechte Seite","gender":"f"},{"word":"Berechtigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anrecht","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"rechts"},{"word":"gleich"},{"word":"nach rechts"},{"word":"sehr","l":1},{"word":"rechtsherum","l":1},{"word":"aufrichten"},{"word":"etw.Akk wiedergutmachen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk richtigstellen","l":1},{"word":"gell"}]},{"id":774,"question":"round","answers":[{"word":"etw.Akk runden"},{"word":"abrunden"},{"word":"um"},{"word":"rund um"},{"word":"Runde","gender":"f"},{"word":"Durchgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Rundgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Spielrunde","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Schuss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Kontrollgang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Visite","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Munitionsladung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"abgegebener Schuss","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Scheibe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ladung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kanon","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Munition f\xfcr einen Schuss","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Rundgesang","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"rund"},{"word":"rundlich","l":1},{"word":"drall","l":1},{"word":"ringsum"},{"word":"rundherum","l":1},{"word":"reihum","l":1},{"word":"ringsherum","l":1}]},{"id":775,"question":"same","answers":[{"word":"Gleiche","gender":"n"},{"word":"gleich"}]},{"id":776,"question":"second","answers":[{"word":"zweite"},{"word":"zweiter"},{"word":"zweites"},{"word":"Zweite","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sekunde","gender":"f"},{"word":"Sekundant","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sekundantin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Zweitausfertigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"nochmalig"},{"word":"zweitens"},{"word":"unterst\xfctzen"},{"word":"helfen","l":1}]},{"id":777,"question":"separate","answers":[{"word":"gesondert"},{"word":"separat"},{"word":"getrennt"},{"word":"einzeln"},{"word":"eigen"},{"word":"unabh\xe4ngig","l":1},{"word":"unterschiedlich","l":1},{"word":"eigenst\xe4ndig","l":1},{"word":"verschieden","l":1},{"word":"voneinander getrennt","l":1},{"word":"abgetrennt","l":1},{"word":"abgesondert","l":1},{"word":"teilen"},{"word":"trennen"},{"word":"auseinandergehen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) separieren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abtrennen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) scheiden","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk scheiden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk vereinzeln","l":1},{"word":"absondern","l":1},{"word":"ausscheiden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abscheiden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk auftrennen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zertrennen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk abspalten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk auslesen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk abspalten","l":1}]},{"id":778,"question":"serious","answers":[{"word":"ernst"},{"word":"ernsthaft"},{"word":"schwerwiegend"},{"word":"schwer"},{"word":"seri\xf6s","l":1},{"word":"gravierend","l":1},{"word":"erheblich","l":1},{"word":"kapital","l":1},{"word":"ernstzunehmend","l":1},{"word":"schlimm","l":1},{"word":"gesetzt","l":1},{"word":"ernstlich","l":1},{"word":"massiv","l":1},{"word":"ernst gemeint","l":1},{"word":"betr\xe4chtlich","l":1},{"word":"folgenreich","l":1},{"word":"bedenklich","l":1},{"word":"folgenschwer","l":1},{"word":"gewichtig","l":1},{"word":"arg","l":1},{"word":"dr\xfcckend","l":1}]},{"id":779,"question":"sharp","answers":[{"word":"stark"},{"word":"scharf"},{"word":"spitz"},{"word":"schlau"},{"word":"deutlich","l":1},{"word":"klar","l":1},{"word":"scharfsinnig","l":1},{"word":"pl\xf6tzlich","l":1},{"word":"drastisch","l":1},{"word":"scharfkantig","l":1},{"word":"gerissen","l":1},{"word":"genau","l":1},{"word":"elegant","l":1},{"word":"pfiffig","l":1},{"word":"herb","l":1},{"word":"durchdringend","l":1},{"word":"geharnischt","l":1},{"word":"bei\xdfend","l":1},{"word":"unvermittelt","l":1},{"word":"schneidend","l":1},{"word":"abrupt","l":1},{"word":"stechend","l":1},{"word":"schrill","l":1},{"word":"verschlagen","l":1},{"word":"scharf"},{"word":"pl\xf6tzlich","l":1},{"word":"genau","l":1},{"word":"schrill","l":1},{"word":"abrupt","l":1},{"word":"Kreuz","gender":"n"},{"word":"Doppelkreuz","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Doppelkreuz-Zeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Erh\xf6hungszeichen","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":780,"question":"smooth","answers":[{"word":"reibungslos"},{"word":"glatt"},{"word":"eben"},{"word":"weich"},{"word":"geschmeidig"},{"word":"ruhig"},{"word":"sanft"},{"word":"gleichm\xe4\xdfig","l":1},{"word":"problemlos","l":1},{"word":"fl\xfcssig","l":1},{"word":"leichtg\xe4ngig","l":1},{"word":"s\xe4mig","l":1},{"word":"nahtlos","l":1},{"word":"mild","l":1},{"word":"lieblich","l":1},{"word":"sacht","l":1},{"word":"faltenlos","l":1},{"word":"fugenlos","l":1},{"word":"gl\xe4tten"},{"word":"ebnen"},{"word":"glatt streichen","l":1},{"word":"spachteln","l":1}]},{"id":781,"question":"sticky","answers":[{"word":"klebrig"},{"word":"verklebt"},{"word":"schw\xfcl"},{"word":"haftend","l":1},{"word":"pappig","l":1},{"word":"stickig","l":1},{"word":"dr\xfcckend","l":1},{"word":"verschwitzt","l":1}]},{"id":782,"question":"stiff","answers":[{"word":"steif"},{"word":"starr"},{"word":"unbeweglich"},{"word":"hart","l":1},{"word":"ungelenkig","l":1},{"word":"fest","l":1},{"word":"schwerg\xe4ngig","l":1},{"word":"ungelenk","l":1},{"word":"stocksteif","l":1},{"word":"z\xe4h","l":1},{"word":"lahm","l":1},{"word":"eingerostet","l":1},{"word":"Leiche","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kassiber","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":783,"question":"straight","answers":[{"word":"gerade"},{"word":"direkt"},{"word":"pur"},{"word":"aufrecht"},{"word":"glatt"},{"word":"geradlinig","l":1},{"word":"klar","l":1},{"word":"rein","l":1},{"word":"unverd\xfcnnt","l":1},{"word":"offen","l":1},{"word":"ehrlich","l":1},{"word":"unverf\xe4lscht","l":1},{"word":"unvermischt","l":1},{"word":"astrein","l":1},{"word":"ordentlich","l":1},{"word":"hetero"},{"word":"gerade","l":1},{"word":"direkt","l":1},{"word":"geradewegs","l":1},{"word":"geradlinig","l":1},{"word":"pur","l":1},{"word":"aufrecht","l":1},{"word":"glatt","l":1},{"word":"klar","l":1},{"word":"rein","l":1},{"word":"schnurstracks","l":1},{"word":"unverd\xfcnnt","l":1},{"word":"offen","l":1},{"word":"ehrlich","l":1},{"word":"stracks","l":1},{"word":"unverf\xe4lscht","l":1},{"word":"unvermischt","l":1},{"word":"ordentlich","l":1},{"word":"Gerade","gender":"f"},{"word":"Stra\xdfe","gender":"f"}]},{"id":784,"question":"strong","answers":[{"word":"stark"},{"word":"fest"},{"word":"stabil"},{"word":"\xfcberzeugend"},{"word":"solide","l":1},{"word":"schwer","l":1},{"word":"kr\xe4ftig","l":1},{"word":"robust","l":1},{"word":"kraftvoll","l":1},{"word":"m\xe4chtig","l":1},{"word":"hart","l":1},{"word":"ausgepr\xe4gt","l":1},{"word":"charakterstark","l":1},{"word":"scharf","l":1},{"word":"kampfstark","l":1},{"word":"derb","l":1}]},{"id":785,"question":"sudden","answers":[{"word":"pl\xf6tzlich"},{"word":"unerwartet"},{"word":"abrupt"},{"word":"j\xe4h"},{"word":"unvorhergesehen","l":1},{"word":"schlagartig","l":1},{"word":"unvermittelt","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberraschend","l":1},{"word":"ruckartig","l":1}]},{"id":786,"question":"sweet","answers":[{"word":"s\xfc\xdf"},{"word":"niedlich"},{"word":"goldig"},{"word":"s\xfc\xdflich","l":1},{"word":"lieblich","l":1},{"word":"lieb","l":1},{"word":"herzig","l":1},{"word":"possierlich","l":1},{"word":"hold","l":1},{"word":"wonnig","l":1},{"word":"S\xfc\xdfe","gender":"f"},{"word":"Bonbon","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Nachspeise","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Nachtisch","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Dessert","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Zuckerl","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gutsel","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":787,"question":"tall","answers":[{"word":"hoch"},{"word":"gro\xdf"},{"word":"hochw\xfcchsig","l":1},{"word":"gro\xdfgewachsen","l":1},{"word":"hochst\xe4mmig","l":1}]},{"id":788,"question":"thick","answers":[{"word":"dick"},{"word":"stark"},{"word":"dicht"},{"word":"z\xe4hfl\xfcssig"},{"word":"dumm"},{"word":"s\xe4mig","l":1},{"word":"m\xe4chtig","l":1},{"word":"dicklich","l":1},{"word":"stockdumm","l":1},{"word":"strohdumm","l":1},{"word":"wulstig","l":1}]},{"id":789,"question":"tight","answers":[{"word":"eng"},{"word":"dicht"},{"word":"fest"},{"word":"knapp"},{"word":"straff"},{"word":"angespannt"},{"word":"eng anliegend"},{"word":"streng","l":1},{"word":"stramm","l":1},{"word":"gespannt","l":1},{"word":"knapp bemessen","l":1},{"word":"geizig","l":1},{"word":"undurchl\xe4ssig","l":1},{"word":"hautnah","l":1},{"word":"knauserig","l":1},{"word":"voll","l":1},{"word":"kn\xfclle","l":1}]},{"id":790,"question":"tired","answers":[{"word":"m\xfcde"},{"word":"ersch\xf6pft"},{"word":"erm\xfcdet"},{"word":"ausgelaugt","l":1},{"word":"strapaziert","l":1},{"word":"geschafft","l":1},{"word":"unausgeschlafen","l":1},{"word":"ermattet","l":1},{"word":"erm\xfcden"},{"word":"m\xfcde werden","l":1},{"word":"erlahmen","l":1},{"word":"erschlaffen","l":1},{"word":"ermatten","l":1}]},{"id":791,"question":"true","answers":[{"word":"wahr"},{"word":"treu"},{"word":"richtig"},{"word":"echt"},{"word":"genau"},{"word":"tats\xe4chlich"},{"word":"getreu","l":1},{"word":"wirklich","l":1},{"word":"zutreffend","l":1},{"word":"wahrheitsgem\xe4\xdf","l":1},{"word":"wahrhaftig","l":1},{"word":"eigentlich","l":1},{"word":"wahrhaft","l":1},{"word":"aufrecht","l":1},{"word":"korrekt","l":1},{"word":"wahrheitsgetreu","l":1},{"word":"abrichten","l":1},{"word":"auswuchten","l":1}]},{"id":792,"question":"violent","answers":[{"word":"gewaltt\xe4tig"},{"word":"gewaltsam"},{"word":"heftig"},{"word":"brutal"},{"word":"stark","l":1},{"word":"rabiat","l":1},{"word":"t\xe4tlich","l":1},{"word":"leidenschaftlich","l":1},{"word":"ungest\xfcm","l":1},{"word":"gewaltig","l":1},{"word":"hitzig","l":1},{"word":"handgreiflich","l":1},{"word":"brachial","l":1},{"word":"st\xfcrmisch","l":1}]},{"id":793,"question":"waiting","answers":[{"word":"Warten","gender":"n"},{"word":"Warterei","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Halten","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Servieren","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Bedienen","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"wartend"},{"word":"warten"},{"word":"abwarten"},{"word":"ausharren","l":1}]},{"id":794,"question":"warm","answers":[{"word":"warm"},{"word":"herzlich"},{"word":"warmherzig","l":1},{"word":"erhitzt","l":1},{"word":"aufw\xe4rmen"},{"word":"sichAkk erw\xe4rmen","l":1},{"word":"w\xe4rmen","l":1},{"word":"warm werden","l":1},{"word":"warm machen","l":1},{"word":"anw\xe4rmen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk erhitzen","l":1}]},{"id":795,"question":"wet","answers":[{"word":"nass"},{"word":"feucht"},{"word":"durchn\xe4sst","l":1},{"word":"regnerisch","l":1},{"word":"klamm","l":1},{"word":"vern\xe4sst","l":1},{"word":"regenreich","l":1},{"word":"schlackig","l":1},{"word":"schlapp","l":1},{"word":"N\xe4sse","gender":"f"},{"word":"Feuchtigkeit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Jammerlappen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"befeuchten"},{"word":"nass machen","l":1},{"word":"benetzen","l":1},{"word":"w\xe4ssern","l":1},{"word":"n\xe4ssen","l":1},{"word":"anfeuchten","l":1},{"word":"netzen","l":1}]},{"id":796,"question":"wide","answers":[{"word":"breit"},{"word":"weit"},{"word":"gro\xdf"},{"word":"umfangreich"},{"word":"umfassend"},{"word":"breitfl\xe4chig"},{"word":"weitgehend","l":1},{"word":"reichhaltig","l":1},{"word":"Breite","gender":"f"},{"word":"weit"}]},{"id":797,"question":"wise","answers":[{"word":"weise"},{"word":"klug"},{"word":"vern\xfcnftig"},{"word":"sinnvoll","l":1},{"word":"ratsam","l":1},{"word":"gelehrt","l":1},{"word":"verst\xe4ndnisvoll","l":1},{"word":"verst\xe4ndig","l":1}]},{"id":798,"question":"yellow","answers":[{"word":"gelb"},{"word":"gehl","l":1},{"word":"feige","l":1},{"word":"feig","l":1},{"word":"Gelb","gender":"n"},{"word":"gelb werden","l":1},{"word":"vergilben","l":1},{"word":"gilben","l":1}]},{"id":799,"question":"young","answers":[{"word":"jung"},{"word":"jugendlich"},{"word":"klein","l":1},{"word":"Jugendliche"}]},{"id":800,"question":"awake","answers":[{"word":"wach"},{"word":"munter"},{"word":"wecken"},{"word":"erwachen"},{"word":"aufwachen"},{"word":"erwecken","l":1},{"word":"wach werden","l":1},{"word":"aufwecken","l":1}]},{"id":801,"question":"bad","answers":[{"word":"schlecht"},{"word":"b\xf6se"},{"word":"schlimm"},{"word":"schwer"},{"word":"stark","l":1},{"word":"ungut","l":1},{"word":"sch\xe4dlich","l":1},{"word":"falsch","l":1},{"word":"krank","l":1},{"word":"\xfcbel","l":1},{"word":"faul","l":1},{"word":"schwach","l":1},{"word":"unangenehm","l":1},{"word":"arg","l":1},{"word":"schei\xdfe","l":1},{"word":"unzureichend","l":1},{"word":"kaputt","l":1},{"word":"verdorben","l":1},{"word":"ungezogen","l":1},{"word":"unrein","l":1},{"word":"mau","l":1},{"word":"unartig","l":1},{"word":"mangelhaft","l":1},{"word":"garstig","l":1},{"word":"Minus","gender":"n"}]},{"id":802,"question":"bent","answers":[{"word":"gebogen"},{"word":"gekr\xfcmmt","l":1},{"word":"gebeugt","l":1},{"word":"verbogen","l":1},{"word":"umgebogen","l":1},{"word":"abgewinkelt","l":1},{"word":"krumm","l":1},{"word":"angewinkelt","l":1},{"word":"versessen","l":1},{"word":"geb\xfcckt","l":1},{"word":"verkr\xfcmmt","l":1},{"word":"korrupt","l":1},{"word":"unsauber","l":1},{"word":"schwul"},{"word":"Neigung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Veranlagung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Begabung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) biegen"},{"word":"etw.Akk verbiegen"},{"word":"sichAkk biegen","l":1},{"word":"knicken","l":1},{"word":"abbiegen","l":1},{"word":"abwinkeln","l":1},{"word":"umbiegen","l":1},{"word":"abknicken","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk kr\xfcmmen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) kr\xfcmmen","l":1},{"word":"anwinkeln","l":1},{"word":"verkr\xfcmmen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk w\xf6lben","l":1},{"word":"Doppelkurve","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":803,"question":"bitter","answers":[{"word":"bitter"},{"word":"verbittert"},{"word":"herb","l":1},{"word":"schmerzlich","l":1},{"word":"erbittert","l":1},{"word":"bitterkalt","l":1},{"word":"schneidend","l":1},{"word":"h\xe4misch","l":1},{"word":"hantig","l":1},{"word":"rau","l":1},{"word":"hart","l":1},{"word":"Bitter","gender":"n"}]},{"id":804,"question":"blue","answers":[{"word":"Blau","gender":"n"},{"word":"blau"},{"word":"traurig"},{"word":"tr\xfcbsinnig","l":1},{"word":"nicht salonf\xe4hig","l":1},{"word":"schl\xfcpfrig","l":1},{"word":"konservativ","l":1},{"word":"melancholisch","l":1},{"word":"derb","l":1},{"word":"verpulvern","l":1},{"word":"verjubeln","l":1}]},{"id":805,"question":"certain","answers":[{"word":"bestimmt"},{"word":"sicher"},{"word":"gewiss","l":1}]},{"id":806,"question":"cold","answers":[{"word":"kalt"},{"word":"k\xfchl"},{"word":"frostig","l":1},{"word":"unvorbereitet","l":1},{"word":"gleichg\xfcltig","l":1},{"word":"gef\xfchlskalt","l":1},{"word":"K\xe4lte","gender":"f"},{"word":"Erk\xe4ltung","gender":"f"},{"word":"Schnupfen","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Grippe","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Erk\xe4ltungsinfekt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Verk\xfchlung","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":807,"question":"complete","answers":[{"word":"komplett"},{"word":"vollst\xe4ndig"},{"word":"fertig"},{"word":"absolut"},{"word":"abgeschlossen","l":1},{"word":"ganz","l":1},{"word":"voll","l":1},{"word":"v\xf6llig","l":1},{"word":"vollkommen","l":1},{"word":"l\xfcckenlos","l":1},{"word":"total","l":1},{"word":"restlos","l":1},{"word":"gesamt","l":1},{"word":"umfassend","l":1},{"word":"vollz\xe4hlig","l":1},{"word":"g\xe4nzlich","l":1},{"word":"r\xfcckhaltlos","l":1},{"word":"vollinhaltlich","l":1},{"word":"ungek\xfcrzt","l":1},{"word":"erg\xe4nzen"},{"word":"vervollst\xe4ndigen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) ausf\xfcllen"},{"word":"absolvieren"},{"word":"beenden"},{"word":"etw.Akk erledigen"},{"word":"(etw.Akk) abschlie\xdfen"},{"word":"ausf\xfchren"},{"word":"fertigstellen"},{"word":"komplettieren","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) vollenden","l":1},{"word":"durchf\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk zu Ende f\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"fertig bekommen","l":1},{"word":"ausbauen","l":1},{"word":"fertigkriegen","l":1},{"word":"fertigbekommen","l":1},{"word":"fertig kriegen","l":1},{"word":"beendigen","l":1}]},{"id":808,"question":"cruel","answers":[{"word":"grausam"},{"word":"unmenschlich"},{"word":"furchtbar"},{"word":"inhuman","l":1},{"word":"schrecklich","l":1},{"word":"unbarmherzig","l":1},{"word":"gemein","l":1},{"word":"schmerzlich","l":1},{"word":"hart","l":1},{"word":"herzlos","l":1},{"word":"erbarmungslos","l":1},{"word":"gnadenlos","l":1},{"word":"grimmig","l":1},{"word":"gef\xfchllos","l":1},{"word":"brutal","l":1},{"word":"barbarisch","l":1},{"word":"grausig","l":1}]},{"id":809,"question":"dark","answers":[{"word":"dunkel"},{"word":"tief","l":1},{"word":"d\xfcster","l":1},{"word":"lichtlos","l":1},{"word":"finster","l":1},{"word":"br\xfcnett","l":1},{"word":"geheim","l":1},{"word":"unbeleuchtet","l":1},{"word":"Dunkel","gender":"n"},{"word":"Dunkelheit","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Finsternis","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Ungewissheit","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":810,"question":"dead","answers":[{"word":"Tote","gender":"f"},{"word":"gestorben"},{"word":"verbraucht"},{"word":"erledigt"},{"word":"absolut","l":1},{"word":"abgestorben","l":1},{"word":"leer","l":1},{"word":"v\xf6llig","l":1},{"word":"kaputt","l":1},{"word":"stromlos","l":1},{"word":"\xf6de","l":1},{"word":"au\xdfer Betrieb","l":1},{"word":"entseelt","l":1},{"word":"matt","l":1},{"word":"genau"}]},{"id":811,"question":"dear","answers":[{"word":"lieb"},{"word":"teuer"},{"word":"geliebt","l":1},{"word":"verehrt","l":1},{"word":"herzig","l":1},{"word":"Schatz","gender":"m"}]},{"id":812,"question":"delicate","answers":[{"word":"zart"},{"word":"delikat"},{"word":"fein"},{"word":"zierlich"},{"word":"empfindlich"},{"word":"heikel"},{"word":"schwierig"},{"word":"zerbrechlich"},{"word":"filigran","l":1},{"word":"feinf\xfchlig","l":1},{"word":"anmutig","l":1},{"word":"grazil","l":1},{"word":"anf\xe4llig","l":1},{"word":"behutsam","l":1},{"word":"sensibel","l":1},{"word":"hochempfindlich","l":1},{"word":"taktvoll","l":1},{"word":"nicht widerstandsf\xe4hig","l":1},{"word":"schw\xe4chlich","l":1},{"word":"schm\xe4chtig","l":1},{"word":"labil","l":1}]},{"id":813,"question":"different","answers":[{"word":"unterschiedlich"},{"word":"verschieden"},{"word":"abweichend","l":1},{"word":"fremd","l":1},{"word":"andersartig","l":1},{"word":"ungleich","l":1},{"word":"verschiedenartig","l":1},{"word":"uneinheitlich","l":1},{"word":"anders geartet","l":1},{"word":"un\xe4hnlich","l":1},{"word":"andersgeartet","l":1}]},{"id":814,"question":"dirty","answers":[{"word":"schmutzig"},{"word":"verschmutzt"},{"word":"unrein","l":1},{"word":"gemein","l":1},{"word":"dreckig","l":1},{"word":"verdreckt","l":1},{"word":"schmuddelig","l":1},{"word":"zotig","l":1},{"word":"schmuddlig","l":1},{"word":"niedertr\xe4chtig","l":1},{"word":"unsauber","l":1},{"word":"beschmutzt","l":1},{"word":"schweinisch","l":1},{"word":"unanst\xe4ndig","l":1},{"word":"unfl\xe4tig","l":1},{"word":"verschmutzen"},{"word":"beschmutzen"},{"word":"schmutzig machen","l":1},{"word":"verunreinigen","l":1},{"word":"besudeln","l":1}]},{"id":815,"question":"dry","answers":[{"word":"trocken"},{"word":"k\xfchl","l":1},{"word":"ausged\xf6rrt","l":1},{"word":"d\xfcrr","l":1},{"word":"regenarm","l":1},{"word":"dr\xf6ge","l":1},{"word":"herb","l":1},{"word":"langweilig","l":1},{"word":"wasserlos","l":1},{"word":"wasserfrei","l":1},{"word":"n\xfcchtern","l":1},{"word":"niederschlagsfrei","l":1},{"word":"trocknen"},{"word":"austrocknen","l":1},{"word":"dorren","l":1},{"word":"d\xf6rren","l":1},{"word":"Verfechter des Alkoholverbots","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Alkoholgegnerin","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Alkoholgegner","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"H\xe4nger","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":816,"question":"false","answers":[{"word":"falsch"},{"word":"unwahr","l":1},{"word":"gestellt","l":1},{"word":"unecht","l":1},{"word":"k\xfcnstlich","l":1},{"word":"unrichtig","l":1},{"word":"inkorrekt","l":1},{"word":"nicht echt","l":1},{"word":"tr\xfcgerisch","l":1},{"word":"gek\xfcnstelt","l":1},{"word":"unaufrichtig","l":1},{"word":"blind","l":1},{"word":"verlogen","l":1}]},{"id":817,"question":"feeble","answers":[{"word":"schwach"},{"word":"kl\xe4glich"},{"word":"lahm","l":1},{"word":"schw\xe4chlich","l":1},{"word":"d\xfcrftig","l":1},{"word":"kraftlos","l":1},{"word":"gebrechlich","l":1},{"word":"unwirksam","l":1},{"word":"zaghaft","l":1},{"word":"wenig \xfcberzeugend","l":1},{"word":"lasch","l":1},{"word":"schlapp","l":1},{"word":"matt","l":1}]},{"id":818,"question":"female","answers":[{"word":"Frau","gender":"f"},{"word":"Weibchen","gender":"n"},{"word":"Buchse","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Weib","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Weibsbild","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Frauenzimmer","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Frauensperson","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"weiblich"}]},{"id":819,"question":"foolish","answers":[{"word":"t\xf6richt"},{"word":"albern"},{"word":"dumm","l":1},{"word":"unklug","l":1},{"word":"n\xe4rrisch","l":1},{"word":"unvern\xfcnftig","l":1},{"word":"einf\xe4ltig","l":1},{"word":"t\xf6lpisch","l":1},{"word":"t\xf6lpelhaft","l":1},{"word":"l\xe4ppisch","l":1},{"word":"d\xfcmmlich","l":1}]},{"id":820,"question":"future","answers":[{"word":"Zukunft","gender":"f"},{"word":"Futur","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"k\xfcnftig"},{"word":"zuk\xfcnftig"},{"word":"angehend"},{"word":"hink\xfcnftig","l":1},{"word":"kommend","l":1},{"word":"futurisch","l":1}]},{"id":821,"question":"green","answers":[{"word":"Gr\xfcnfl\xe4che","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Gr\xfcnanlage","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Anger","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Grasplatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"begr\xfcnt","l":1},{"word":"unreif","l":1},{"word":"naiv","l":1},{"word":"ungebrannt","l":1},{"word":"unerfahren"}]},{"id":822,"question":"ill","answers":[{"word":"krank"},{"word":"erkrankt","l":1},{"word":"schlecht","l":1},{"word":"mangelhaft","l":1},{"word":"\xfcbel","l":1},{"word":"schlimm","l":1},{"word":"malad","l":1},{"word":"Krankheit","gender":"f"},{"word":"Missgeschick","gender":"n"}]},{"id":823,"question":"last","answers":[{"word":"letzte"},{"word":"letzter"},{"word":"letztmalig","l":1},{"word":"neueste","l":1},{"word":"vorig","l":1},{"word":"neuester","l":1},{"word":"zuletzt","l":1},{"word":"als Letzter","l":1},{"word":"das letzte Mal","l":1},{"word":"bleiben"},{"word":"dauern"},{"word":"andauern"},{"word":"ausreichen"},{"word":"aushalten"},{"word":"fortdauern"},{"word":"anhalten","l":1},{"word":"w\xe4hren","l":1},{"word":"durchhalten","l":1},{"word":"bestehen bleiben","l":1},{"word":"vorhalten","l":1},{"word":"ausdauern","l":1},{"word":"Leisten","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Schuhleisten","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":824,"question":"late","answers":[{"word":"sp\xe4t"},{"word":"versp\xe4tet"},{"word":"verstorben"},{"word":"selig"}]},{"id":825,"question":"left","answers":[{"word":"linke"},{"word":"hinterlassen"},{"word":"\xfcbrig"},{"word":"verlassen","l":1},{"word":"gelassen","l":1},{"word":"\xfcberlassen","l":1},{"word":"linker","l":1},{"word":"linkes","l":1},{"word":"zur\xfcckgelassen","l":1},{"word":"belassen","l":1},{"word":"stehen gelassen","l":1},{"word":"liegen gelassen","l":1},{"word":"weggegangen","l":1},{"word":"\xfcbrig gelassen","l":1},{"word":"\xfcbriggelassen","l":1},{"word":"ausgereist","l":1},{"word":"vererbt","l":1},{"word":"links"},{"word":"nach links"},{"word":"Linke","gender":"f"},{"word":"linke Seite","gender":"f"},{"word":"verlassen"},{"word":"\xfcberlassen"},{"word":"etw.Akk lassen"},{"word":"hinterlassen"},{"word":"abfahren"},{"word":"weggehen"},{"word":"fahren","l":1},{"word":"stehen lassen","l":1},{"word":"belassen","l":1},{"word":"zur\xfccklassen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk entfernen","l":1},{"word":"ausscheiden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk \xfcbrig lassen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk liegen lassen","l":1},{"word":"abreisen","l":1},{"word":"fortgehen","l":1},{"word":"austreten","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk vererben","l":1},{"word":"aufgeben","l":1},{"word":"wegfahren","l":1},{"word":"fortfahren","l":1},{"word":"losgehen","l":1}]},{"id":826,"question":"loose","answers":[{"word":"lose"},{"word":"locker"},{"word":"los"},{"word":"frei","l":1},{"word":"weit","l":1},{"word":"schlaff","l":1},{"word":"ungebunden","l":1},{"word":"unverpackt","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) freilassen"},{"word":"etw.Akk l\xf6sen"},{"word":"abfeuern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk lockern","l":1},{"word":"feuern","l":1}]},{"id":827,"question":"loud","answers":[{"word":"laut"},{"word":"lautstark"},{"word":"grell"},{"word":"schreiend","l":1},{"word":"kr\xe4ftig","l":1},{"word":"knallig","l":1},{"word":"phonstark","l":1},{"word":"auff\xe4llig","l":1},{"word":"aufdringlich","l":1},{"word":"ger\xe4uschvoll","l":1}]},{"id":828,"question":"low","answers":[{"word":"niedrig"},{"word":"gering"},{"word":"tief"},{"word":"leise"},{"word":"klein","l":1},{"word":"nieder","l":1},{"word":"schwach","l":1},{"word":"billig","l":1},{"word":"flach","l":1},{"word":"ersch\xf6pft","l":1},{"word":"niedergedr\xfcckt","l":1},{"word":"niedergeschlagen","l":1},{"word":"unentwickelt","l":1},{"word":"kraftlos","l":1},{"word":"halblaut","l":1},{"word":"seicht","l":1},{"word":"primitiv","l":1},{"word":"Tief","gender":"n"},{"word":"Tiefpunkt","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Tiefstand","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"muhen","l":1},{"word":"br\xfcllen","l":1},{"word":"bl\xf6ken","l":1}]},{"id":829,"question":"mixed","answers":[{"word":"gemischt"},{"word":"vermischt"},{"word":"unterschiedlich","l":1},{"word":"gemixt","l":1},{"word":"durchmischt","l":1},{"word":"meliert","l":1},{"word":"anger\xfchrt","l":1},{"word":"angemacht","l":1},{"word":"uneinheitlich","l":1},{"word":"zwiesp\xe4ltig","l":1},{"word":"gemischtwirtschaftlich","l":1},{"word":"vermengen"},{"word":"vermischen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk vermischen","l":1},{"word":"mixen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verr\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"anr\xfchren","l":1},{"word":"kreuzen","l":1},{"word":"abmischen","l":1},{"word":"mengen","l":1},{"word":"ansetzen","l":1},{"word":"melieren","l":1},{"word":"versetzen","l":1},{"word":"anmachen","l":1}]},{"id":830,"question":"narrow","answers":[{"word":"eng"},{"word":"schmal"},{"word":"begrenzt","l":1},{"word":"engstirnig","l":1},{"word":"knapp","l":1},{"word":"spaltbreit","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk einschr\xe4nken"},{"word":"beschr\xe4nken"},{"word":"sichAkk verringern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk begrenzen","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk eingrenzen","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) einengen","l":1},{"word":"enger werden","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk verschm\xe4lern","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk verschm\xe4lern","l":1},{"word":"(etw.Akk) verkleinern","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk pr\xe4zisieren","l":1},{"word":"enger machen","l":1},{"word":"geringer werden","l":1},{"word":"Engstelle","gender":"f"},{"word":"enge Stelle","l":1,"gender":"f"}]},{"id":831,"question":"old","answers":[{"word":"alt"},{"word":"betagt","l":1},{"word":"bejahrt","l":1},{"word":"oll","l":1},{"word":"ehemalig","l":1}]},{"id":832,"question":"opposite","answers":[{"word":"Gegen\xfcber","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gegenteil","gender":"n"},{"word":"Gegensatz","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Gegenst\xfcck","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Gegenkathete","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"entgegengesetzt"},{"word":"gegen\xfcberliegend"},{"word":"gegens\xe4tzlich"},{"word":"umgekehrt"},{"word":"gegenl\xe4ufig","l":1},{"word":"gegenteilig","l":1},{"word":"nebenstehend","l":1},{"word":"kontr\xe4r","l":1},{"word":"ungleichnamig","l":1},{"word":"gegen\xfcber"},{"word":"vis-\xe0-vis","l":1},{"word":"auf der gegen\xfcberliegenden Seite","l":1},{"word":"gegen\xfcber"}]},{"id":833,"question":"public","answers":[{"word":"\xf6ffentlich"},{"word":"allgemein"},{"word":"staatlich"},{"word":"publik","l":1},{"word":"allgemein bekannt","l":1},{"word":"Publikum","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":834,"question":"rough","answers":[{"word":"grob"},{"word":"rau"},{"word":"roh"},{"word":"holprig"},{"word":"ungef\xe4hr"},{"word":"uneben"},{"word":"wild"},{"word":"ann\xe4hernd","l":1},{"word":"hart","l":1},{"word":"spr\xf6de","l":1},{"word":"ruppig","l":1},{"word":"derb","l":1},{"word":"schroff","l":1},{"word":"kratzig","l":1},{"word":"unsanft","l":1},{"word":"unwirsch","l":1},{"word":"rabiat","l":1},{"word":"barsch","l":1},{"word":"rissig","l":1},{"word":"gesch\xe4tzt","l":1},{"word":"st\xfcrmisch","l":1},{"word":"schaukelig","l":1},{"word":"bewegt","l":1},{"word":"schauklig","l":1},{"word":"unwegsam","l":1},{"word":"Rohentwurf","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"schruppen"}]},{"id":835,"question":"sad","answers":[{"word":"traurig"},{"word":"bedauerlich"},{"word":"betr\xfcbt","l":1},{"word":"tragisch","l":1},{"word":"schlimm","l":1},{"word":"schwerm\xfctig","l":1},{"word":"schmerzlich","l":1},{"word":"d\xfcster","l":1},{"word":"kummervoll","l":1},{"word":"trist","l":1},{"word":"bek\xfcmmert","l":1},{"word":"ungl\xfccklich","l":1},{"word":"betr\xfcblich","l":1},{"word":"beklagenswert","l":1}]},{"id":836,"question":"safe","answers":[{"word":"sicher"},{"word":"ungef\xe4hrlich"},{"word":"in Sicherheit"},{"word":"unversehrt"},{"word":"gesch\xfctzt","l":1},{"word":"gefahrlos","l":1},{"word":"geborgen","l":1},{"word":"zuverl\xe4ssig","l":1},{"word":"risikofrei","l":1},{"word":"vorsichtig","l":1},{"word":"risikolos","l":1},{"word":"ungef\xe4hrdet","l":1},{"word":"Safe","gender":"m"},{"word":"Tresor","gender":"m"},{"word":"Geldschrank","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Panzerschrank","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"Sicherheitsschrank","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":837,"question":"secret","answers":[{"word":"geheim"},{"word":"verschwiegen"},{"word":"heimlich"},{"word":"verborgen","l":1},{"word":"Geheimnis","gender":"n"},{"word":"Hehl","gender":"n"}]},{"id":838,"question":"short","answers":[{"word":"kurz"},{"word":"knapp"},{"word":"klein"},{"word":"gering","l":1},{"word":"kurz angebunden","l":1},{"word":"m\xfcrbe","l":1},{"word":"barsch","l":1},{"word":"kleingewachsen","l":1},{"word":"Kurzer","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kurzfilm","gender":"m"},{"word":"Kurzschluss","gender":"m"},{"word":"K\xfcrze","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Kurzl\xe4ufer","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":839,"question":"shut","answers":[{"word":"(etw.Akk) schlie\xdfen"},{"word":"zumachen","l":1},{"word":"zugehen","l":1},{"word":"sperren","l":1},{"word":"verriegeln","l":1},{"word":"versperren","l":1},{"word":"verschlie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"zufallen","l":1},{"word":"zuschlie\xdfen","l":1},{"word":"zuriegeln","l":1},{"word":"zudr\xfccken","l":1},{"word":"zusperren","l":1},{"word":"zusammenklappen","l":1},{"word":"geschlossen"},{"word":"verschlossen","l":1},{"word":"zugeschlossen","l":1},{"word":"versperrt","l":1},{"word":"zugegangen","l":1},{"word":"verriegelt","l":1},{"word":"zugemacht","l":1},{"word":"zugeriegelt","l":1},{"word":"zugefallen","l":1}]},{"id":840,"question":"simple","answers":[{"word":"einfach"},{"word":"simpel"},{"word":"leicht"},{"word":"schlicht"},{"word":"unkompliziert"},{"word":"klar","l":1},{"word":"problemlos","l":1},{"word":"einf\xe4ltig","l":1},{"word":"bieder","l":1},{"word":"arglos","l":1},{"word":"schn\xf6rkellos","l":1}]},{"id":841,"question":"slow","answers":[{"word":"langsam"},{"word":"schleppend","l":1},{"word":"tr\xe4ge","l":1},{"word":"bed\xe4chtig","l":1},{"word":"beh\xe4big","l":1},{"word":"schwerf\xe4llig","l":1},{"word":"lahm","l":1},{"word":"gem\xfctlich","l":1},{"word":"transusig","l":1},{"word":"geruhsam","l":1},{"word":"d\xf6sig","l":1},{"word":"begriffsstutzig","l":1},{"word":"tranig","l":1},{"word":"bummelig","l":1},{"word":"etw.Akk bremsen"},{"word":"etw.Akk verlangsamen","l":1},{"word":"hemmen","l":1},{"word":"sichAkk abschw\xe4chen","l":1}]},{"id":842,"question":"small","answers":[{"word":"klein"},{"word":"gering"},{"word":"unbedeutend","l":1},{"word":"schmal","l":1},{"word":"geringf\xfcgig","l":1},{"word":"kleinw\xfcchsig","l":1},{"word":"kleingewachsen","l":1}]},{"id":843,"question":"soft","answers":[{"word":"weich"},{"word":"soft"},{"word":"sanft"},{"word":"zart"},{"word":"leise"},{"word":"matt"},{"word":"mild","l":1},{"word":"geschmeidig","l":1},{"word":"flauschig","l":1},{"word":"bequem","l":1},{"word":"nachgiebig","l":1},{"word":"sacht","l":1},{"word":"schw\xe4chlich","l":1},{"word":"weichlich","l":1},{"word":"ged\xe4mpft","l":1},{"word":"nachgebend","l":1}]},{"id":844,"question":"solid","answers":[{"word":"solide"},{"word":"solid"},{"word":"fest"},{"word":"stabil"},{"word":"massiv","l":1},{"word":"robust","l":1},{"word":"zuverl\xe4ssig","l":1},{"word":"kompakt","l":1},{"word":"fundiert","l":1},{"word":"dauerhaft","l":1},{"word":"durchgehend","l":1},{"word":"gediegen","l":1},{"word":"gesetzt","l":1},{"word":"verl\xe4sslich","l":1},{"word":"konsistent","l":1},{"word":"k\xf6rperlich","l":1},{"word":"stabil gebaut","l":1},{"word":"von fester Beschaffenheit","l":1},{"word":"kompress","l":1},{"word":"substanzreich","l":1},{"word":"derb","l":1},{"word":"Festk\xf6rper","gender":"m"},{"word":"Feststoff","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"K\xf6rper","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"fester Stoff","l":1,"gender":"m"}]},{"id":845,"question":"special","answers":[{"word":"besondere"},{"word":"speziell"},{"word":"besonderes"},{"word":"besonderer"},{"word":"spezial","l":1},{"word":"extra","l":1},{"word":"au\xdfergew\xf6hnlich","l":1},{"word":"au\xdferordentlich","l":1},{"word":"ungew\xf6hnlich","l":1},{"word":"sonderlich","l":1},{"word":"Sonderausgabe","gender":"f"},{"word":"etwas Spezielles","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"Extrawurst","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"Extrablatt","l":1,"gender":"n"}]},{"id":846,"question":"strange","answers":[{"word":"seltsam"},{"word":"fremd"},{"word":"eigen"},{"word":"merkw\xfcrdig"},{"word":"komisch"},{"word":"eigenartig"},{"word":"fremdartig"},{"word":"au\xdfergew\xf6hnlich"},{"word":"sonderbar","l":1},{"word":"unbekannt","l":1},{"word":"ungewohnt","l":1},{"word":"ungew\xf6hnlich","l":1},{"word":"eigent\xfcmlich","l":1},{"word":"verwunderlich","l":1},{"word":"absonderlich","l":1},{"word":"befremdlich","l":1},{"word":"skurril","l":1},{"word":"kurios","l":1},{"word":"befremdend","l":1},{"word":"kauzig","l":1},{"word":"wunderlich","l":1},{"word":"gediegen","l":1},{"word":"verquer","l":1},{"word":"ulkig","l":1},{"word":"sonderlich","l":1},{"word":"verschroben","l":1},{"word":"mysteri\xf6s","l":1},{"word":"au\xdferordentlich","l":1},{"word":"un\xfcblich","l":1}]},{"id":847,"question":"thin","answers":[{"word":"d\xfcnn"},{"word":"mager"},{"word":"schlank"},{"word":"sch\xfctter"},{"word":"d\xfcrr"},{"word":"fein","l":1},{"word":"schmal","l":1},{"word":"leicht","l":1},{"word":"d\xfcnnfl\xfcssig","l":1},{"word":"licht","l":1},{"word":"hager","l":1},{"word":"sp\xe4rlich","l":1},{"word":"verd\xfcnnen"},{"word":"d\xfcnn werden","l":1},{"word":"lichten","l":1},{"word":"d\xfcnner machen","l":1}]},{"id":848,"question":"white","answers":[{"word":"wei\xdf"},{"word":"Wei\xdf","gender":"n"}]},{"id":849,"question":"wrong","answers":[{"word":"falsch"},{"word":"verkehrt"},{"word":"unrichtig","l":1},{"word":"irrig","l":1},{"word":"unrecht","l":1},{"word":"nicht richtig","l":1},{"word":"Unrecht","gender":"n"},{"word":"Tort","l":1,"gender":"m"},{"word":"zivilrechtliches Delikt","l":1,"gender":"n"},{"word":"zivilrechtlich unerlaubte Handlung","l":1,"gender":"f"},{"word":"jdm. Unrecht tun"},{"word":"benachteiligen"},{"word":"jdm. ein Leid antun","l":1},{"word":"jdm. Unrecht zuf\xfcgen","l":1},{"word":"ungerecht behandeln","l":1}]}]')},36:function(e,r,d){e.exports=d(50)},50:function(e,r,d){"use strict";d.r(r);var n=d(0),o=d.n(n),w=d(23),l=d.n(w),g=d(7),t=d(3),i=Object(n.createContext)(null),s=Object(n.createContext)(function(){});function a(){return Object(n.useContext)(i)}function u(e){var r=e.children,d=Object(n.useState)(null),w=Object(t.a)(d,2),l=w[0],g=w[1];return o.a.createElement(i.Provider,{value:l},o.a.createElement(s.Provider,{value:g},r))}var f=d(10),h=d(9),c=d(1),m=d(2);function k(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  color: #c66;\n"]);return k=function(){return e},e}function b(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  color: #0c6;\n"]);return b=function(){return e},e}function p(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  color: #06c;\n"]);return p=function(){return e},e}var A=m.b.div(p()),z=m.b.div(b()),S=m.b.div(k());function q(e){var r,d=e.input,n=e.rightness;return null===n&&(r=A),!0===n&&(r=z),!1===n&&(r=S),o.a.createElement(r,null,d)}var v=d(14);function B(e,r){var d=1===e?"hide":"show";return o.a.createElement("span",{className:d},r)}function G(e){Object(n.useEffect)(function(){return document.addEventListener("keydown",e),function(){document.removeEventListener("keydown",e)}})}function K(){var e=Object(c.a)([""]);return K=function(){return e},e}function E(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  // color: #666;\n"]);return E=function(){return e},e}function F(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  // color: #f66;\n"]);return F=function(){return e},e}function j(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  // color: #66f;\n"]);return j=function(){return e},e}function V(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  opacity: 0.5;\n  font-size: 50%;\n"]);return V=function(){return e},e}function W(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n"]);return W=function(){return e},e}function L(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  list-style: none;\n  font-size: 50%;\n  color: #888;\n  max-height: 50vh;\n  overflow-y: auto;\n"]);return L=function(){return e},e}var R=m.b.ul(L()),T=m.b.li(W()),H=m.b.li(V()),P=m.b.div(j()),D=m.b.div(F()),M=m.b.div(E()),O=m.b.div(K());var y=function(e){var r=e.answers;return o.a.createElement(R,null,r.map(function(e,r){var d=function(e){var r="m"===e.gender,d="f"===e.gender,n="n"===e.gender,w="";r&&(w="der ");d&&(w="die ");n&&(w="das ");var l=O;r&&(l=P);d&&(l=D);n&&(l=M);return o.a.createElement(l,null,"".concat(w).concat(e.word))}(e);return e.l?o.a.createElement(H,{key:r},d):o.a.createElement(T,{key:r},d)}))},Z=d(8),N=d.n(Z),x=d(11),U=d(26),C=d(33),I=d(12);function J(e,r){var d=Object.keys(e);if(Object.getOwnPropertySymbols){var n=Object.getOwnPropertySymbols(e);r&&(n=n.filter(function(r){return Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(e,r).enumerable})),d.push.apply(d,n)}return d}function Q(e){for(var r=1;r<arguments.length;r++){var d=null!=arguments[r]?arguments[r]:{};r%2?J(d,!0).forEach(function(r){Object(I.a)(e,r,d[r])}):Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors?Object.defineProperties(e,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors(d)):J(d).forEach(function(r){Object.defineProperty(e,r,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(d,r))})}return e}var _=new(d(30).a)("DrawingsDatabase");_.version(1).stores({drawings:"++id,question,drawing"});var Y=_.drawings;function $(){return($=Object(x.a)(N.a.mark(function e(r,d){return N.a.wrap(function(e){for(;;)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.abrupt("return",_.transaction("rw",Y,Object(x.a)(N.a.mark(function e(){var n,o,w;return N.a.wrap(function(e){for(;;)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.next=2,re(r);case 2:if(n=e.sent,o={question:r,drawing:d},!n){e.next=9;break}return w=n.id,e.abrupt("return",Y.put(Q({id:w},o)));case 9:return e.abrupt("return",Y.add(o));case 10:case"end":return e.stop()}},e)}))));case 1:case"end":return e.stop()}},e)}))).apply(this,arguments)}function X(e){return ee.apply(this,arguments)}function ee(){return(ee=Object(x.a)(N.a.mark(function e(r){var d;return N.a.wrap(function(e){for(;;)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.next=2,re(r);case 2:if(!(d=e.sent)){e.next=7;break}return e.abrupt("return",d.drawing);case 7:return e.abrupt("return",null);case 8:case"end":return e.stop()}},e)}))).apply(this,arguments)}function re(e){return Y.where("question").equals(e).first()}function de(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  position: fixed;\n  right: 0;\n  top: 0;\n  color: red;\n"]);return de=function(){return e},e}function ne(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  position: fixed;\n  left: 0;\n  top: 0;\n  width: 100vw;\n  height: 100vh;\n"]);return ne=function(){return e},e}var oe="#fff",we="#000",le=3,ge=1,te=m.b.div(ne()),ie=m.b.div(de()),se=function(e,r){!function(e,r){$.apply(this,arguments)}(e,r.getSaveData())},ae=JSON.stringify({lines:[],width:10,height:10});var ue=function(e){var r=e.question,d=e.drawing;G(function(e){"Delete"===e.key&&d&&w.current.undo()}),Object(n.useEffect)(function(){function e(){return(e=Object(x.a)(N.a.mark(function e(){var d;return N.a.wrap(function(e){for(;;)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.next=2,X(r);case 2:(d=e.sent)?w.current&&w.current.loadSaveData(d):w.current&&w.current.loadSaveData(ae);case 4:case"end":return e.stop()}},e)}))).apply(this,arguments)}!function(){e.apply(this,arguments)}()},[r]);var w=Object(n.useRef)(),l=Object(U.a)(),g=l.vw,t=l.vh,i=a();return o.a.createElement(te,null,i?null:o.a.createElement(C.a,{ref:w,onChange:function(e){return se(r,e)},disabled:!d,catenaryColor:oe,brushRadius:le,brushColor:we,lazyRadius:ge,canvasWidth:g,canvasHeight:t,hideGrid:!0,immediateLoading:!0,loadTimeOffset:0}),d&&o.a.createElement(ie,null,"Drawing mode"))};function fe(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  color: #fff;\n  margin: 10px 0;\n"]);return fe=function(){return e},e}function he(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  left: 50%;\n  transform: translateY(","px) translateX(-50%);\n  height: ","px;\n  width: ","px;\n  border-radius: 50%;\n  background-color: ",";\n"]);return he=function(){return e},e}function ce(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  width: 100%;\n  display: flex;\n  > div {\n    top: ","%;\n    position: absolute;\n  }\n  > div:nth-child(1) {\n    right: calc(50% + ","px);\n  }\n  > div:nth-child(2) {\n    // Circle below\n  }\n  > div:nth-child(3) {\n    left: calc(50% + ","px);\n  }\n"]);return ce=function(){return e},e}function me(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  position: absolute;\n  left: 50%;\n  top: 50%;\n"]);return me=function(){return e},e}function ke(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  position: absolute;\n  left: 0;\n  top: 0;\n  width: 100%;\n  height: 100%;\n  overflow: hidden;\n"]);return ke=function(){return e},e}function be(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  position: fixed;\n  z-index: 100;\n  right: 0;\n  bottom: 0;\n  color: gray;\n  font-size: 32px;\n"]);return be=function(){return e},e}function pe(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  position: fixed;\n  z-index: 100;\n  left: 0;\n  bottom: 0;\n  color: gray;\n  font-size: 32px;\n"]);return pe=function(){return e},e}function Ae(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  font-size: 48pt;\n  display: flex;\n  overflow: hidden;\n  ","\n"]);return Ae=function(){return e},e}function ze(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  * {\n    margin: 0;\n    padding: 0;\n  }\n  html, body, #root, #root > div {\n    height: 100%;\n  }\n  .show, .hide {\n    transition: opacity 0.3s;\n  }\n  .show {\n    opacity: 1;\n  }\n  .hide {\n    opacity: 0;\n  }\n"]);return ze=function(){return e},e}var Se=Object(m.a)(ze()),qe=m.b.div(Ae(),function(e){return e.finished?"":"pointer-events: none;"}),ve=m.b.div(pe()),Be=m.b.div(be()),Ge=m.b.div(ke()),Ke=m.b.div(me()),Ee=m.b.div(ce(),30,20,20),Fe=m.b.div(he(),38,10,10,function(e){return null===e.rightness?"#06c":!0===e.rightness?"#0c6":"#c66"}),je=m.b.hr(fe());var Ve=function(e){var r=e.rightness,d=e.info,n=e.center,w=e.stats,l=e.left,g=e.right,t=e.done,i=Object(h.b)({config:{friction:1,clamp:1},from:{width:"100%",opacity:1,transform:"rotate(0deg) scale(1)",transformOrigin:"center"},to:t?[{opacity:.5,transform:"rotate(360deg) scale(0.5)"},{opacity:0,transform:"rotate(0deg) scale(0)"}]:[]}),s=a();return o.a.createElement(qe,{finished:s},o.a.createElement(Se,null),o.a.createElement(Ge,null,o.a.createElement(Ke,null,n)),o.a.createElement(h.a.div,{style:i},o.a.createElement(Ee,null,o.a.createElement("div",null,l),o.a.createElement(Fe,{rightness:r}),o.a.createElement("div",null,g))),d?o.a.createElement(ve,null,o.a.createElement("ul",null,d.map(function(e,r){return"---"===e?o.a.createElement(je,{key:r}):o.a.createElement("li",{key:r},e)}))):null,o.a.createElement(Be,null,w))};function We(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  position: absolute;\n  left: 0;\n  top: 30px;\n  background-color: white;\n  z-index: 100;\n"]);return We=function(){return e},e}function Le(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  & > span {\n    display: none;\n  }\n\n  &:hover {\n    & > span {\n      display: block;\n    }\n  }\n\n  position: relative;\n"]);return Le=function(){return e},e}function Re(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  text-decoration: ",";\n  color: ",";\n"]);return Re=function(){return e},e}function Te(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  position: absolute;\n  font-size: 32px;\n  white-space: nowrap;\n"]);return Te=function(){return e},e}function He(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  transform: translate(-50%, -50%);\n"]);return He=function(){return e},e}var Pe=m.b.div(He()),De=m.b.div(Te()),Me=m.b.div(Re(),function(e){return e.done?"none":e.hit?"none":"line-through"},function(e){return e.done?e.hit?"#0c6":"#c66":"#ddd"}),Oe=m.b.div(Le()),ye=m.b.span(We());var Ze=function(e){var r=e.x,d=e.y,n=(e.children,e.hit),w=e.word,l=e.done,g=e.answers,t=Object(h.b)({transform:"translate(".concat(r,"px, ").concat(d,"px)"),from:{transform:"translate(".concat(r,"px, ").concat(d,"px)")}}),i=l?o.a.createElement(Oe,null,w,o.a.createElement(ye,null,o.a.createElement(y,{answers:g}))):w;return o.a.createElement(De,null,o.a.createElement(h.a.div,{style:t},o.a.createElement(Pe,null,o.a.createElement(Me,{done:l,hit:n},i))))},Ne=d(52),xe=d(31);function Ue(){var e=Object(c.a)(["\n  display: none;\n"]);return Ue=function(){return e},e}var Ce=m.b.div(Ue()),Ie=function(e,r){var d=e.durationSec,w=e.onDone,l=e.paused,g=Object(n.useState)(null),i=Object(t.a)(g,2),s=i[0],a=i[1],u=Object(n.useState)(null),f=Object(t.a)(u,2),h=f[0],c=f[1],m=Object(n.useState)(!1),k=Object(t.a)(m,2),b=k[0],p=k[1],A=Object(n.useState)(null),z=Object(t.a)(A,2),S=z[0],q=z[1],v=Object(n.useState)(null),B=Object(t.a)(v,2),G=B[0],K=B[1],E=G||d;Object(n.useEffect)(function(){var e=new Date;if(l){var r=E-Object(Ne.a)(e,s);q(r)}else S&&(a(e),K(S))},[l]),Object(xe.a)(function(){if(!b&&!l&&s){var e=new Date,r=Object(Ne.a)(e,s);r!==h&&c(r),E-h<=0&&(w(),p(!0))}},100),Object(n.useImperativeHandle)(r,function(){return{start:function(){s||a(new Date)},finish:function(){b||(w(),p(!0))}}});var F=E-h;return o.a.createElement(Ce,null,F," sec.")},Je=Ie=Object(n.forwardRef)(Ie),Qe=d(4),_e=d(6);function Ye(e,r){var d=localStorage.getItem(e);return d?JSON.parse(d):r}function $e(e,r){r=JSON.stringify(r),localStorage.setItem(e,r)}var Xe=function(){function e(r){Object(Qe.a)(this,e),this.allCards=r}return Object(_e.a)(e,[{key:"getAllCards",value:function(){return this.allCards}},{key:"getCardPoints",value:function(){return Ye("CARD_POINTS_KEY",{})}},{key:"_getLastPoint",value:function(){return Ye("LAST_POINT_KEY",0)}},{key:"_setLastPoint",value:function(e){$e("LAST_POINT_KEY",e)}},{key:"getNewPoint",value:function(){var e=this._getLastPoint()+1;return this._setLastPoint(e),e}},{key:"_getCardDeltas",value:function(){return Ye("CARD_DELTAS_KEY",{})}},{key:"getDelta",value:function(e){return this._getCardDeltas()[e]||1}},{key:"recordDelta",value:function(e,r){var d=this._getCardDeltas();d[e]=r,$e("CARD_DELTAS_KEY",d)}},{key:"recordPoint",value:function(e,r){var d=this.getCardPoints();d[e]=r,$e("CARD_POINTS_KEY",d)}}]),e}(),er=function(){function e(r){Object(Qe.a)(this,e),this.cards=r}return Object(_e.a)(e,[{key:"hasMore",value:function(){return!!this.cards.length}},{key:"takeNextCard",value:function(){return this.cards.shift()}}]),e}(),rr=function(){function e(r,d){Object(Qe.a)(this,e),this.sessionDeck=r,this.zeroDeck=d}return Object(_e.a)(e,[{key:"takeNextCard",value:function(){return this.sessionDeck.hasMore()?this.sessionDeck.takeNextCard():this.zeroDeck.takeNextCard()}}]),e}();var dr=function(){function e(r){Object(Qe.a)(this,e),this.storage=r;var d=this.storage.getAllCards(),n=this.storage.getCardPoints(),o=this.storage.getNewPoint();this.point=o;var w=function(e,r,d){var n=e.filter(function(e){return!r[e.id]}),o=new er(n),w=function(e,r){var d=Object.entries(e).filter(function(e){var d=Object(t.a)(e,2);d[0];return d[1]<=r});return(d=Object(g.sortBy)(d,function(e){return e[0]})).map(function(e){var r=Object(t.a)(e,2),d=r[0];r[1];return d})}(r,d).map(function(r){return e.find(function(e){return e.id==r})}),l=new er(w);return{zeroDeck:o,sessionDeck:l}}(d,n,o),l=w.zeroDeck,i=w.sessionDeck,s=new rr(i,l);this.player=s}return Object(_e.a)(e,[{key:"takeNextCard",value:function(){var e=this.player.takeNextCard();if(this.lastCard=e,e)return this.storage.recordPoint(e.id,this.point),e}},{key:"recordHit",value:function(){var e=this.lastCard.id,r=this.storage.getDelta(e)+1,d=this.point+r;this.storage.recordDelta(e,r),this.storage.recordPoint(e,d)}},{key:"recordMiss",value:function(){var e=this.lastCard.id,r=this.point+1;this.storage.recordDelta(e,1),this.storage.recordPoint(e,r)}}]),e}(),nr=null;var or=function(e){if(nr)return nr;var r=new Xe(e);return nr=new dr(r)};var wr=function(){var e=Object(n.useState)(!1),r=Object(t.a)(e,2),d=r[0],o=r[1],w=function(){return o(!d)};return G(function(e){"Insert"===e.key&&w()}),[d,o]},lr=60,gr=["Type a translation with enter when you are ready","Press esc to see results of the session","If you want to start again \u2014 reload the page","---",'\xab\xe4\xbb can be produced by typing \xaba:\xbb or \xaba"\xbb',"\xab\xdf\xbb can be replaced with just \xabss\xbb","Omit \xabder/die/das\xbb if you feel like","---","Press \xabinsert\xbb to enter/exit drawing mode","Press \xabdelete\xbb to delete the last line","The drawing will be associated with the current word"],tr=/^.$/;var ir=["???"];var sr=function(){var e=Object(n.useState)(!1),r=Object(t.a)(e,2),d=r[0],w=r[1],l=Object(n.useState)(!1),i=Object(t.a)(l,2),a=i[0],u=i[1],c=Object(n.useState)(0),m=Object(t.a)(c,2),k=m[0],b=m[1],p=Object(n.useState)(0),A=Object(t.a)(p,2),z=A[0],S=A[1],K=Object(n.useRef)();function E(){K.current&&K.current.finish()}var F=Object(n.useState)(""),j=Object(t.a)(F,2),V=j[0],W=j[1],L=Object(n.useState)([]),R=Object(t.a)(L,2),T=R[0],H=R[1],P=Object(n.useState)(null),D=Object(t.a)(P,2),M=D[0],O=D[1];(M=or().lastCard)||(or().lastCard?O(or().lastCard):a||E());var Z=M||{question:"",answers:[]},N=Object(n.useState)(!1),x=Object(t.a)(N,2),U=x[0],C=x[1],I=Object(n.useState)(!1),J=Object(t.a)(I,2),Q=J[0],_=J[1],Y=function(){var e=[];Object(g.times)(1,function(){var r=function(){var e=Object(g.random)(0,2*Math.PI,!0),r=Object(g.random)(400,500);return{dx:r*Math.cos(e),dy:r*Math.sin(e)}}(),d=r.dx,n=r.dy,o={input:V,word:Z.question,answers:Z.answers,x:d,y:n,hit:Q};e.push(o)}),H(T.concat(e)),O(or().takeNextCard()),W("")},$=function(){w(!0)};G(function(e){if(!a&&!e.ctrlKey){var r=U;if("Escape"===e.key)E();else if("Enter"===e.key)if($(),U)C(!1),Y();else{(V=V.trim())||(V=Object(g.sample)(ir),W(V));var d=function(e,r){var d=new RegExp("\b".concat(Object(g.escapeRegExp)(e),"\b"));return!!r.find(function(r){var n=r.word,o=n.replace(/\xdf/g,"ss"),w=[n,o],l=function(e){var r=w.map(e);w.push.apply(w,Object(f.a)(r))};return"m"===r.gender&&l(function(e){return"der ".concat(e)}),"f"===r.gender&&l(function(e){return"die ".concat(e)}),"n"===r.gender&&l(function(e){return"das ".concat(e)}),w.find(function(r){return r===e||r.match(d)})})}(V,Z.answers);d?(b(k+1),or().recordHit()):(S(z+1),or().recordMiss()),_(d),C(!0)}else if("Backspace"===e.key){if(r)return;W(V.substring(0,V.length-1))}else if(tr.test(e.key)){if(r)return;$(),V+=e.key,W(function(e){if(e.length<2)return e;var r=e[e.length-1],d=e[e.length-2];if(":"!==r&&'"'!==r)return e;var n=function(r){return e.slice(0,e.length-2)+r};return"A"===d?n("\xc4"):"a"===d?n("\xe4"):"O"===d?n("\xd6"):"o"===d?n("\xf6"):"U"===d?n("\xdc"):"u"===d?n("\xfc"):e}(V))}}});var X=Object(n.useContext)(s),ee=wr(),re=Object(t.a)(ee,2),de=re[0],ne=(re[1],a?"#06c":"gray"),oe=Object(h.b)({color:ne,padding:a?30:0,from:{color:"gray",padding:0}}),we=Object(h.b)({opacity:a?0:1,from:{opacity:1}}),le=U?Q:null;return o.a.createElement(o.a.Fragment,null,o.a.createElement(ue,{question:Z.question,drawing:de}),o.a.createElement(Ve,{done:a,rightness:le,info:d?null:gr,center:T.map(function(e,r){return o.a.createElement(Ze,{answers:e.answers,x:e.x,y:e.y,hit:e.hit,word:e.word,key:r,done:a})}),left:Z.question,right:o.a.createElement(o.a.Fragment,null,o.a.createElement(q,{input:V,rightness:le}),U?o.a.createElement("div",null,o.a.createElement(y,{answers:Z.answers})):null),stats:o.a.createElement(h.a.div,{style:oe},o.a.createElement(h.a.div,{style:we},o.a.createElement(Je,{ref:K,durationSec:lr,onDone:function(){X(!0),u(!0),function(e,r){var d=[],n=0;Object(g.times)(e.length,function(r){Object(g.times)(e.length,function(e){d.push({source:r,target:e,index:n}),n+=1})});var o=Object(v.d)(e).force("links",Object(v.c)(d)).force("collide",Object(v.b)(100)).force("center",Object(v.a)());return function(){o.tick(100),e=Object(f.a)(e),r(e)}}(T,H)()},paused:de})),o.a.createElement("div",null,k," hit",B(k,"s")),o.a.createElement("div",null,z," miss",B(z,"es")))}))},ar=d(32);var ur=function(){var e=ar;return e=Object(g.shuffle)(e),or(e).takeNextCard(),o.a.createElement(u,null,o.a.createElement(sr,{questions:e}))},fr=Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));function hr(e,r){navigator.serviceWorker.register(e).then(function(e){e.onupdatefound=function(){var d=e.installing;null!=d&&(d.onstatechange=function(){"installed"===d.state&&(navigator.serviceWorker.controller?(console.log("New content is available and will be used when all tabs for this page are closed. See https://bit.ly/CRA-PWA."),r&&r.onUpdate&&r.onUpdate(e)):(console.log("Content is cached for offline use."),r&&r.onSuccess&&r.onSuccess(e)))})}}).catch(function(e){console.error("Error during service worker registration:",e)})}l.a.render(o.a.createElement(ur,null),document.getElementById("root")),function(e){if("serviceWorker"in navigator){if(new URL("/ogden-german",window.location.href).origin!==window.location.origin)return;window.addEventListener("load",function(){var r="".concat("/ogden-german","/service-worker.js");fr?(!function(e,r){fetch(e).then(function(d){var n=d.headers.get("content-type");404===d.status||null!=n&&-1===n.indexOf("javascript")?navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(e){e.unregister().then(function(){window.location.reload()})}):hr(e,r)}).catch(function(){console.log("No internet connection found. App is running in offline mode.")})}(r,e),navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(){console.log("This web app is being served cache-first by a service worker. To learn more, visit https://bit.ly/CRA-PWA")})):hr(r,e)})}}()}},[[36,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.f6b9a802.chunk.js.map